(One day in November with colorful fall foliage)
(يوم واحد من شهر نوفمبر مع أوراق الشجر الملونة)
This is nice. I hear echoes in here.
هذا جميل. أسمع أصداء هنا.
Aren't they supposed to be here by now?
أليس من المفترض أن يكونوا هنا الآن؟
Why would they be absent from school?
ولماذا سيتغيبون عن المدرسة؟
They must've gotten too lax.
لا بد أنهم أصبحوا متساهلين للغاية.
This is not right. I'm going to scold them.
هذا ليس صحيحا. انا ذاهب لتوبيخهم.
Look at these. Are these made by the fans?
أنظر إلى هذه. هل هذه من صنع المعجبين؟
My, they're cute.
يا إلهي، إنهم لطيفون.
- That's really great. - Let's go in.
- هذا عظيم حقا. - دعنا ندخل.
- Oh, my. What? - Where are you going?
- يا بلدي. ماذا؟ - إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
- It's been a while. - Hey, you're finally here.
- لقد كان بعض الوقت. - مهلا، أنت أخيرا هنا.
- Where is Mimi Minu? - Wait. Hold on.
- أين ميمي مينو؟ - انتظر. يتمسك.
- What? Christian is here. - This is my seat now.
- ماذا؟ كريستيان هنا. - هذا مقعدي الآن.
- I'm glad you're here. - Come on, baby!
- أنا سعيد لأنك هنا. - هيا يا عزيزي!
- I can't watch this. - Let's do this!
- لا أستطيع مشاهدة هذا. - دعونا نفعل هذا!
- What was that? Kids watch this. - That's inappropriate.
- ماذا كان هذا؟ الاطفال يشاهدون هذا. - هذا غير مناسب.
- What's wrong with him? - Let's go!
- ما هو الخطأ معه؟ - دعنا نذهب!
- Hi!
- أهلاً! - أهلاً!
My friends!
أصدقائي!
- Christian. - Yes, Ho Dong.
- مسيحي. - نعم، هو دونغ.
Did you transfer to this school again?
هل انتقلت إلى هذه المدرسة مرة أخرى؟
- Yes, I'm back. - What's with him?
- نعم، لقد عدت. - ماذا به؟
- Christian, why are you here? - Yes?
- كريستيان، لماذا أنت هنا؟ - نعم؟
I came here for the foreigners special.
لقد جئت إلى هنا للأجانب بشكل خاص.
(Christian appeared in Episode 503 representing Mexico.)
(ظهر كريستيان في الحلقة 503 ممثلاً للمكسيك.)
(It was supposed to have my full name on it.)
(كان من المفترض أن يكون اسمي الكامل عليها.)
(His stories were as impressive as his name.)
(كانت قصصه مثيرة للإعجاب مثل اسمه).
- Please continue. - The show hit high ratings.
- يرجى الاستمرار. - حقق العرض تقييمات عالية.
- That's right. - The ratings were very high.
- هذا صحيح. - التقييمات كانت عالية جدًا.
- That's impressive. - So what are you going to do today?
- هذا مثير للإعجاب. - إذن ماذا ستفعل اليوم؟
I'm a member of the newspaper club.
أنا عضو في نادي الصحف.
- Oh, you are? - Yes, I am.
- أوه، أنت؟ - نعم أنا.
I've watched the episodes where you guys made newspaper.
لقد شاهدت الحلقات التي صنعتم فيها الصحف يا رفاق.
- But... - You need to write articles.
- لكن... - أنت بحاجة إلى كتابة المقالات.
It was boring, to be honest.
كان الأمر مملاً، لأكون صادقًا.
- Was it boring? - It was boring.
- هل كان مملاً؟ - كان مملاً.
- Because it was boring... - Is he talking about our newspaper?
- لأنه كان مملاً... - هل يتحدث عن صحيفتنا؟
- It was not interesting. So... - Yes?
- لم يكن الأمر مثيرا للاهتمام. إذن... - نعم؟
- I came up with a new topic. - What's the topic?
- لقد توصلت إلى موضوع جديد. - ما هو الموضوع؟
"I file a complaint against my friends."
"أقدم شكوى ضد أصدقائي."
- So we can tell on one another? - File a complaint.
- حتى نتمكن من معرفة بعضنا البعض؟ - تقديم شكوى.
That's right. You can tell on one another.
هذا صحيح. يمكنك أن تقول على بعضها البعض.
- I'll say something about Ho Dong. - I'll complain about Hee Chul.
- سأقول شيئا عن هو دونغ. - سأشتكي من هيي تشول.
- You should write it down. - Okay.
- يجب عليك كتابتها. - تمام.
- He doesn't go home after a shoot. - Oh, my.
- لا يعود إلى منزله بعد التصوير. - يا بلدي.
After we finished the shoot last week,
بعد أن انتهينا من التصوير الأسبوع الماضي
I was walking to my car to go home.
كنت أسير إلى سيارتي للعودة إلى المنزل.
And I saw Ho Dong's manager...
ورأيت مدير هو دونغ...
- getting out of the car... - What?
- الخروج من السيارة... - ماذا؟
with naengmyeon in his hands.
مع naengmyeon في يديه.
- I asked, "Aren't you going home?"
- ماذا؟ - سألت: "ألا تعود إلى المنزل؟"
He said that he couldn't leave as Ho Dong was going to eat it.
قال إنه لا يستطيع المغادرة لأن هو دونغ كان سيأكله.
- He doesn't go straight home. - Eat at home.
- لا يذهب مباشرة إلى المنزل. - تناول الطعام في المنزل.
- Why would you not go home? - I mean...
- لماذا لا تذهب إلى المنزل؟ - أعني...
- Why would he eat three meals here? - I'm going to ask him later.
- لماذا يأكل ثلاث وجبات هنا؟ - سأسأله لاحقا.
Since we're talking about Ho Dong,
بما أننا نتحدث عن هو دونغ،
I'll tell you something about him. This could be on the first page.
سأخبرك شيئا عنه. قد يكون هذا في الصفحة الأولى.
- Oh, really? - Nice.
- أوه حقًا؟ - لطيف - جيد.
He has Pyongyang naengmyeon very often these days, right?
لديه ناينغ ميون في بيونغ يانغ كثيرًا هذه الأيام، أليس كذلك؟
- I guess the word spread. - I see.
- أعتقد أن الكلمة انتشرت. - أرى.
He was chosen as the South Korean celebrity...
تم اختياره كمشاهير كوريا الجنوبية...
whom Kim Jong Un wants to meet the most.
الذي يريد كيم جونغ أون مقابلته أكثر من غيره.
- Gosh, seriously. - Is that true?
- يا إلهي، بجدية. - هل هذا صحيح؟
- Hey, you... - Hey...
- مهلا، أنت... - مهلا ...
You shouldn't make too big a deal out of it.
لا ينبغي عليك أن تجعل صفقة كبيرة للخروج منه.
- But... - You shouldn't cross the line.
- لكن... - لا يجب أن تتجاوز الحدود.
"North Korea Invites Ho Dong."
“كوريا الشمالية تدعو هو دونغ”.
It's snowballing!
انها كرة الثلج!
He's the PR ambassador of Pyongyang now.
وهو سفير العلاقات العامة في بيونغ يانغ الآن.
("Ho Dong Shows off, Wrapped with Pyongyang naengmyeon")
("هو دونغ يتباهى، مغلفًا ببيونغ يانغ ناينغ ميون")
("'I'm As Proud As Luxury Brand Ambassadors.'")
(""أنا فخور مثل سفراء العلامات التجارية الفاخرة."")
- The PR ambassador of Pyongyang. - Exactly.
- سفير العلاقات العامة في بيونغ يانغ. - بالضبط.
- No, that's not true. - Yes, it's true.
- لا، هذا ليس صحيحا. - نعم هذا صحيح.
Did anyone in your family have to leave North Korea?
هل اضطر أي شخص في عائلتك إلى مغادرة كوريا الشمالية؟
- No... - Then why do you...
- لا... - إذن لماذا...
eat Pyongyang naengmyeon so often?
أكل بيونغ يانغ naengmyeon في كثير من الأحيان؟
- Who eats it that often? - He can't help it.
- من يأكله كثيرًا؟ - لا يستطيع مساعدته.
- Oh, my gosh. - He startled me.
- يا إلهي. - لقد أذهلني.
- Oh, yes! - Our transfer students are here.
- أوه، نعم! - طلابنا المنقولون هنا.
Is this Brother School?
هل هذه مدرسة الأخ؟
- Yes. - Why does he speak in a dialect?
- نعم. - لماذا يتكلم بلهجة؟
Oh, is that so?
أوه، هل هذا صحيح؟
This is Brother School.
هذه هي مدرسة الأخ.
- Why are they angry? - ALLDAY
- لماذا هم غاضبون؟ - طوال اليوم
Oh, they're trying to give off such vibes.
أوه، إنهم يحاولون إطلاق مثل هذه المشاعر.
- Hey, why... - They've changed their hairstyles.
- مهلا، لماذا... - لقد غيروا تسريحات الشعر الخاصة بهم.
Come on, baby
هيا يا عزيزي
They're the famous ALLDAY PROJECT.
إنهم مشروع ALLDAY الشهير.
ALLDAY PROJECT!
مشروع طوال اليوم!
(Those whom we waited for all day are here.)
(أولئك الذين انتظرناهم طوال اليوم موجودون هنا).
- This is great. - Hi.
- هذا عظيم. - أهلاً.
- This is awesome.
- هذا رائع. - أهلاً.
- We are...
- أهلاً. - نحن...
from Beyond The Limits Of Genres And Formats High School.
من خارج حدود الأنواع والأشكال الثانوية.
That's where we came from.
ومن هنا أتينا.
- I'm ANNIE. - ANNIE.
- أنا آني. - آني.
- It's nice to meet you. - ANNIE!
- تشرفنا. - آني!
- ANNIE - And...
- آني - و...
Hi, I'm WOOCHAN.
مرحبًا، أنا ووشان.
- Yes! - WOOCHAN.
- نعم! - ووشان.
Hi, I'm YOUNGSEO.
مرحبًا، أنا يونغسيو.
- It's good to see you. - It's nice to meet you.
- من الجيد أن أراك. - تشرفنا.
- And... - Well... I am...
- و... - حسنًا... أنا...
As you all must know,
وكما يجب أن تعلموا جميعا،
I'm TARZZAN also known as Pretty Boy T.
أنا طرزان المعروف أيضًا باسم Pretty Boy T.
Oh, yes. TARZZAN is here.
أوه نعم. طرزان هنا.
- TARZZAN! - Really?
- طرزان! - حقًا؟
- And... - Please go on.
- و... - من فضلك استمر.
I am BAILEY.
أنا بيلي.
- That was a cool self-introduction. - Indeed.
- لقد كانت تلك مقدمة رائعة للذات. - بالفعل.
("ALLDAY PROJECT Was Voted as Newcomer of the Year")
("تم التصويت لمشروع ALLDAY باعتباره الوافد الجديد لهذا العام")
("ALLDAY PROJECT Ranks 94th on Billboard Global 200")
("مشروع AllDAY يحتل المرتبة 94 على Billboard Global 200")
("The Debut Song Makes Top 10 on Melon Charts on Its Release Day")
("الأغنية الأولى تصل إلى المراكز العشرة الأولى في مخططات البطيخ في يوم إصدارها")
(They swept all the music charts as soon as they made their debut!)
(لقد اكتسحوا جميع المخططات الموسيقية بمجرد ظهورهم لأول مرة!)
(The total number of views of their music videos is over 70 million.)
(يتجاوز إجمالي عدد مشاهدات مقاطع الفيديو الموسيقية الخاصة بهم 70 مليونًا).
(The monstrous newcomers who achieved a meteoric rise)
(الوافدون الجدد الوحشيون الذين حققوا صعودًا نيزكيًا)
By the way, TARZZAN, what did you shout...
بالمناسبة، طرزان، ماذا صرخت...
as you opened the door and walked in?
عندما فتحت الباب ودخلت؟
I asked if this was Brother School.
سألت إذا كانت هذه مدرسة الأخ.
- He speaks in dialect. - Do you talk in dialect on purpose?
- يتحدث باللهجة. - هل تتحدث باللهجة عمداً؟
No, I'm from Ulsan. I'm an Ulsaner.
لا، أنا من أولسان. أنا أولسانر.
- He's an Ulsaner too. - Oh, no.
- وهو أولسانر أيضا. - أوه لا.
- Yeong Cheol will become chatty. - I'm from Ulsan too.
- سوف يصبح Yeong Cheol ثرثارًا. - أنا من أولسان أيضا.
I'm from Ulsan too.
أنا من أولسان أيضًا.
- We're in trouble. He's from Ulsan. - Did you know I was from Ulsan?
- نحن في ورطة. إنه من أولسان. - هل تعلم أنني من أولسان؟
Every morning, on my way to school,
كل صباح، في طريقي إلى المدرسة،
I heard you sing like this. "A Better Yeong Cheol"
سمعت أنك تغني مثل هذا. "يونغ تشول أفضل"
- What is that? - You listened to my radio show.
- ما هذا؟ - لقد استمعت إلى برنامجي الإذاعي.
- That's not important. - Hold on.
- هذا ليس مهما. - يتمسك.
- He said it by himself...
- هذا ليس مهما. - قالها بنفسه..
ALLDAY PROJECT is...
مشروع ALLDAY هو...
- the most popular band in Korea. - Absolutely.
- الفرقة الأكثر شعبية في كوريا. - قطعاً.
- They're on top. - Right? They're on top.
- إنهم في الأعلى. - يمين؟ إنهم في الأعلى.
Didn't you guys want to meet us?
ألا تريدون أن تقابلونا يا رفاق؟
I wanted to meet you all very much.
أردت أن ألتقي بكم جميعا كثيرا.
Honestly, I wanted so much...
بصراحة كنت أريد الكثير..
to meet especially Ho Dong and Jang Hoon.
للقاء بشكل خاص هو دونغ وجانغ هون.
I've seen Jang Hoon on the street.
لقد رأيت جانغ هون في الشارع.
- Oh, my. Really? - I thought that could be the case.
- يا بلدي. حقًا؟ - اعتقدت أن هذا قد يكون هو الحال.
- Do you walk on the streets? - He rarely walks on the streets.
- هل تمشي في الشوارع؟ - نادرا ما يمشي في الشوارع.
I guess they lived in the same neighborhood.
أعتقد أنهم كانوا يعيشون في نفس الحي.
- Where did you see me? - Wait. Hold on.
- أين رأيتني؟ - انتظر. يتمسك.
I saw you on the street when I was in middle school.
لقد رأيتك في الشارع عندما كنت في المدرسة المتوسطة.
- When you were in middle school? - You were in middle school?
- عندما كنت في المدرسة المتوسطة؟ - كنت في المدرسة المتوسطة؟
- In what neighborhood? - Tell them.
- في أي حي؟ - أخبرهم.
- Where did you see him? - Where was he walking around?
- أين رأيته؟ - أين كان يتجول؟
- In front of O restaurant? - I saw him in Nonhyeon-dong.
- أمام مطعم O؟ - رأيته في نونهيون دونغ.
In Nonhyeon-dong?
في نونهيون دونغ؟
- My parents' house was there. - A building you own is there?
- كان منزل والدي هناك. - مبنى تملكه هناك؟
- Oh, I see. - Oh, his parents lived there.
- أوه، فهمت. - أوه، والديه عاشوا هناك.
My friend who was with me said she had spotted a TV celebrity.
قالت صديقتي التي كانت معي إنها شاهدت أحد مشاهير التلفاز.
I wondered who it was, and it turned out to be Jang Hoon.
تساءلت من هو، وتبين أنه جانغ هون.
Was he on variety shows back then?
هل كان في برامج متنوعة في ذلك الوقت؟
I can tell how much younger ANNIE is than we are.
أستطيع أن أعرف كم عمر آني أصغر منا.
When we were younger, we knew Jang Hoon...
عندما كنا أصغر سناً، كنا نعرف جانغ هون...
- as a basketball player. - That's right.
- كلاعب كرة سلة. - هذا صحيح.
But she knew him as a TV celebrity.
لكنها عرفته كأحد مشاهير التلفاز.
So he had started to star on variety shows.
لذلك بدأ بالتمثيل في البرامج المتنوعة.
I also wanted to meet Hee Chul and Shin Dong.
أردت أيضًا مقابلة هي تشول وشين دونغ.
- Why? - Your group and we...
- لماذا؟ - مجموعتك ونحن...
- worked in the same period. - That's right.
- عمل في نفس الفترة . - هذا صحيح.
- We worked in the same period? - We...
- عملنا في نفس الفترة؟ - نحن...
- liked you guys so much. - We were very busy.
- أحببتكم كثيرًا يا رفاق. - كنا مشغولين للغاية.
This right here is a 100 percent certified slapper
هذا هنا هو الطارق المعتمد بنسبة 100 بالمئة
Her pronunciation is so different from ours.
نطقها مختلف تمامًا عن نطقنا.
(The intro of "Express Mode" performed by Si Won)
(مقدمة "الوضع السريع" يؤديها سي وون)
- She pronounced it so fluently. - It sounded so fluent.
- لقد نطقتها بطلاقة. - وبدا بطلاقة جدا.
- I didn't know it was our song. - BAILEY loves the song.
- لم أكن أعلم أنها أغنيتنا. - بيلي يحب الأغنية.
- I love the song. - Really?
- أنا أحب الأغنية. - حقًا؟
- BAILEY, sing it. - This is a 100 percent certified
- بيلي، غنيها. - هذه شهادة 100 بالمئة
- Slapper - Slapper
- الاسترخاء - الاسترخاء
- Her pronunciation... - What song did she just sing?
- نطقها... - ما هي الأغنية التي غنتها للتو؟
- Is it really our song? - That is...
- هل هي حقا أغنيتنا؟ - إنه...
Shin Dong, you must be able to sing it. Sing it for us.
شين دونغ، يجب أن تكون قادرًا على غنائها. غنيها لنا.
- Shin Dong, you're a singer. - You must know the part.
- شين دونغ، أنت مغني. - يجب أن تعرف الجزء.
I don't know that part.
أنا لا أعرف هذا الجزء.
Shin Dong...
شين دونغ...
Shin Dong can't seem to memorize...
يبدو أن شين دونغ لا يستطيع الحفظ...
- the other members' parts. - I don't know that part.
- أجزاء الأعضاء الآخرين. - أنا لا أعرف هذا الجزء.
(The professional idol group divides the song parts thoroughly.)
(تقوم مجموعة الآيدولز المحترفة بتقسيم أجزاء الأغنية بدقة.)
- He knows only his parts? - Yes. I don't know his part.
- لا يعرف إلا أجزائه؟ - نعم. أنا لا أعرف دوره.
- Oh, really? - Thank you anyway.
- أوه حقًا؟ - شكرا لك على أية حال.
Your pronunciation is so good.
نطقك جيد جدا.
- What song was it? - We like your song so much...
- ما هي الأغنية؟ - نحن نحب أغنيتك كثيرا ...
that I would dance BAILEY's shooting dance,
أنني سأرقص رقصة بيلي في الرماية،
and then Shin Dong would fall down just as TARZZAN does.
وبعد ذلك سوف يسقط شين دونغ تمامًا كما يفعل طرزان.
- He has a great fall technique. - Shin Dong does that?
- لديه تقنية سقوط رائعة . - شين دونغ هل يفعل ذلك؟
I really like this dance move.
أنا حقا أحب هذه الخطوة الرقص.
You change your dance moves every time.
يمكنك تغيير حركات الرقص الخاصة بك في كل مرة.
(The shooting move that's split up into beats is so satisfying.)
(حركة التصوير المقسمة إلى إيقاعات مرضية للغاية.)
There's something I'm so curious about.
هناك شيء أشعر بالفضول تجاهه.
Jang Hoon, can you stand up just once for me?
جانغ هون، هل يمكنك الوقوف من أجلي مرة واحدة فقط؟
Can you stand up just once for me?
هل يمكنك الوقوف مرة واحدة فقط بالنسبة لي؟
- Of course. - She must want to see.
- بالطبع. - لابد أنها تريد أن ترى.
- I'm so curious about his height. - That's everyone's dream.
- أنا غريبة جدا عن طوله. - هذا حلم الجميع.
- Please show me just once. - Jang Hoon is so tall...
- من فضلك أرني مرة واحدة فقط. -جانغ هون طويل جدًا..
- I can't tell as you're seated. - I'm sorry, but...
- لا أستطيع أن أقول وأنت جالس. - أنا آسف، ولكن...
- YOUNGSEO, come here. - You should see him up close.
- يونجسيو، تعال إلى هنا. - يجب أن تراه عن قرب.
Let's all go and stand next to him.
فلنذهب جميعا ونقف بجانبه
- Come here. - All together?
- تعال الى هنا. - كل ذلك معا؟
- Go alone. Why should I join you? - YOUNGSEO, you should come alone.
- اذهب وحدك. لماذا يجب أن أنضم إليكم؟ - يونغسيو، يجب أن تأتي وحدك.
- YOUNGSEO, come alone. - Why should I go with you?
- يونغسيو، تعال وحدك. - لماذا يجب أن أذهب معك؟
- Go ahead. - Don't worry. He doesn't bite.
- تفضل. - لا تقلق. انه لا يعض.
- YOUNGSEO, you should go alone. - He doesn't bite.
- يونغسيو، يجب أن تذهب وحدك. - لا يعض.
- Come here. - Can you all come with us?
- تعال الى هنا. - هل يمكنكم جميعا أن تأتي معنا؟
(Standing up)
(واقفاً)
(Impressed)
(معجب)
- Come here. - He might step forward.
- تعال الى هنا. - قد يتقدم إلى الأمام.
- He's so tall. - I don't want to stand next to him.
- انه طويل القامة جدا. - لا أريد أن أقف بجانبه.
I shouldn't stand next to him.
لا ينبغي لي أن أقف بجانبه.
It's the only special talent he has.
إنها الموهبة الخاصة الوحيدة التي يمتلكها.
- It's his only special talent. - It's a special talent.
- إنها موهبته الخاصة الوحيدة. - إنها موهبة خاصة.
(He kindly showed his special talent to the young girls.)
(لقد أظهر موهبته الخاصة للفتيات الصغيرات بلطف).
- I'm jealous of his special talent. - It's a special talent...
- أنا غيور من موهبته الخاصة. - إنها موهبة خاصة..
- They seem excited. - They must be.
- يبدو أنهم متحمسون. - يجب أن يكونوا كذلك.
(The 2-meter Jang Hoon experience was satisfying?)
(كانت تجربة جانغ هون التي يبلغ طولها مترين مرضية؟)
(Daddy Long Legs is sweet toward the girls.)
(الأب ذو الساقين الطويلة لطيف تجاه الفتيات.)
- Right. - That's nice of him.
- يمين. - هذا لطيف منه.
- Indeed. - That was nice.
- بالفعل. - كان ذلك لطيفا.
Why were you excited to wear school uniforms?
لماذا كنت متحمسة لارتداء الزي المدرسي؟
We've never worn matching clothes before.
لم نرتدي ملابس متطابقة من قبل.
- That's right. - Also, some of the members here...
- هذا صحيح. -وأيضاً بعض الأعضاء هنا...
- went to school overseas. - I see.
- ذهب إلى المدرسة في الخارج. - أرى.
It's their first time wearing a school uniform.
إنها المرة الأولى التي يرتدون فيها الزي المدرسي.
- They never wore school uniforms? - Oh, really?
- لم يرتدوا الزي المدرسي أبدا؟ - أوه حقًا؟
Which members have never worn a school uniform?
من هم الأعضاء الذين لم يرتدوا الزي المدرسي من قبل؟
- These two have never worn one. - Oh, I see.
- هذان الاثنان لم يرتديا واحدة قط. - أوه، فهمت.
- So... - There are such expensive schools.
- إذن... - هناك مثل هذه المدارس باهظة الثمن.
I always dreamed of wearing a school uniform.
كنت أحلم دائمًا بارتداء الزي المدرسي.
- Really? - Unexpectedly...
- حقًا؟ - بشكل غير متوقع...
TARZZAN, you wore a school uniform, right?
طرزان، كنت ترتدي الزي المدرسي، أليس كذلك؟
- I wore a school uniform... - He's from Ulsan, so...
- ارتديت الزي المدرسي... - إنه من أولسان، لذا...
throughout my school years.
طوال سنوات دراستي.
- I wore it my entire school years. - Based on...
- ارتديته طوال سنوات دراستي. - بناء على...
Based on appearances, you seem like you've never worn it.
بناءً على المظهر، يبدو أنك لم ترتديه أبدًا.
Exactly. I thought he had gone to school overseas.
بالضبط. اعتقدت أنه ذهب إلى المدرسة في الخارج.
TARZZAN looks like he studied overseas.
طرزان يبدو وكأنه درس في الخارج.
You're the one who wore a uniform throughout your school years.
أنت الذي ارتديت الزي الرسمي طوال سنوات الدراسة.
Yes, and that's why I used to wear my school uniform...
نعم، ولهذا السبب كنت أرتدي الزي المدرسي...
- in my own style. - Oh, I see.
- بأسلوبي الخاص. - أوه، فهمت.
- Tell us. He has long legs. - First, I wear suede boots.
- أخبرنا. لديه أرجل طويلة. - أولاً، أرتدي حذاءً من جلد الغزال.
Since I went to an arts high school,
منذ أن ذهبت إلى مدرسة ثانوية للفنون،
it was mandatory to wear flat shoes.
كان إلزاميا ارتداء الأحذية المسطحة.
We used to call those "Aladdin boots."
لقد اعتدنا أن نطلق على تلك الأحذية "أحذية علاء الدين".
They're similar to Aladdin boots,
إنها تشبه أحذية علاء الدين،
- but they're slightly different. - Right.
- لكنهم مختلفون قليلا. - يمين.
I wore these to make myself look cool.
ارتديت هذه لأجعل نفسي أبدو رائعًا.
It wasn't allowed to narrow the pants legs.
لم يكن مسموحًا بتضييق أرجل البنطال.
It shouldn't go up above the knees.
ولا ينبغي أن يرتفع فوق الركبتين.
But it looks cool when it's slim-fit.
لكنها تبدو رائعة عندما تكون ذات مقاس نحيف.
- It's considered cool in the area. - The leg opening is about 20cm.
- يعتبر باردا في المنطقة. - فتحة الساق حوالي 20 سم.
But your pants... Your legs seem...
لكن سروالك... يبدو أن ساقيك...
Even Ho Dong's arms wouldn't fit in them.
حتى ذراعي هو دونغ لن تناسبهما.
(TARZZAN's trousers seem too tight for Ho Dong's forearms.)
(يبدو بنطال طرزان ضيقًا جدًا بالنسبة لساعدي هو دونغ.)
By the way, Tarzan lives in the wilderness.
بالمناسبة، طرزان يعيش في البرية.
So don't you think you're wearing too much jewelry?
إذن، ألا تعتقدين أنك ترتدي الكثير من المجوهرات؟
But I like jewelry, so I always wear...
لكني أحب المجوهرات، لذا أرتدي دائماً...
- a lot of accessories. - He likes accessories.
- الكثير من الملحقات. - يحب الأكسسوارات .
- He's wearing the most accessories. - That's a lot, indeed.
- إنه يرتدي معظم الملحقات. - هذا كثير بالفعل.
- He looks flashiest of all. - He does, indeed.
- يبدو أكثر بهرجة من الجميع. - إنه كذلك بالفعل.
He has the flashiest nail style too.
لديه أسلوب الأظافر الأكثر بهرجة أيضًا.
(The flashy nail style suits TARZZAN perfectly as well.)
(أسلوب الأظافر المبهرج يناسب TARZZAN تمامًا أيضًا.)
TARZZAN, do you smile with your eyes like that intentionally?
طرزان، هل تبتسم بعينيك هكذا عمداً؟
- What did you say? "Smise?" - Sorry?
- ماذا قلت؟ "سميز؟" - آسف؟
- Smiling with your eyes. - Oh, no, I don't.
- ابتسم بعينيك . - أوه، لا، لا أفعل.
- I did this even when I was little. - Even he couldn't understand that.
- فعلت هذا حتى عندما كنت صغيرا. - حتى هو لم يستطع فهم ذلك.
- He's from Ulsan, but he couldn't. - Hey.
- إنه من أولسان، لكنه لم يستطع. - يا.
Ho Dong must not be from Gyeongsang Province.
يجب ألا يكون Ho Dong من مقاطعة جيونج سانج.
You should speak to him in English.
يجب أن تتحدث معه باللغة الإنجليزية.
He couldn't understand what you said when he's from Ulsan.
لم يستطع فهم ما قلته عندما كان من أولسان.
TARZZAN, you smile with your eyes, which looks amazing.
طرزان، تبتسمين بعينيك، وهذا يبدو رائعًا.
- Is it awesome? - Yes, it's awesome.
- هل هو رائع؟ - نعم، إنه رائع.
- He's incredible. - I agree.
- إنه أمر لا يصدق. - أنا موافق.
I'm sorry to say this, TARZZAN,
أنا آسف لقول هذا، طرزان،
but you look as if you'd never been to Korea before.
لكنك تبدو كما لو أنك لم تزر كوريا من قبل.
He looks like he grew up in a foreign country.
يبدو أنه نشأ في بلد أجنبي.
- He looks like a hair stylist... - Right.
- يبدو وكأنه مصفف شعر... - صحيح.
from South America.
من أمريكا الجنوبية.
That's why these things happen.
ولهذا السبب تحدث هذه الأشياء.
Whenever I go on a trip...
كلما ذهبت في رحلة...
- and check into a hotel, - That's so funny.
- وأدخل إلى فندق - هذا مضحك جداً.
the receptionist thinks I'm a foreigner...
موظف الاستقبال يعتقد أنني أجنبي.
- and speaks to me in English. - Right.
- ويتحدث معي باللغة الإنجليزية. - يمين.
Then I would say I'm Korean speaking in dialect,
ثم أود أن أقول أنني كوري أتحدث باللهجة،
- and he or she understands. - "The thing is..."
- وهو يفهم. - "الأمر هو..."
- TARZZAN has unexpected charms. - Right.
- تتمتع طرزان بسحر غير متوقع. - يمين.
- He speaks in a dialect, but he... - He's easygoing.
- يتحدث بلهجة، لكنه... - إنه بسيط.
- I heard that one of you... - Did you...
- سمعت أن أحدكم... - هل...
had been inspired by a cast member's song...
كانت مستوحاة من أغنية أحد أعضاء فريق التمثيل ...
- and decided to pursue music. - Really?
- وقرر متابعة الموسيقى. - حقًا؟
They're a mixed-gender group, so...
إنهم مجموعة مختلطة بين الجنسين، لذا...
- Isn't it Super Junior? - Super Junior's song?
- أليس سوبر جونيور؟ - أغنية سوبر جونيور؟
- There's Buzz too. - Could it be...
- هناك ضجيج أيضا. - هل يمكن أن يكون...
- It could be Kyung Hoon. - Could it be Roo'Ra?
- يمكن أن يكون كيونغ هون. - هل يمكن أن تكون رورع؟
- They're a mixed-gender group too. - Oh, Roo'Ra.
- إنهم مجموعة مختلطة بين الجنسين أيضًا. - أوه، رورع.
- They're too young to know them. - Oh, they're a mixed-gender group.
- إنهم أصغر من أن يعرفوهم. - أوه، إنهم مجموعة مختلطة بين الجنسين.
- Let me explain. - Who is it?
- اسمحوا لي أن أشرح. - من هذا؟
When I was a little boy, my mom wanted me to listen to music,
عندما كنت طفلاً صغيراً، أرادت أمي أن أستمع إلى الموسيقى،
so she bought me a lot of cassette tapes.
لذلك اشترت لي الكثير من أشرطة الكاسيت.
- So I could hear it while studying. - Even when you were little?
- لذلك كنت أسمع ذلك أثناء الدراسة. - حتى عندما كنت صغيرا؟
And one of those cassette tapes was Ho Dong's Christmas album.
وكان أحد أشرطة الكاسيت تلك هو ألبوم عيد الميلاد لـ Ho Dong.
- He sang "Feliz Navidad" and... - You guys don't know that, right?
- لقد غنى "فيليز نافيداد" و... - أنتم لا تعرفون ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
- You heard my Christmas album? - None of them must know.
- هل سمعت ألبوم عيد الميلاد الخاص بي؟ - لا ينبغي لأحد منهم أن يعرف.
- Did he debut as a singer too? - What songs did he sing?
- هل ظهر لأول مرة كمغني أيضًا؟ - ما الأغاني التي غناها؟
- I released a Christmas album.
- ما الأغاني التي غناها؟ - لقد أصدرت ألبوم عيد الميلاد.
I listened to that album even in summer.
لقد استمعت إلى هذا الألبوم حتى في الصيف.
I listened to the cassette tape every day.
كنت أستمع إلى شريط الكاسيت كل يوم.
- I listened to it all the time. - Did he make a music video too?
- لقد استمعت إليها طوال الوقت. - هل صنع فيديو موسيقي أيضاً؟
- This is his pose in the thumbnail. - Did you debut as a singer?
- وهذا هو وضعه في الصورة المصغرة. - هل ظهرت لأول مرة كمغنية؟
- Did you release a music video too? - He released a song album.
- هل قمت بإصدار فيديو موسيقي أيضًا؟ - أصدر ألبومًا غنائيًا.
- Did he say "thumbnail?" - Really?
- هل قال "صورة مصغرة؟" - حقًا؟
- What's that? - That's Ho Dong's music video.
- ما هذا؟ - هذا هو الفيديو الموسيقي لـ Ho Dong.
- Chae Yeon - Why?
- تشاي يون - لماذا؟
Shall we go outside for a sled ride?
هل يجب أن نذهب للخارج لركوب الزلاجة؟
(The lyrics say, "You will break the sled.")
(تقول الكلمات: "سوف تكسر الزلاجة".)
- You go first - My goodness.
- اذهب أنت أولاً - يا إلهي.
My, I look so cute.
يا إلهي، أنا أبدو لطيفًا جدًا.
Isn't that Ji Sang Yeol?
أليس هذا جي سانغ يول؟
Oh, my. That's Yu Jae Seok.
يا بلدي. هذا يو جاي سيوك.
(The rare Christmas song music video that features so many top stars)
(الفيديو الموسيقي النادر لأغنية عيد الميلاد والذي يضم العديد من كبار النجوم)
Many entertainers released a Christmas album back in the day.
أصدر العديد من الفنانين ألبومًا لعيد الميلاد في ذلك اليوم.
(Ho Dong's Christmas song inspired TARZZAN to become a singer?)
(أغنية عيد الميلاد التي كتبها هو دونغ ألهمت طرزان ليصبح مغنيًا؟)
- That's... - Many entertainers did.
- هذا... - العديد من الفنانين فعلوا ذلك.
- So he's our senior singer. - It was common back then.
- إذن فهو مغنينا الكبير. - كان شائعا في ذلك الوقت.
- I mean... - Well, I think it's time...
- أعني... - حسنًا، أعتقد أن الوقت قد حان...
Such stories are not important.
مثل هذه القصص ليست مهمة.
- That's not important. - That's...
- هذا ليس مهما. - هذا...
- What matters is the transfer form. - That's right.
- ما يهم هو استمارة النقل. - هذا صحيح.
Bring me your transfer form so that we can officially begin.
أحضر لي نموذج النقل الخاص بك حتى نتمكن من البدء رسميًا.
- Does WOOCHAN have it? - I'll come to you, Soo Geun.
- هل يمتلكها ووشان؟ - سآتي إليك، سو جيون.
- All right. That's nice. - Okay.
- حسنًا. هذا جميل. - تمام.
- We've met before. - What?
- لقد التقينا من قبل. - ماذا؟
- We've met before? - They've met before?
- لقد التقينا من قبل؟ - لقد التقيا من قبل؟
- Soo Geun doesn't remember it. - He doesn't remember it.
- سو جيون لا يتذكر ذلك. - لا يتذكر ذلك.
He doesn't remember it?
انه لا يتذكر ذلك؟
- I'm sorry, but I've never met you. - But...
- أنا آسف، ولكنني لم أقابلك قط. - لكن...
- I don't think I've met you... - Was it when you were little?
- لا أعتقد أنني التقيت بك... - هل كان ذلك عندما كنت صغيراً؟
- Let's get back to that later on. - He must be Tae Joon's friend.
- دعونا نعود إلى ذلك لاحقا. - يجب أن يكون صديق تاي جون.
Really? Don't be like this.
حقًا؟ لا تكن هكذا.
- It's okay. - Where did I meet you?
- لا بأس. - أين التقيت بك؟
- It's okay. Try to remember it. - You...
- لا بأس. حاول أن تتذكرها. - أنت...
I'm sorry, but do you play billiards?
أنا آسف، لكن هل تلعب البلياردو؟
- I don't play billiards. - Did I meet him at a billiard hall?
- أنا لا ألعب البلياردو. - هل التقيت به في قاعة البلياردو؟
- Sit down and tell us. - I think it's a bad memory.
- اجلس وأخبرنا. - أعتقد أنها ذكرى سيئة.
The transfer form to Men on a Mission.
استمارة التحويل إلى رجال في مهمة.
ANNIE, TARZZAN, BAILEY, WOOCHAN, and YOUNGSEO.
آني، طرزان، بيلي، ووشان، ويونغسيو.
- Okay. Welcome! - Yes!
- تمام. مرحباً! - نعم!
- Welcome! - It must be their first time here.
- مرحباً! - يجب أن تكون المرة الأولى لهم هنا.
But the names I just said were their stage names.
لكن الأسماء التي قلتها للتو كانت أسماءهم الفنية.
Now I'll tell you their real names.
الآن سأخبرك بأسمائهم الحقيقية.
- They must not be their real names. - I'll tell you their real names.
- يجب ألا تكون أسمائهم الحقيقية. - سأخبرك بأسمائهم الحقيقية.
- ANNIE's real name is... - ANNIE?
- اسم آني الحقيقي هو... - آني؟
- Moon Seo Yoon. - Seo Yoon?
- مون سيو يون. - سيو يون؟
- Seo Yoon, yes.
- سيو يون؟ - سيو يون، نعم.
- Did you go by ANNIE in the US? - No.
- هل ذهبت عن طريق آني في الولايات المتحدة؟ - لا.
ANNIE is the name I went by at my English kindergarten.
ANNIE هو الاسم الذي كنت أستخدمه في روضة الأطفال الإنجليزية.
- Were you given the name then? - When I was little,
- هل أعطيت الاسم بعد ذلك؟ - عندما كنت صغيراً،
there were no English kindergartens.
لم تكن هناك رياض أطفال إنجليزية.
I asked Director William...
سألت المدير ويليام...
to pick an English name for me.
لاختيار اسم الانجليزية بالنسبة لي.
The director said "ANNIE" would suit me.
قال المخرج أن "آني" سوف تناسبني.
(Director William gave her the English name "ANNIE.")
(أعطاها المخرج ويليام الاسم الإنجليزي "ANNIE".)
I was called "ANNIE" when I was in the US,
لقد كان يُدعى "آني" عندما كنت في الولايات المتحدة،
and only my English-speaking friends called me that.
وأصدقائي الناطقون باللغة الإنجليزية فقط هم من اتصلوا بي بهذا الاسم.
But since I made my debut as ANNIE,
لكن منذ أن ظهرت لأول مرة بشخصية "آني"،
- I've been called that at home too. - "ANNIE?"
- لقد تم استدعائي ذلك في المنزل أيضًا. - "آني؟"
Even my parents call me "ANNIE."
حتى والدي ينادونني "آني".
- My fans call me Big Sis ANNIE. - Big Sis ANNIE?
- معجبيني ينادونني بالأخت الكبرى آني. - الأخت الكبرى آني؟
Big Sis ANNIE.
الأخت الكبرى آني.
- And when I'm home... - "Big Sis ANNIE."
- وعندما أكون في المنزل... - "الأخت الكبرى آني".
My mom calls herself...
أمي تسمي نفسها...
- AM as in ANNIE's mom. - "ANNIE's mom?"
- أنا كما في والدة آني. - "والدة آني؟"
- She gave herself a nickname. - So everyone calls you ANNIE now.
- أعطت لنفسها لقبا. - لذلك الجميع يدعوك آني الآن.
- Who's next? - TARZZAN's real name is...
- من التالي؟ - اسم طرزان الحقيقي هو...
- I'm curious. - His real name has...
- أنا فضولي. - اسمه الحقيقي...
such different vibes.
مثل هذه المشاعر المختلفة.
- Promise you won't laugh. - It has the opposite vibe?
- وعد أنك لن تضحك. - لديها فيبي المعاكس؟
- Do you think we can guess it? - You want to guess his real name?
- هل تعتقد أننا نستطيع تخمين ذلك؟ - هل تريد تخمين اسمه الحقيقي؟
I've never called TARZZAN by his real name.
لم أنادي طرزان باسمه الحقيقي مطلقًا.
- Not even once? - Almost never.
- ولا مرة واحدة؟ - أبدا تقريبا.
- You do know his real name, right? - I just can't call him that.
- أنت تعرف اسمه الحقيقي، أليس كذلك؟ - لا أستطيع أن أسميه ذلك.
- Right. His real name... - I can't seem to do so either.
- يمين. اسمه الحقيقي... - لا يبدو أنني أفعل ذلك أيضًا.
- doesn't suit him. - His name doesn't sound like him.
- لا يناسبه. - اسمه لا يبدو مثله.
- It's Lee Chae Won. - What?
- أنا لي تشاي وون. - ماذا؟
- Lee Chae Won? - Chae Won.
- لي تشاي وون؟ - تشاي وون.
- It sounds like BAILEY's real name. - Lee Chae Won?
- يبدو وكأنه اسم بيلي الحقيقي. - لي تشاي وون؟
BAILEY's real name is Chae Won, right?
اسم بيلي الحقيقي هو تشاي وون، أليس كذلك؟
I guess your parents thought you were a girl when you were born.
أعتقد أن والديك اعتقدا أنك فتاة عندما ولدت.
- Because he had long hair? - Right?
- لأنه كان لديه شعر طويل؟ - يمين؟
- Yes. People would say, - Right?
- نعم. سيقول الناس، - أليس كذلك؟
"We got the wrong name on the list?"
"هل حصلنا على الاسم الخطأ في القائمة؟"
- "It's a girl's name." - Right.
- "إنه اسم فتاة." - يمين.
- Chae Won? - It happened a lot.
- تشاي وون؟ - لقد حدث الكثير.
How many siblings do you have?
كم عدد الأخوة لديك؟
Sorry?
آسف؟
- He can't understand what he says. - He's not from Gyeongsang Province.
- لا يستطيع أن يفهم ما يقول. - إنه ليس من مقاطعة جيونج سانج.
- Tuck your hair behind your ear! - Sorry?
- دس شعرك خلف أذنك! - آسف؟
Open your ears.
افتح أذنيك.
If he can't communicate with a person...
إذا لم يتمكن من التواصل مع أي شخص...
- from Gyeongsang Province... - He can't communicate with him.
- من مقاطعة كيونغسانغ... - لا يستطيع التواصل معه.
Then whom could I communicate with?
ثم من الذي يمكنني التواصل معه؟
- Whom could he communicate with? - He's not from Gyeongsang Province.
- مع من يمكنه التواصل؟ - إنه ليس من مقاطعة جيونج سانج.
- Who gave you the name TARZZAN? - The name Chae Won...
- من أعطاك اسم طرزان؟ - اسم تشاي وون...
As for the name TARZZAN...
أما اسم طرزان...
- I majored in contemporary dance. - That's right. He majored in dance.
- تخصصت في الرقص المعاصر. - هذا صحيح. تخصص في الرقص.
I gave a performance when I was in the 12th grade.
لقد قدمت عرضًا عندما كنت في الصف الثاني عشر.
And I wore shorts in the same color as my skin color.
وارتديت شورتاً بنفس لون بشرتي.
People saw me dancing in those pants without anything else...
لقد رآني الناس أرقص بهذا البنطلون دون أي شيء آخر...
(His stage outfit seemed like part of his body.)
(بدا زيه المسرحي وكأنه جزء من جسده).
- "Is that brat Tarzan or what?" - "That brat?"
- "هل هذا الشقي طرزان أم ماذا؟" - "هذا الشقي؟"
- "That brat looks like Tarzan." - "That brat."
- "هذا الشقي يشبه طرزان." - "هذا الشقي."
- He grew up in Gyeongsang Province.
- نشأ في مقاطعة كيونغسانغ. - "هذا الشقي."
He sure grew up there.
من المؤكد أنه نشأ هناك.
One day,
يوم واحد،
I was trying to come up with an ID for my Instagram account.
كنت أحاول الحصول على معرف لحساب Instagram الخاص بي.
I happened to pick the name TARZZAN,
لقد صادف أنني اخترت اسم طرزان،
and people have been calling me as TARZZAN ever since.
وكان الناس ينادونني باسم طرزان منذ ذلك الحين.
- The name TARZZAN suits him. - The name suits him.
- اسم طرزان يناسبه. - الاسم يناسبه.
- It suits you. - It suits you really well.
- إنه يناسبك. - إنه يناسبك جيدًا.
- And he has long hair. - Exactly.
- وله شعر طويل. - بالضبط.
- He picked the right name. - Next up is BAILEY.
- اختار الاسم الصحيح. - التالي هو بيلي.
- BAILEY. - BAILEY's real name is...
- بيلي. - اسم بيلي الحقيقي هو...
It sounds like the name of an apartment complex.
يبدو وكأنه اسم مجمع سكني.
- Bailey Deuryu Seok? - Like the one in Banpo.
- بيلي ديوريو سوك؟ - مثل الذي في بانبو.
- Bailey Drew Sok. - Bailey Drewsa?
- بيلي درو سوك. - بيلي دروزا؟
- Oh, BAILEY is her real name? - Oh, "Drew?"
- أوه، بيلي هو اسمها الحقيقي؟ - أوه، "درو؟"
- "Sok" is my family name. - Oh, I see.
- "سوك" هو اسم عائلتي. - أوه، فهمت.
- And "Drew" is my middle name.
- و"درو" هو اسمي الأوسط. - أوه، فهمت.
- Where were you born? - In California, the US.
- أين ولدت؟ - في كاليفورنيا بالولايات المتحدة.
- Welcome to the Hotel California - California, man.
- مرحبًا بك في فندق كاليفورنيا، كاليفورنيا يا رجل.
(BAILEY was born and raised in California, the US.)
(وُلدت بيلي ونشأت في كاليفورنيا بالولايات المتحدة).
- Are you from California? - Yes.
- هل أنت من كاليفورنيا؟ - نعم.
Why? Do you know much about California?
لماذا؟ هل تعرف الكثير عن كاليفورنيا؟
Ho Dong, I asked you if you knew much about California.
هو دونغ، سألتك إذا كنت تعرف الكثير عن كاليفورنيا.
It's famous for almonds.
وتشتهر باللوز.
- Is it famous for almonds? - Almonds from California.
- هل تشتهر باللوز؟ - اللوز من كاليفورنيا.
- It's famous for corn chips too. - I didn't know that.
- وتشتهر برقائق الذرة أيضًا. - لم أكن أعرف ذلك.
- It's famous for almonds. - Almonds...
- مشهور باللوز . - اللوز...
Hotel California
فندق كاليفورنيا
- Isn't it from that song? - That's right.
- أليس من تلك الأغنية؟ - هذا صحيح.
(California will be remembered by its specialty and the old song.)
(سوف نتذكر كاليفورنيا بتخصصها والأغنية القديمة.)
- Hold on a second.
- هذا صحيح. - انتظر ثانية.
- That's right. - Where in California?
- هذا صحيح. - أين في كاليفورنيا؟
- Orange County. - What did you say?
- مقاطعة أورانج. - ماذا قلت؟
- Wonju?
- مقاطعة أورانج. - ونجو؟
- Orange County.
- مقاطعة أورانج. - مقاطعة أورانج.
Repeat after me. "Orange County."
كرر بعدي. "مقاطعة أورانج."
- Try it. - In Korea...
- جربه. - في كوريا...
- What's wrong with you? - "Orange County."
- ما مشكلتك؟ - "مقاطعة أورانج".
- What? Say that again. Sorry. - "County."
- ماذا؟ قل ذلك مرة أخرى. آسف. - "المقاطعة."
Orange... Say it again. Where did you say you were from?
برتقالي... قلها مرة أخرى. من أين قلت أنك من؟
Orange County.
مقاطعة أورانج.
- Orange County. - She grew up in Orange County.
- مقاطعة أورانج. - نشأت في مقاطعة أورانج.
- She sounds like a native speaker. - Orange County.
- إنها تبدو وكأنها متحدث أصلي. - مقاطعة أورانج.
- She's fluent in English. - "Orange County."
- إنها تتقن اللغة الإنجليزية. - "مقاطعة أورانج".
- How about WOOCHAN? - As for WOOCHAN,
- ماذا عن ووشان؟ - أما بالنسبة لووتشان،
it's his real name. His full name is Jo Woo Chan.
إنه اسمه الحقيقي. اسمه الكامل هو جو وو تشان.
- Everyone knows it. - That's his full name.
- الجميع يعرف ذلك. - وهذا هو اسمه الكامل.
WOOCHAN, what's the meaning of your first name in Chinese?
ووشان، ما معنى اسمك الأول باللغة الصينية؟
- "Chan" as in "to shine." - I see.
- "تشان" كما في "للتألق". - أرى.
- "Woo" as in "sunrise."
- "وو" كما في "الشروق". - أرى.
It means to shine brightly like the sun.
يعني أن تشرق مثل الشمس.
To shine brightly? Nice.
للتألق الزاهية؟ لطيف - جيد.
You do shine brightly.
أنت تتألق بشكل مشرق.
That's why I included the word "shine..."
ولهذا السبب أدرجت كلمة "تألق..."
- in the lyrics of "Famous." - Oh, that's the reason?
- في كلمات "مشهور". - اه هذا هو السبب؟
- Is that why you used the word? - That's meaningful.
- هل هذا هو سبب استخدامك للكلمة؟ - وهذا ذو معنى.
- Even the members didn't know that? - Did you know that just now?
- حتى الأعضاء لم يعرفوا ذلك؟ - هل تعلم ذلك الآن؟
The other members know that now thanks to his answer to my question.
يعرف الأعضاء الآخرون ذلك الآن بفضل إجابته على سؤالي.
- I think ANNIE didn't know that. - I thought that...
- أعتقد أن آني لم تكن تعرف ذلك. - اعتقدت ذلك...
- you wanted to use a swear word... - That it had two meanings?
- أردت أن تستخدم كلمة بذيئة... - أن لها معنيين؟
- You thought it had dual meaning? - and picked one with dual meaning.
- هل تعتقد أن لها معنى مزدوج؟ - واختار واحدة ذات معنى مزدوج.
It has a profound meaning.
لها معنى عميق.
- Right. You... - I want you all to look it up.
- يمين. أنت... - أريدكم جميعا أن تبحثوا عنه.
That's what his name means.
وهذا ما يعنيه اسمه.
- Where should we look it up? - Where?
- أين يجب أن ننظر إليه؟ - أين؟
- You have pride in your lyrics. - Have you ever meant it that way?
- لديك الفخر في كلماتك. - هل سبق لك أن قصدت ذلك بهذه الطريقة؟
Why are you guys doing this to me?
لماذا يا رفاق تفعلون هذا بي؟
I didn't say anything.
لم أقل أي شيء.
WOOCHAN, why do you...
ووشان، لماذا أنت...
(Even my root is different, it's green)
(حتى جذوري مختلفة، فهي خضراء)
(I can't hide it because I shine)
(لا أستطيع إخفاء ذلك لأنني أتألق)
(He included the meaning of his name in the lyrics.)
(أدرج معنى اسمه في كلمات الأغاني).
Did you write the lyrics of your rap part?
هل كتبت كلمات جزء الراب الخاص بك؟
- Yes, I wrote them. - I see.
- نعم، لقد كتبت لهم. - أرى.
- We wrote the lyrics for our parts. - That's awesome.
- لقد كتبنا كلمات أجزائنا. - هذا رائع.
- All right. - Next up is YOUNGSEO.
- حسنًا. - التالي هو YOUNGSEO.
- Her name is Lee Young Seo. - Is it her real name?
- اسمها لي يونغ سيو. - هل هذا اسمها الحقيقي؟
- It's Lee Young Seo. - Oh, it's her real name.
- أنا لي يونغ سيو. - أوه، هذا هو اسمها الحقيقي.
Do you have any story regarding your name?
هل لديك أي قصة بخصوص اسمك؟
There's no such story, as far as I know.
ليس هناك مثل هذه القصة، على حد علمي.
- You and WOOCHAN seem upset. - She's unsure about it.
- يبدو أنك وWOOCHAN منزعجين. - إنها غير متأكدة من ذلك.
- When you were little... - We call her Zero.
- عندما كنتِ صغيرة... - كنا نسميها صفر.
- You call her what? - Zero.
- تسميها ماذا؟ - صفر.
- Oh, because of "Young?" - "Young" means "zero."
- أوه، بسبب "الشباب؟" - "الشباب" يعني "صفر".
- Guess who gave her the nickname. - They call me Zero.
- خمن من أعطاها اللقب. - يسمونني صفر.
- Zero... - You must be the one.
- صفر... - يجب أن تكون أنت.
- No, it wasn't me. - Is it a quiz?
- لا، لم يكن أنا. - هل هو اختبار؟
- Why? - Was it TARZZAN?
- لماذا؟ - هل كان طرزان؟
- WOOCHAN gave her the nickname. - Really?
- ووشان أعطاها اللقب. - حقًا؟
- We were awkward around each other. - At first,
- كنا محرجين حول بعضنا البعض. - في البداية،
they were so awkward around each other.
لقد كانوا محرجين للغاية حول بعضهم البعض.
- Before they became friends. - Indeed.
- قبل أن يصبحوا أصدقاء. - بالفعل.
I told YOUNGSEO to move slightly to one side.
لقد طلبت من YOUNGSEO أن يتحرك قليلاً إلى جانب واحد.
Then WOOCHAN suddenly said...
ثم قال ووشان فجأة...
- None of us was close to him then. - I see.
- ولم يكن أحد منا قريباً منه حينها. - أرى.
He suddenly looked in the mirror and said,
فجأة نظر في المرآة وقال:
"YOUNGSEO? Young... Zero?"
"يونغسيو؟ يونغ... صفر؟"
- That's how... - That's right.
- هكذا... - هذا صحيح.
- He pronounced it fluently. "Zero." - "Zero."
- ينطقها بطلاقة. "صفر." - "صفر".
"Zero."
"صفر."
- I have a question. - So that's how...
- لدي سؤال. - هكذا إذن..
- Do you stay in separate houses? - We stay in separate places.
- هل تقيمون في منازل منفصلة؟ - نبقى في أماكن منفصلة.
- The girls stay together. - Based on their hair lengths,
- الفتيات البقاء معا. - على أساس أطوال شعرهم،
- these four stay in one place, - And the guys stay together.
- هؤلاء الأربعة يبقون في مكان واحد - ويبقى الرجال معًا.
and WOOCHAN stays in another.
ويبقى WOOCHAN في مكان آخر.
They must be divided by the length of hair.
يجب أن يتم تقسيمها على طول الشعر.
(WOOCHAN is alone.)
(ووتشان وحده.)
Right. He probably needs the same hair products as theirs.
يمين. ربما يحتاج إلى نفس منتجات الشعر التي يستخدمونها.
If he shares them with WOOCHAN, they would drift apart.
إذا شاركهم مع ووشان، فسوف يبتعدون عن بعضهم البعض.
- When I get my hair done, - That was good.
- عندما أصفف شعري - كان ذلك جيدًا.
I have to get to the salon earlier than he does...
لا بد لي من الوصول إلى الصالون في وقت مبكر قبل أن يفعل ...
- it takes me as long as the girls. - Of course.
- يستغرق مني ما دامت الفتيات. - بالطبع.
- Because I have long hair. - You need to get your hair curled.
- لأن شعري طويل . - أنت بحاجة إلى تجعيد شعرك.
- ALLDAY PROJECT is so amazing... - You guys...
- مشروع ALLDAY مذهل جدًا... - يا رفاق...
- Why? - It drew attention in Mexico.
- لماذا؟ - لفتت الانتباه في المكسيك.
Only three days after their debut,
بعد ثلاثة أيام فقط من ظهورهم لأول مرة،
- they topped the music charts. - That's right.
- تصدروا المخططات الموسيقية. - هذا صحيح.
- And ten days after their debut,
- هذا صحيح. - وبعد عشرة أيام من ترسيمهم،
- they ranked 1st on a music show. - They ranked 1st.
- احتلوا المركز الأول في برنامج موسيقي. - احتلوا المركز الأول.
In two weeks after their debut, they made it...
وبعد أسبوعين من ترسيمهم، نجحوا في ذلك..
- To the Billboard chart. - to the Billboard chart.
- إلى مخطط بيلبورد. - إلى مخطط بيلبورد.
These are great achievements.
هذه إنجازات عظيمة.
Since it's been brought up... As soon as they made their debut,
منذ أن نشأوا… بمجرد ظهورهم لأول مرة،
- That's right. - they set such remarkable records.
- هذا صحيح. - لقد سجلوا مثل هذه الأرقام القياسية الرائعة.
- It's not an easy thing to achieve. - Those are remarkable, indeed.
- ليس بالأمر السهل تحقيقه. - تلك رائعة بالفعل.
It's rare to get energy that brings great success and to place first.
من النادر أن تحصل على الطاقة التي تحقق نجاحًا كبيرًا وتحتل المرتبة الأولى.
It's the best record since Roo'Ra.
إنه أفضل سجل منذ Roo'Ra.
- Is it the best since Roo'Ra? - Yes, it is.
- هل هو الأفضل منذ روعه؟ - نعم إنه كذلك.
Do any of you know Roo'Ra?
هل يعرف أحد منكم روعا؟
- Of course, they know Roo'Ra. - Oh, they know the group.
- بالطبع، يعرفون روعا. - أوه، وهم يعرفون المجموعة.
- Our album sold a million copies... - Of course, they know Roo'Ra.
- ألبومنا باع مليون نسخة... - بالطبع، يعرفون روعا.
in a single week.
في أسبوع واحد.
ALLDAY PROJECT broke that record.
حطم ALLDAY PROJECT هذا الرقم القياسي.
- They achieved it in three days. - That's not important.
- لقد حققوها في ثلاثة أيام. - هذا ليس مهما.
I agree. That's not important.
أنا موافق. هذا ليس مهما.
- We... - May I?
- نحن... - هل لي؟
Yes? Go ahead.
نعم؟ تفضل.
As he's my senior singer from a mixed-gender group,
بما أنه المغني الكبير لدي من مجموعة مختلطة بين الجنسين،
I want to see him, but I can't because of Ho Dong.
أريد رؤيته، لكن لا أستطيع بسبب هو دونغ.
- Can you move aside a little bit? - ANNIE...
- هل يمكنك التحرك جانبا قليلا؟ - آني...
- ANNIE. - Seriously...
- آني. - بجد...
As you keep recording the show with us,
بينما تستمر في تسجيل العرض معنا،
you'll realize that you don't really have to see him.
ستدرك أنه ليس عليك رؤيته حقًا.
You will realize that eventually.
سوف تدرك ذلك في نهاية المطاف.
When you watch this on TV,
عندما تشاهد هذا على شاشة التلفزيون،
you'll see JTBC's logo over Sang Min's face.
سترى شعار JTBC على وجه سانغ مين.
You will realize that...
وسوف تدرك ذلك...
you don't really have to see him.
ليس عليك حقًا رؤيته.
Let's just watch their performance.
دعونا فقط نشاهد أدائهم.
They could become the best group after Roo'Ra,
من الممكن أن يصبحوا أفضل فرقة بعد Roo'Ra،
- Yes. - so let's check them out.
- نعم. - لذلك دعونا التحقق منها.
- Let's do this. - Then...
- دعونا نفعل هذا. - ثم...
We'll be seeing them in person?
هل سنراهم شخصيا؟
- Yes. - Okay.
- نعم. - تمام.
(Ready to set the discipline on their first transfer!)
(على استعداد لضبط الانضباط عند النقل الأول!)
They're good. They're really good.
إنهم جيدون. إنهم جيدون حقًا.
Ho Dong's favorite song.
أغنية هو دونغ المفضلة.
Say what?
يقول ما؟
- We ain't even famous - We ain't even famous
- نحن لسنا مشهورين حتى - نحن لسنا مشهورين حتى
- Here it is! It's that part! - Here it is!
- ها هو! إنه هذا الجزء! - ها هو!
Go, BAILEY!
اذهب، بيلي!
TARZZAN!
طرزان!
(The brothers are in maximum excitement.)
(الإخوة في أقصى قدر من الإثارة.)
Nice.
لطيف - جيد.
(ADP's performance blew everyone away with their spirit.)
(أذهل أداء ADP الجميع بروحهم المعنوية.)
- Hey, Shin Dong is crying. - Are you okay, TARZZAN?
- مهلا، شين دونغ يبكي. - هل أنت بخير، طرزان؟
- It was that amazing. - Are you okay?
- كان ذلك مذهلاً. - هل أنت بخير؟
Such performances make me cry, you know?
مثل هذه العروض تجعلني أبكي، هل تعلم؟
- For real. - You startled me, TARZZAN.
- لريال مدريد. - لقد أذهلتني يا طرزان.
(After seeing TARZZAN's technique,)
(بعد رؤية تقنية طرزان،)
(Senior Dong became emotional.)
(أصبح الكبير دونغ عاطفيًا.)
Can you do what TARZZAN did? No, right?
هل يمكنك أن تفعل ما فعله طرزان؟ لا، أليس كذلك؟
- I can't. - Nice.
- لا أستطبع. - لطيف - جيد.
- Why are you crying? - Because they're so cool.
- لماذا تبكي؟ - لأنهم بارد جدا.
They're really cool.
إنهم رائعون حقًا.
- Hey, Shin Dong is crying. - Are you okay, TARZZAN?
- مهلا، شين دونغ يبكي. - هل أنت بخير، طرزان؟
- It was that amazing. - Are you okay?
- كان ذلك مذهلاً. - هل أنت بخير؟
It was a light jump, but he landed like he was bungee jumping.
لقد كانت قفزة خفيفة، لكنه هبط كما لو كان يقفز بالحبال.
- Right? - That was great.
- يمين؟ - ًكان كبيرا.
- The secret behind that is that... - Yes?
- السر وراء ذلك هو... - نعم؟
if BAILEY doesn't pull it off well,
إذا لم يقم بيلي بالتصرف بشكل جيد،
- I get scared and can't do it. - Of course.
- أشعر بالخوف ولا أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك. - بالطبع.
But I can jump only because BAILEY does it so well.
لكن لا يمكنني القفز إلا لأن بيلي يقوم بذلك بشكل جيد.
- For real. - That was truly incredible.
- لريال مدريد. - كان ذلك لا يصدق حقا.
(After the main dancer BAILEY sets the tone with her solo dance,)
(بعد أن تحدد الراقصة الرئيسية بيلي النغمة برقصتها المنفردة،)
(TARZZAN carries the spirit on and shows perfect teamwork.)
(يحمل طرزان الروح ويظهر العمل الجماعي المثالي.)
These guys...
هؤلاء الرجال...
- are beyond ordinary. - Yes?
- خارجة عن المألوف. - نعم؟
Despite being rookies, they have a pre-debut history.
على الرغم من كونهم مبتدئين، إلا أن لديهم تاريخ ما قبل الترسيم.
People don't usually write it down...
الناس عادة لا يكتبون ذلك...
unless it's something incredible.
إلا إذا كان شيئا لا يصدق.
- How great is everyone? - Starting off with ANNIE,
- كم هو عظيم الجميع؟ - البدء مع آني،
she wrote, "Accepted to Ivy League."
كتبت: "تم قبولها في Ivy League".
- Ivy League? - That's amazing.
- آيفي ليج؟ - هذا مذهل.
Rumor has it that you went because...
هناك شائعات تقول أنك ذهبت بسبب...
of a promise you made to your parents.
من الوعد الذي قطعته على والديك.
It's true. I desperately wanted to become a singer.
هذا صحيح. أردت بشدة أن أصبح مغنية.
But the condition was that...
لكن الشرط كان...
to become one, I had to get accepted to an Ivy League school.
لكي أصبح واحدًا، كان علي أن يتم قبولي في إحدى مدارس Ivy League.
- You had a condition? - It's something like,
- كان لديك شرط؟ - إنه شيء مثل،
"I'll buy you something if you get full marks," when you're a kid.
"سأشتري لك شيئاً إذا حصلت على العلامات الكاملة" عندما تكون طفلاً.
So you went to an Ivy League school and became a singer?
إذن ذهبت إلى مدرسة Ivy League وأصبحت مغنية؟
- That's right. - Goodness.
- هذا صحيح. - الخير.
- You'll never make it. - Which Ivy League school is it?
- لن تتمكني من ذلك أبداً. - ما هي مدرسة Ivy League؟
I'm currently attending Columbia University.
أنا حاليا أدرس في جامعة كولومبيا.
- Are you taking classes? - I took a leave of absence.
- هل تأخذ دروسا؟ - أخذت إجازة.
(ANNIE got into Columbia University to fulfill her long dream.)
(التحقت آني بجامعة كولومبيا لتحقيق حلمها الطويل.)
Why did your parents make such a promise?
لماذا قدم والديك مثل هذا الوعد؟
They didn't expect me to get in.
لم يتوقعوا دخولي.
Her parents didn't want her to become a singer.
لم يكن والداها يريدان لها أن تصبح مغنية.
But you proved them wrong.
ولكنك أثبت لهم أنهم على خطأ.
And they had already made a promise.
وقد قطعوا وعداً بالفعل.
Since she could become one if she got accepted, she made it happen.
وبما أنها يمكن أن تصبح واحدة إذا تم قبولها، فقد حققت ذلك.
- Is that so? - I have a stupid question.
- هل هذا صحيح؟ - لدي سؤال غبي.
How well do you have to study to get accepted?
ما مدى جودة دراستك للحصول على القبول؟
Honestly, here's something that scares me a little.
بصراحة، هناك شيء يخيفني قليلاً.
People think that I'm great at studying.
يعتقد الناس أنني رائع في الدراسة.
Getting into an Ivy League school...
الالتحاق بمدرسة Ivy League ...
- isn't easy. - But the thing is,
- ليس بالأمر السهل. - ولكن الأمر هو،
I have good short-term memory.
لدي ذاكرة جيدة على المدى القصير.
- Cramming? - I'm a pro at cramming exams.
- حشر؟ - أنا محترف في الامتحانات.
That's how I got good marks on exams.
وهكذا حصلت على علامات جيدة في الامتحانات.
- That too is a talent. - It's a talent.
- وهذه أيضا موهبة. - إنها موهبة.
- Having good short-term memory. - Of course.
- التمتع بذاكرة جيدة على المدى القصير. - بالطبع.
Her parents didn't think...
ولم يفكر والداها...
- ANNIE, - she would get in.
- آني، - سوف تدخل.
you must never get the lyrics...
يجب ألا تحصل على الكلمات أبدًا...
or choreography wrong on stage.
أو تصميم الرقصات بشكل خاطئ على المسرح.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I don't think I have yet. Have I?
لا أعتقد أنني فعلت ذلك بعد. هل فعلت؟
We've only just debuted, so it's still short-term.
لقد ترسمنا للتو، لذلك لا يزال الأمر قصير المدى.
- Exactly. - Short-term.
- بالضبط. - قصير المدى.
It's true we're still short-term.
صحيح أننا لا نزال على المدى القصير.
- Short-term from short-term memory. - You'll become long-term.
- قصير المدى من الذاكرة قصيرة المدى. - سوف تصبح على المدى الطويل.
During concerts or performances.
خلال الحفلات الموسيقية أو العروض.
- TARZZAN.
- طرزان. - طرزان.
- Nice one.
- طرزان. - هذا لطيف.
(Falling in love in real time)
(الوقوع في الحب في الوقت الحقيقي)
- Gosh. - You're good.
- يا إلهي. - أنت جيدة أو أنت طيب.
- He's good. - You've only released two songs.
- انه جيد. - لقد أصدرت أغنيتين فقط.
- That was witty. - Yes.
- كان ذلك ذكيا. - نعم.
You've studied abroad...
لقد درست في الخارج...
- since you were young. - Yes.
- منذ كنت صغيرا. - نعم.
- Did you ever miss Korea... - Right.
- هل اشتقت لكوريا من قبل... - صحيح.
or your parents?
أو والديك؟
I've always wanted to attend a Korean school.
لقد أردت دائمًا الالتحاق بمدرسة كورية.
- A Korean school? - So you've never attended one.
- مدرسة كورية؟ - إذن أنت لم تحضر واحدة من قبل.
I moved to the US after attending elementary school...
انتقلت إلى الولايات المتحدة بعد أن التحقت بالمدرسة الابتدائية.
for three years in Korea.
لمدة ثلاث سنوات في كوريا.
(Started studying abroad in the US in 3rd grade)
(بدأت الدراسة بالخارج في الولايات المتحدة في الصف الثالث)
Wearing a Korean school uniform,
يرتدي الزي المدرسي الكوري،
running to the snack bar...
يركض إلى مطعم الوجبات الخفيفة...
like in dramas,
كما هو الحال في الأعمال الدرامية،
and that kind of vibe, you know?
وهذا النوع من الأجواء، هل تعلم؟
What was cute about ANNIE today...
ما الذي كان لطيفًا بشأن آني اليوم...
was when we were waiting in these school uniforms.
كان ذلك عندما كنا ننتظر بهذا الزي المدرسي.
"How do Korean students take photos..."
"كيف يلتقط الطلاب الكوريون الصور..."
"in their school uniforms?"
"في زيهم المدرسي؟"
"How do Korean students pose?"
"كيف يقف الطلاب الكوريين؟"
With these two girls,
مع هاتين الفتاتين،
I recalled my memories...
استرجعت ذكرياتي..
and took photos with a Korean high school student vibe.
والتقطت صوراً مع طالبة في المدرسة الثانوية الكورية.
"Vibe?"
"الاهتزاز؟"
Here's what I've always wanted to do.
إليك ما أردت دائمًا فعله.
Get tteokbokki on my way home...
احصل على tteokbokki في طريقي إلى المنزل...
- with my friends from school... - Tteokbokki?
- مع أصدقائي من المدرسة... - تتوكبوكي؟
while wearing our school uniforms.
أثناء ارتداء الزي المدرسي لدينا.
(After-school tteokbokki)
(تيوكبوكي بعد المدرسة)
And sundae too.
والمثلجات أيضا.
- That and... - Sundae?
- هذا و... - مثلجات؟
- Hold on. Time out. - Out of the blue?
- يتمسك. نفذ الوقت. - فجأة؟
- Tteokbokki, not sundae. - What about sundae?
- تتوكبوكي، وليس مثلجات. - ماذا عن المثلجات؟
She was talking about tteokbokki, so why mention sundae?
لقد كانت تتحدث عن تتوكبوكي، فلماذا تذكر المثلجات؟
Tteokbokki and sundae are a pair.
Tteokbokki و مثلجات زوجان.
- Come on. - Some people...
- تعال. - بعض الناس...
- Tteokbokki. - can't eat sundae.
- تتوكبوكي. - لا أستطيع أن أكل مثلجات.
And she might hate sundae.
وقد تكره المثلجات.
- I like sundae. - Sorry for interrupting.
- أحب المثلجات. - آسف للمقاطعة.
Back in Ho Dong's days, even hog maw was sold.
مرة أخرى في أيام هو دونغ، تم بيع حتى خنزير ماو.
Don't you know how chewy that is?
ألا تعرف كم هو مطاطي هذا؟
You dip it slightly in salt.
يمكنك غمسه قليلاً في الملح.
Look at the expression of the 2005 baby.
انظر إلى تعبير طفل 2005.
- Hog maw is rare, you know? - What's hog maw?
- خنزير ماو نادر، هل تعلم؟ - ما هو خنزير ماو؟
- The thin one. - Was it not sold in schools?
- الرقيقة . - ألم يباع في المدارس؟
- It's similar to liver on the side. - I bet Ho Dong ate it all.
- يشبه الكبد من الجانب. - أراهن أن هو دونغ أكل كل شيء.
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
The next student is...
الطالب التالي هو...
- You guys ended up with us oldies. - TARZZAN.
- يا رفاق انتهى بكم الأمر معنا كبار السن. - طرزان.
- TARZZAN's pre-debut history is... - What is it?
- تاريخ طرزان قبل ترسيمه هو... - ما هو؟
He wrote, "A dance talent taken away by the music industry."
وكتب: "موهبة الرقص سلبتها صناعة الموسيقى".
Really? Taken away from the dance industry?
حقًا؟ هل تم استبعادها من صناعة الرقص؟
- He's famous. - Contemporary dance.
- إنه مشهور. - الرقص المعاصر .
His earlier jump seemed quite different.
بدت قفزته السابقة مختلفة تمامًا.
You mentioned you used to dance.
لقد ذكرت أنك كنت ترقص.
- Yes. - And that's why you're TARZZAN.
- نعم. - ولهذا السبب أنت طرزان.
That's right. But I didn't start dancing because I wanted to.
هذا صحيح. لكنني لم أبدأ بالرقص لأنني أردت ذلك.
When I was little, I was introduced to hip-hop culture very early.
عندما كنت صغيرًا، تعرفت على ثقافة الهيب هوب في وقت مبكر جدًا.
When moving to the US, I wanted to be different from the others...
عندما انتقلت إلى الولايات المتحدة، أردت أن أكون مختلفًا عن الآخرين...
and wondered what I should do.
وتساءلت ماذا يجب أن أفعل.
Back then... There's a rapper named ASAP Rocky who is my favorite.
في ذلك الوقت... كان هناك مغني راب يدعى ASAP Rocky وهو المفضل لدي.
After watching his music video "Peso,"
بعد مشاهدة الفيديو الموسيقي الخاص به "بيزو"،
I thought of...
فكرت في...
becoming cool with gold teeth and all that.
تصبح باردة مع أسنان ذهبية وكل ذلك.
I wanted to become someone like him.
أردت أن أصبح شخصًا مثله.
When I came to Korea, I rebelled against my mom.
عندما أتيت إلى كوريا، تمردت على أمي.
"Mom, I want to become a rapper. Let me become one."
"أمي، أريد أن أصبح مغني راب. دعني أصبح واحدًا."
My mom told me to quit dreaming and go to university.
طلبت مني أمي أن أتوقف عن الحلم وأذهب إلى الجامعة.
Only after that could I do whatever I want.
فقط بعد ذلك يمكنني أن أفعل ما أريد.
- That's a similar story to ANNIE's. - Yes, it is.
- هذه قصة مشابهة لقصة آني. - نعم إنه كذلك.
But my cousin was learning ballet.
لكن ابن عمي كان يتعلم الباليه.
She dragged me to the dance academy, which started my dance life.
لقد جرتني إلى أكاديمية الرقص، والتي بدأت حياتي في الرقص.
- She dragged you into it. - Yes.
- لقد جرتك إليه. - نعم.
I put up with all the hours and somehow ended up...
لقد تحملت كل الساعات وانتهى الأمر بطريقة أو بأخرى ...
getting accepted to the Korea National University of Arts.
الحصول على قبول في جامعة كوريا الوطنية للفنون.
(With his excellent talent, he even got accepted...)
(بموهبته الممتازة، تم قبوله حتى...)
(to the Korea National University of Arts!)
(إلى جامعة كوريا الوطنية للفنون!)
That means you were born to do contemporary dance.
هذا يعني أنك ولدت للقيام بالرقص المعاصر.
You won a prize in your first competition.
لقد فزت بجائزة في مسابقتك الأولى.
Rather than saying I was born to do it,
بدلاً من القول أنني ولدت لأقوم بذلك،
I strive to be perfect in whatever I do.
أسعى إلى أن أكون مثاليًا في كل ما أقوم به.
- He's a hard worker. - If what I do...
- إنه عامل مجتهد. - إذا ماذا أفعل..
isn't perfect, I don't like showing it to people.
ليست مثالية، ولا أحب أن أظهرها للناس.
I was very harsh on myself.
لقد كنت قاسياً جداً على نفسي.
- I see. - What a surprise.
- أرى. - يا لها من مفاجأة.
Appearance-wise, you look like you'd just wing things.
من ناحية المظهر، تبدو وكأنك تجنح للأشياء فقط.
Other than work, I just wing things.
بخلاف العمل، أنا فقط أجنّح الأشياء.
TARZZAN makes the greatest comments.
طرزان يقدم أعظم التعليقات.
If you have experience dancing,
إذا كان لديك خبرة في الرقص،
K-pop dance must have been easy.
لا بد أن رقصة الكيبوب كانت سهلة.
No, it was really hard.
لا، كان الأمر صعبًا حقًا.
Here's an easy-to-understand example. It's the same...
إليك مثال سهل الفهم. إنه نفس الشيء...
as asking a vocalist to rap in a show...
كأنك تطلب من مطرب أن يغني موسيقى الراب في أحد العروض...
- like "Show Me the Money." - Right.
- مثل "أرني المال". - يمين.
I received a lot of help from BAILEY.
لقد تلقيت الكثير من المساعدة من بيلي.
- When it comes to dancing... - I was bad at dancing.
- عندما يتعلق الأمر بالرقص... - كنت سيئاً في الرقص.
But she taught me everything.
لكنها علمتني كل شيء.
- Still, I find it difficult. - Right.
- ومع ذلك، أجد صعوبة في ذلك. - يمين.
- YOUNGSEO wrote, - Zero.
- كتب يونجسيو، - صفر.
"Ranked second in an audition show."
"المرتبة الثانية في عرض الاختبار."
- Really? - I was in the show...
- حقًا؟ - كنت في المعرض...
- "R U Next?" that aired on JTBC. - "R U Next?"
- "RU التالي؟" التي تم بثها على قناة JTBC. - "RU التالي؟"
(Advancing to the final round in the girl group selection,)
(التأهل إلى الجولة النهائية في اختيار مجموعة الفتيات،)
(she came in 2nd place overall.)
(جاءت في المركز الثاني بشكل عام.)
(After working really hard,)
(بعد جهد كبير)
(YOUNGSEO took the first step towards her dream.)
(اتخذت يونغسيو الخطوة الأولى نحو حلمها.)
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I made up my mind...
لقد اتخذت قراري...
- and went for it. - I see.
- وذهب لذلك. - أرى.
But I really wanted to work with THEBLACKLABEL.
لكنني أردت حقًا العمل مع THEBLACKLABEL.
I applied to THEBLACKLABEL myself.
لقد تقدمت بطلب إلى THEBLACKLABEL بنفسي.
I sent a direct message on Instagram...
لقد أرسلت رسالة مباشرة على Instagram ...
with my height, weight, name,
مع طولي، وزني، اسمي،
singing video, dancing video,
فيديو غناء فيديو رقص,
- and profile photo. - Right.
- وصورة الملف الشخصي. - يمين.
After an audition at the company...
بعد الاختبار في الشركة..
and several meetings,
و عدة لقاءات
the company said it already had a girl group.
قالت الشركة أن لديها بالفعل مجموعة فتيات.
But it was preparing a different group...
لكنها كانت تستعد لمجموعة مختلفة...
and claimed it would be extremely cool.
وادعى أنه سيكون رائعًا للغاية.
I was asked, "Can you take it on, even though it isnt a girl group?"
سُئلت: "هل يمكنك قبولها، على الرغم من أنها ليست فرقة فتيات؟"
- "Can you take it on?"
- "هل يمكنك أن تأخذ ذلك؟" - "هل يمكنك أن تأخذ ذلك؟"
- Does TEDDY like period dramas? - TEDDY...
- هل يحب تيدي الأعمال الدرامية القديمة؟ - تيدي...
TEDDY asked YOUNGSEO, "Can you take it on?"
سأل تيدي يونغسيو، "هل يمكنك القيام بذلك؟"
- "Decide." - "YOUNGSEO, you are to answer."
- "يقرر." - "يونغسيو، عليك الإجابة."
(Decide right at this moment!)
(اتخذ القرار الصحيح في هذه اللحظة!)
- "It is a most splendid group." - "It will be a cool group."
- "إنها مجموعة رائعة." - "ستكون مجموعة رائعة."
- "Can you take it on?" - "It'll be very cool."
- "هل يمكنك أن تأخذ ذلك؟" - "سيكون رائعًا جدًا."
And what did you say?
وماذا قلت؟
- "I can take it on." - "I will do it."
- "أستطيع أن أتحمل ذلك." - "أنا سأفعلها."
- "I shall do it."
- "سأفعل". - "سأفعل".
But honestly...
لكن بصراحة...
"Have the manager come in."
"اطلب من المدير الدخول."
(Please stop it now...)
(من فضلك توقف عن ذلك الآن...)
- It's like a period drama.
- إنها مثل الدراما الفترة. - إنها مثل الدراما الفترة.
- You clenched your teeth. - That's the system.
- لقد صرتُ على أسنانك. - هذا هو النظام.
(That's not true.)
(هذا ليس صحيحا).
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
he said I wasn't going to go solo, it was going to be a team...
لقد قال أنني لن أذهب منفرداً، بل سيكون فريقاً...
but not a girl group.
ولكن ليس فرقة فتيات.
It was during the time when virtual singers were trending.
كان ذلك في الوقت الذي كان فيه المطربون الافتراضيون رائجين.
I thought, "Am I going to be an AI singer?"
فكرت: "هل سأصبح مغنية تعمل بالذكاء الاصطناعي؟"
- You would be worried. - "What will I be doing?"
- سوف تكون قلقة. - "ماذا سأفعل؟"
Becoming an AI singer...
أن تصبح مغنية بالذكاء الاصطناعي...
- Pardon? - AI singer...
- عفو؟ - مغنية الذكاء الاصطناعي...
- You know what a virtual singer is. - Yes.
- أنت تعرف ما هو المغني الافتراضي. - نعم.
To put it simply, it's like Adam.
بكل بساطة، إنه مثل آدم.
- Adam. - Is that so?
- آدم. - هل هذا صحيح؟
- You wouldn't know. - Adam...
- لن تعرف. - آدم...
There's an original senior.
هناك كبار الأصلي.
Adam got infected with a virus.
أصيب آدم بفيروس.
There was a rumor like that.
كانت هناك شائعة من هذا القبيل.
- It was infected. - Is it in the data center?
- لقد أصيب. - هل هو في مركز البيانات؟
- It's too... - Where is Adam?
- إنه أيضًا... - أين آدم؟
Some also say it was hacked.
ويقول البعض أيضًا أنه تم اختراقه.
You were there.
كنت هناك.
I was destined to be in ALLDAY PROJECT.
لقد كان مقدرًا لي أن أكون في مشروع ALLDAY.
- Okay. - Good.
- تمام. - جيد.
- As far as I know, - Yes.
- على حد علمي - نعم.
YOUNGSEO and I have the same background.
يونغسيو وأنا لدينا نفس الخلفية.
Are you also from "R U Next?"
هل أنت أيضًا من "RU Next؟"
No.
لا.
Is YOUNGSEO also from Mexico? What do you mean?
هل يونغسيو أيضاً من المكسيك؟ ماذا تقصد؟
Are you from Mexico, YOUNGSEO?
هل أنت من المكسيك، يونغسيو؟
- Senorita. - I'm Korean.
- سنيوريتا. - أنا كورية.
I meant YouTube.
كنت أقصد اليوتيوب.
Didn't you start YouTube a long time ago?
لم تبدأ يوتيوب منذ فترة طويلة؟
I was a kid YouTuber.
لقد كنت طفلاً على YouTube.
- Really? - Ever since...
- حقًا؟ - منذ...
- she was really young. - Very young.
- كانت صغيرة حقا. - صغير جدًا.
- Hello. - That's...
- مرحبًا. - هذا...
I'm Mylynn.
أنا ميلين.
(YOUNGSEO, in 7th grade)
(يونغسيو، في الصف السابع)
(Mylynn)
(ميلين)
(CherryGrapefruit)
(الكرز والجريب فروت)
- That's... - Today, I'm here with...
- هذا... - أنا هنا اليوم مع...
(Kid YouTuber YOUNGSEO who went by CherryGrapefruit)
(مستخدم YouTube الصغير YOUNGSEO الذي اختار CherryGrapefruit)
- Goodness. - CherryGrapefruit...
- الخير. -الكرز والجريب فروت...
(This is CherryGrapefruit, the final winner...)
(هذا هو CherryGrapefruit، الفائز النهائي...)
(of the 3rd Kids Creator Competition.)
(من مسابقة الأطفال الثالثة للمبدعين.)
You talked well ever since you were young.
لقد تحدثت جيدًا منذ أن كنت صغيرًا.
- She's the final winner. - I didn't know about that.
- إنها الفائز النهائي. - لم أكن أعرف عن ذلك.
Congratulations.
تهانينا.
- That time... - You weren't that young.
- ذلك الوقت... - لم تكن صغيرا.
- In 7th grade.
- في الصف السابع. - في الصف السابع.
You're the most senior here.
أنت الأقدم هنا.
So I'm the senior...
إذن أنا الأكبر...
in the YouTube world.
في عالم اليوتيوب.
- Right. - The first generation.
- يمين. - الجيل الأول.
- First generation. - Who edited the videos?
- الجيل الأول. - من قام بتحرير الفيديوهات؟
At the time, I did all the planning, directing, and editing.
في ذلك الوقت، قمت بكل التخطيط والإخراج والتحرير.
- That's amazing. - How many subscribers did you have?
- هذا مذهل. - كم عدد المشتركين لديك؟
I was a major YouTuber back then.
لقد كنت أحد مستخدمي YouTube الرئيسيين في ذلك الوقت.
Normally, elementary school YouTubers...
عادةً، مستخدمي YouTube في المدارس الابتدائية...
had 100 to 1,000 subscribers.
كان لديه 100 إلى 1000 مشترك.
I had tens of thousands.
كان لدي عشرات الآلاف.
- That's a lot. - Did that boy...
- هذا كثير. - هل ذلك الفتى...
- become Ddotty? - That's not easy.
- تصبح ددوتي؟ - هذا ليس بالأمر السهل.
- Back then, - He was popular.
- في ذلك الوقت - كان يتمتع بشعبية كبيرة.
- Mylynn. - he was like the Yu Jae Seok...
- ميلين . - لقد كان مثل يو جاي سوك...
of elementary school kids.
من أطفال المدارس الابتدائية.
(H'es already at the age to go to the military.)
(إنه بالفعل في سن الذهاب إلى الجيش.)
It's really amazing that she planned and edited...
إنه لأمر مدهش حقًا أنها خططت وقامت بالتحرير ...
- back then. - Right.
- في ذلك الوقت. - يمين.
- That's hard. - What happened to the channel?
- هذا صعب. - ماذا حدث للقناة؟
I boldly deleted the account...
لقد قمت بحذف الحساب بكل شجاعة..
to become a trainee.
لتصبح متدربا.
You could have given it to me.
كان بإمكانك أن تعطيها لي.
- You could have just closed it. - We can't watch it now.
- كان بإمكانك إغلاقه للتو. - لا يمكننا مشاهدته الآن.
- Did you come up with the name?
- لا يمكننا مشاهدته الآن. - هل توصلت إلى الاسم؟
- I did. - Why?
- فعلتُ. - لماذا؟
- "I did." - What does it mean?
- "فعلتُ." - ماذا يعني ذلك؟
I also think it's a bit...
وأعتقد أيضا أنه قليلا ...
corny.
حنطي.
But back then, I thought it was cute.
ولكن في ذلك الوقت، اعتقدت أنه كان لطيفا.
- It was a childish vibe. - It was a cute name.
- لقد كانت أجواء طفولية. - لقد كان اسما لطيفا.
- CherryGrapefruit.
-الكرز والجريب فروت. -الكرز والجريب فروت.
You could have debuted as CherryGrapefruit...
كان من الممكن أن تترسم كـ CherryGrapefruit...
- of ALLDAY PROJECT. - Right.
- من مشروع ALLDAY. - يمين.
- That's nice. - Actually,
- هذا لطيف. - في الحقيقة،
Producer TEDDY said he wanted me to use a stage name.
قال المنتج تيدي إنه يريد مني أن أستخدم اسمًا مسرحيًا.
He told the company to get a list of stage names for YOUNGSEO.
أخبر الشركة أن تحصل على قائمة بأسماء المسرح لـ YOUNGSEO.
All the employees really came up...
لقد جاء جميع الموظفين حقًا. . .
- with a whole list. - What was there? Tell us a few...
- مع قائمة كاملة. - ماذا كان هناك؟ أخبرنا ببعض...
- that were nice. - I was really shocked by this.
- كان ذلك لطيفا. - لقد صدمت حقا من هذا.
The employees knew that YOUNG stood for zero.
عرف الموظفون أن YOUNG تمثل الصفر.
They seriously came up with "Zero West."
لقد توصلوا بجدية إلى "Zero West".
- YOUNGSEO.
- يونجسيو. - يونجسيو.
- That's almost like Sang Min. - They just use the words.
- هذا تقريبا مثل سانغ مين. - إنهم يستخدمون الكلمات فقط.
- East coast! - Zero West.
- الساحل الشرقي! - صفر غرب .
- They were really outdated. - That's how Sang Min...
- لقد كانوا عفا عليها الزمن حقا. - هكذا سانغ مين...
- makes names. - West coast!
- يصنع أسماء. - الساحل الغربي!
- Instead of CherryGrapefruit, - Cherry is nice.
- بدلاً من الكرز، الجريب فروت، - الكرز جميل.
you could have used Cherry.
كان بإمكانك استخدام الكرز.
If she goes with Cherry, you need to give...
إذا ذهبت مع شيري، عليك أن تعطي...
some fruit names to the members.
بعض أسماء الفواكه للأعضاء.
I should go with Apple.
يجب أن أذهب مع أبل.
- Apple and so on. - Blueberry.
- أبل وهكذا. - توت.
ANNIE would have been Zucchini.
كان من الممكن أن تكون آني كوسة.
You need fruit names.
أنت بحاجة إلى أسماء الفاكهة.
- Zucchini. - Wait. They all have pretty names.
- كوسة. - انتظر. كلهم لديهم أسماء جميلة.
- Why is mine Zucchini? - I mean...
- لماذا لي كوسة؟ - أعني...
You should still keep the surname.
لا يزال يتعين عليك الاحتفاظ باللقب.
BAILEY could be Pear.
يمكن أن يكون بيلي كمثرى.
- Pear. - Pear. I like that.
- كُمَّثرَى. - كُمَّثرَى. أحب ذلك.
TARZZAN could go with Walnut.
طرزان يمكن أن يذهب مع الجوز.
Hold on. Walnuts aren't fruits.
يتمسك. الجوز ليس فاكهة.
You go well with nuts.
تسير على ما يرام مع المكسرات.
Tylenol?
تايلينول؟
Walnut suits you well.
الجوز يناسبك جيدا.
Why am I Walnut?
لماذا أنا الجوز؟
- TARZZAN... - Zucchini.
- طرزان... - كوسة.
looks like a foreigner, so instead of Walnut,
يبدو وكأنه أجنبي، لذا بدلاً من الجوز،
he could be Pecan.
يمكن أن يكون البقان.
- What is pecan? - He really likes coconuts.
- ما هو البقان؟ - انه حقا يحب جوز الهند.
- I like coconuts. - Just because you've eaten them...
- أنا أحب جوز الهند. - فقط لأنك أكلتهم..
Just because you've eaten them a lot...
فقط لأنك أكلتهم كثيراً..
- Because you ate pecan pie... - What's a pecan?
- لأنك أكلت فطيرة البقان... - ما هو البقان؟
Pecan.
البقان.
- Pecan pie. - Sir. I'm sorry,
- فطيرة البقان. - سيد. أنا آسف،
- but are pecans...
- فطيرة البقان. - ولكن هي البقان ...
that rare in Korea?
هذا نادر في كوريا؟
- I've never had that before. - We've never had pecan pie.
- لم يسبق لي ذلك من قبل. - لم يسبق لنا أن تناولنا فطيرة جوز البقان.
Do I have to be scolded so much...
هل يجب أن أتوب إلى هذا الحد...؟
just because I said pecan instead of walnut?
فقط لأنني قلت البقان بدلا من الجوز؟
Don't spread rumors to your colleagues.
لا تنشر الشائعات بين زملائك.
It'll be hard to invite them.
سيكون من الصعب دعوتهم.
I don't know what it is.
لا أعرف ما هو.
You also ate it. You just don't know you did.
أنت أيضا أكلته. أنت فقط لا تعرف أنك فعلت.
We've never eaten pecans.
نحن لم نأكل قط البقان.
- You also... - Jang Hoon could become a rapper.
- أنت أيضًا... - يمكن لجانغ هون أن يصبح مغني راب.
Jang Hoon.
جانج هون.
I've been listening quietly...
كنت أستمع بهدوء..
- Angry Man. - Right.
- رجل غاضب. - يمين.
I've been listening quietly,
لقد كنت أستمع بهدوء،
and all I can hear is his voice.
وكل ما أستطيع سماعه هو صوته.
I can give you a rap name.
أستطيع أن أعطيك اسم الراب.
- From today, you're Seo Pecan. - Seo Pecan.
- من اليوم، أنت سيو بيكان. - سيو بيكان.
- No. - What meaning...
- لا. - أي معنى...
does it have?
هل لديها؟
- Pecan... - Be careful of him.
- البقان... - كن حذرا منه.
- You'll be in trouble. - Pecan is a bit long.
- سوف تكون في ورطة. - البقان طويل بعض الشيء.
- He has a name. It's West Long. - You've all had it.
- لديه اسم. إنه الغرب الطويل. - لقد كان كل ذلك.
West Long.
غرب طويل.
- Seo Pecan. - Stop saying you don't know.
- سيو بيكان. - توقف عن قول أنك لا تعرف.
Now, it's WOOCHAN.
الآن، إنه ووشان.
- Let me see. - West Long.
- دعني أرى. - غرب طويل.
Speaking of rap, WOOCHAN wrote...
بالحديث عن موسيقى الراب، كتب WOOCHAN...
- "rapper on the rise." - Skills.
- "مغني الراب في الارتفاع." - مهارات.
"Show Me the Money."
"أرني المال."
- You know him. - But...
- أنت تعرفه. - لكن...
- do you really not remember? - He...
- هل حقا لا تتذكر؟ - هو...
- Hold on. - Soo Geun...
- يتمسك. - سو جيون...
Answer my question, WOOCHAN.
أجب على سؤالي، ووشان.
Do you have a connection with Soo Geun or not?
هل لديك اتصال مع Soo Geun أم لا؟
- I have a connection with him. - Hey.
- لدي اتصال معه. - يا.
Do you have a connection with WOOCHAN or not?
هل لديك اتصال مع WOOCHAN أم لا؟
- I don't. - Goodness.
- أنا لا. - الخير.
I also remember...
وأتذكر أيضا...
- because I was a bit involved. - Really?
- لأنني كنت متورطا قليلا. - حقًا؟
- Right. - That's why I know.
- يمين. - ولهذا أعرف.
- I'm sorry, but... - I say this all the time.
- أنا آسف، ولكن... - أقول هذا طوال الوقت.
Soo Geun is the coldest one here.
Soo Geun هي الأكثر برودة هنا.
- He's cold. - When the recording ends,
- إنه بارد. - عندما ينتهي التسجيل،
he forgets about everything.
ينسى كل شيء.
West Long!
غرب طويل!
I'm very different now.
أنا مختلف جدًا الآن.
- I grew up a lot. - I'm sorry.
- لقد كبرت كثيرا. - أنا آسف.
How do I remember you?
كيف أتذكرك؟
We were in a show called "Player."
كنا في عرض يسمى "اللاعب".
I was his rap teacher.
كنت مدرس الراب له.
(When others recited Buddhist scriptures)
(عندما كان الآخرون يتلون الكتب البوذية المقدسة)
(He even got his rap judged by him.)
(حتى أنه حكم على موسيقى الراب بواسطته).
(I think the team we're up against...)
(أعتقد أن الفريق الذي سنواجهه ...)
(is Team Dynamic Duo.)
(هو فريق الثنائي الديناميكي.)
(They even had a meeting together.)
(حتى أنهم عقدوا اجتماعًا معًا.)
- Goodness. - That much?
- الخير. - بهذا القدر؟
- You forgot your teacher? - When you were MC Jooji.
- نسيت معلمك؟ - عندما كنت MC Jooji.
Jooji.
أوقفه.
MC Jooji doesn't learn...
MC Jooji لا يتعلم...
- how to rap from others. - No.
- كيفية الراب من الآخرين. - لا.
I taught MC Jooji the rhythm.
لقد علمت MC Jooji الإيقاع.
I also helped you write the lyrics.
لقد ساعدتك أيضًا في كتابة الكلمات.
He even wrote the lyrics for you?
حتى أنه كتب كلمات الأغاني لك؟
He acted like he did everything.
لقد تصرف وكأنه فعل كل شيء.
He wrote it for him.
لقد كتب ذلك بالنسبة له.
Did Soo Geun take care of you well?
هل اعتنت بك Soo Geun جيدًا؟
- He didn't... - Honestly, that wouldn't be true.
- لم يفعل... - بصراحة، هذا لن يكون صحيحاً.
- I would have been really nice. - He was cold, right?
- كنت سأكون لطيفا حقا. - كان باردا، أليس كذلك؟
- He was cold. - Right.
- كان باردا. - يمين.
- But I'm used to that.
- يمين. - ولكن أنا معتاد على ذلك.
I've been doing broadcasting work...
كنت أقوم بأعمال إذاعية..
from a young age,
منذ الصغر،
so I was pushed around a lot.
لذلك تم دفعي كثيرًا.
People also look down on you because you're young.
الناس أيضًا ينظرون إليك بازدراء لأنك صغير السن.
Lee Soo Geun...
لي سو جيون ...
Lee Soo Geun caused trouble.
تسبب لي سو جيون في المتاعب.
I told you not to look down on people. Please.
قلت لك ألا تنظر إلى الناس باستخفاف. لو سمحت.
I told you to be sincere when you're with people.
أخبرتك أن تكون صادقًا عندما تكون مع الناس.
Whether it's an adult or a child...
سواء كان بالغًا أو طفلًا..
Sincerity!
الإخلاص!
(Hitting the spot)
(ضرب المكان)
Apologize to him now.
اعتذري له الآن.
- I'm sorry. - You should get up and apologize.
- أنا آسف. - يجب عليك النهوض والاعتذار.
- What did I do? I don't remember. - No.
- ماذا فعلت؟ أنا لا أتذكر. - لا.
What did you teach him?
ماذا علمته؟
- You wrote the lyrics for him. - Well...
- لقد كتبت كلمات له. - حسنًا...
- I was the judge. - MC...
- كنت القاضي. - ام سي...
I gave him the necklace,
وأعطيته القلادة
and he came to my team.
وجاء إلى فريقي.
I passed the audition in front of WOOCHAN.
لقد اجتزت الاختبار أمام WOOCHAN.
Reenact it. Standby.
أعد تمثيلها. تعليق.
Back then, I...
في ذلك الوقت، أنا...
(To all the people)
(إلى كل الناس)
(I)
(أنا)
I was MC Jooji.
لقد كنت MC Jooji.
- Give joy, I give laughter - Right.
- أعط الفرح، أعطي الضحك - صحيح.
- Right. - So give me that necklace
- يمين. - لذا أعطني تلك القلادة
- Like that. - Right.
- هكذا. - يمين.
How do you remember that?
كيف تتذكر ذلك؟
I picked you after seeing you hit like this.
لقد اخترتك بعد أن رأيتك تضرب بهذه الطريقة.
Really?
حقًا؟
(To all the people)
(إلى كل الناس)
(I give joy, I give laughter)
(أعطي الفرح، أعطي الضحك)
(So give me that necklace)
(فأعطني تلك القلادة)
(Exclaiming)
(صراخ)
(He's amazed by the rhyme.)
(إنه مندهش من القافية.)
(You have to learn how to rap from MC Jooji.)
(عليك أن تتعلم كيفية غناء الراب من MC Jooji.)
- I'm really sorry. - It's okay.
- أنا آسف حقا. - لا بأس.
I don't know how I should apologize to you.
لا أعرف كيف يجب أن أعتذر لك.
It's okay. I'm used to it.
لا بأس. أنا معتاد على ذلك.
That's sad.
هذا محزن.
The adults...
الكبار...
He knows how to kill people.
إنه يعرف كيف يقتل الناس.
Actually, I'm...
في الواقع، أنا...
- Right. - I've become 21.
- يمين. - لقد أصبح عمري 21.
WOOCHAN kills me with one shot.
WOOCHAN يقتلني برصاصة واحدة.
I want to be nicer.
أريد أن أكون أجمل.
I want to be nicer to people younger than me.
أريد أن أكون ألطف مع الأشخاص الأصغر مني.
- Ever since that day? - You've been hurt.
- منذ ذلك اليوم؟ - لقد تأذيت.
I want to be nice to people who want to rap well...
أريد أن أكون لطيفًا مع الأشخاص الذين يريدون غناء الراب بشكل جيد..
or have a dream.
أو لديك حلم.
WOOCHAN is really attacking Soo Geun well.
WOOCHAN يهاجم Soo Geun جيدًا حقًا.
- Right. - WOOCHAN...
- يمين. - ووشان...
- WOOCHAN had quite an experience.
- كان لدى WOOCHAN خبرة كبيرة. - ووشان...
I was a good adult.
لقد كنت بالغًا جيدًا.
It was a very good lesson.
لقد كان درسا جيدا جدا.
- Right. - Seriously.
- يمين. - بجد.
Soo Geun.
سو جيون.
WOOCHAN is the youngest participant of "Show Me the Money."
WOOCHAN هو أصغر مشارك في برنامج "Show Me the Money".
It must have been so overwhelming...
لا بد أن الأمر كان ساحقا للغاية ...
- with so many seniors watching. - Right.
- مع مشاهدة الكثير من كبار السن. - يمين.
- There was something famous.
- يمين. - كان هناك شيء مشهور.
I made it to the top six.
لقد وصلت إلى المراكز الستة الأولى.
- Really? - That wouldn't have been easy.
- حقًا؟ - لم يكن ذلك سهلاً.
He was amazing.
لقد كان مذهلاً.
- Top six. - His battle...
- الستة الأوائل. - معركته...
with Woo Won Jae is really famous.
مع Woo Won Jae مشهور حقًا.
(Do your thing properly)
(قم بعملك بشكل صحيح)
(Won Jae)
(وون جاي)
(Don't worry, WOOCHAN, you can cry)
(لا تقلق، وووتشان، يمكنك البكاء)
(Santa doesn't exist)
(سانتا غير موجود)
- It's similar. - His Instagram ID...
- انها مماثلة. - معرف الانستغرام الخاص به...
is still Santa WOOCHAN.
لا يزال سانتا ووشان.
- Santa. - So...
- المقدسة. - أنا أعرف...
It's not anger,
إنه ليس الغضب،
but I think those things turned into energy.
ولكن أعتقد أن تلك الأشياء تحولت إلى طاقة.
Being looked down and all...
نظرت إلى الأسفل وكل شيء...
Hold on. Not looked down...
يتمسك. لم تنظر للأسفل...
- Thank you. - Looking down on an eighth grader?
- شكرًا لك. - النظر إلى أسفل على طالب الصف الثامن؟
- I shouldn't keep doing this. - I don't do that.
- لا ينبغي لي أن أستمر في فعل هذا. - أنا لا أفعل ذلك.
- That's not what I mean. - You don't intend...
- ليس هذا ما أقصده. - أنت لا تنوي...
- to apologize officially, do you? - No.
- للاعتذار رسميا، أليس كذلك؟ - لا.
- Ho Dong is excited. - I'm sorry.
- هو دونغ متحمس. - أنا آسف.
- This is too much. - You should come and hug him.
- هذا كثير جدا. - يجب أن تأتي وتعانقه.
- I... - Come and hug him.
- أنا... - تعالي وعانقيه.
- Give him a hug. - Right.
- أعطيه عناق. - يمين.
I didn't mean...
لم أقصد...
- Okay. - You should hug him.
- تمام. - يجب أن تعانقه.
- Hug him. - Yes, WOOCHAN.
- احتضنه. - نعم، ووشان.
- I'm sorry. - No. Don't say that.
- أنا آسف. - لا، لا تقل ذلك.
- Soo Geun. - You should become successful.
- سو جيون. - يجب أن تصبح ناجحا.
Give him a genuine hug.
أعطه عناقًا حقيقيًا.
Please be sincere.
من فضلك كن صادقا.
Even while hugging, you only look at the camera.
حتى أثناء العناق، فإنك تنظر فقط إلى الكاميرا.
(They reconciled.)
(تصالحوا).
He was made fun of a lot...
لقد سخر منه كثيرا..
- saying there's no Santa. - He would have been teased a lot.
- قائلا لا يوجد سانتا. - لكان قد أزعج كثيرا.
So much.
كثيرا.
- People recognized me a lot. - Right.
- عرفني الناس كثيرًا. - يمين.
I used to take subways and buses...
كنت أستقل مترو الأنفاق والحافلات..
- Really? - because I was young.
- حقًا؟ - لأنني كنت صغيرا.
- Someone suddenly came... - Did people recognize you?
- جاء شخص فجأة... - هل تعرف عليك الناس؟
next to me...
بجانبي...
and said, "There's no Santa, WOOCHAN."
وقال: "ليس هناك سانتا، ووشان."
Like a catchphrase?
مثل عبارة شعار؟
I would also get calls from unknown callers.
سأتلقى أيضًا مكالمات من متصلين غير معروفين.
They would say that phrase and cut the call.
سيقولون هذه العبارة ويقطعون المكالمة.
That happened many times.
لقد حدث ذلك عدة مرات.
Recently, I met Won Jae...
لقد التقيت مؤخرًا بـ وون جاي.
- at an event. - Right.
- في حدث ما. - يمين.
But I'm actually very thankful...
لكني في الحقيقة ممتنة للغاية..
- that he created that for me. - The meme?
- أنه خلق ذلك لي. - الميم؟
But what's interesting is, you were doing well in hip-hop,
لكن المثير للاهتمام هو أنك كنت تبلي بلاءً حسناً في الهيب هوب،
so why didn't you continue on with that...
فلماذا لم تستمر في ذلك...
instead of training to become an idol?
بدلا من التدريب ليصبح ايدول؟
Because I got too much attention at such a young age,
لأنني حصلت على الكثير من الاهتمام في مثل هذه السن المبكرة،
my parents were very worried.
كان والدي قلقين للغاية.
And it was a bit too much for me as well,
وكان الأمر كثيرًا جدًا بالنسبة لي أيضًا،
since I was young.
منذ أن كنت صغيرا.
So it was really tough mentally,
لذلك كان الأمر صعبًا جدًا على المستوى الذهني،
and my parents told me to stop...
ووالداي طلبا مني أن أتوقف..
and focus on my teenage life,
والتركيز على حياتي في مرحلة المراهقة،
so I came back to my life as a student.
لذلك عدت إلى حياتي كطالبة.
I did my studies and traveled,
اكملت دراستي وسافرت
building up on those experiences.
البناء على تلك التجارب.
But looking back, if it weren't for those times, I wouldn't be here.
لكن إذا نظرنا إلى الوراء، لولا تلك الأوقات، لما كنت هنا.
You grew up right.
لقد كبرت على حق.
You ignored him at such an important time.
لقد تجاهلته في مثل هذا الوقت المهم.
- You did. - So...
- لقد فعلت. - لذا...
It became such a big energy for him.
لقد أصبحت طاقة كبيرة بالنسبة له.
WOOCHAN,
ووشان،
this is not your place.
هذا ليس مكانك.
- It's not? - It's not.
- ليست كذلك؟ - ليست كذلك.
Go back.
عُد.
- This isn't for him? - Hey.
- هذا ليس له؟ - يا.
- MC Jooji. - West Long, drop the beat.
- إم سي جوجي. - ويست لونج، توقف عن الإيقاع.
West Long.
غرب طويل.
He loves it when I have a hard time.
إنه يحب ذلك عندما أواجه صعوبة.
(It's the most welcomed time for Jang Hoon.)
(إنه الوقت الأكثر ترحيبًا لجانغ هون.)
- BAILEY.
- بيلي. - بيلي.
For BAILEY's debut...
بالنسبة لظهور بيلي الأول...
I felt this when I saw her perform earlier.
شعرت بهذا عندما رأيتها تؤدي في وقت سابق.
She wrote "choreographer."
كتبت "مصممة الرقصات".
She did so much work.
لقد فعلت الكثير من العمل.
Who did you...
من فعلت...
choreograph for, BAILEY?
مصممة الرقصات لبيلي؟
- Lisa of BLACKPINK, - What?
- ليزا من بلاك بينك، - ماذا؟
Taeyang,
تايانغ،
- Taeyang? - and aespa, as well.
- تايانغ؟ - و إيسبا كذلك.
- For aespa? - Yes.
- لايسبا؟ - نعم.
- That's amazing. - SHINee.
- هذا مذهل. - شايني.
- SHINee, too? - Really?
- شايني أيضاً؟ - حقًا؟
- And ALLDAY PROJECT. - That's all of SM.
- ومشروع طوال اليوم. - هذا كل ما في SM.
Then how old were you when you first started choreography?
إذن كم كان عمرك عندما بدأت تصميم الرقصات لأول مرة؟
About 13 or 14 years old.
حوالي 13 أو 14 سنة.
- Really? - Since middle school?
- حقًا؟ - منذ المدرسة المتوسطة؟
Then did you make all the moves for the performance you showed us?
إذن هل قمت بكل الحركات للأداء الذي أظهرته لنا؟
Yes. Almost.
نعم. بالكاد.
She's a goat. The GOAT.
إنها عنزة. الماعز.
- Is that why it's "GOAT?" - Yes.
- هل هذا هو السبب في أنها "عنزة؟" - نعم.
She's our ultimate performance director.
إنها مديرة الأداء النهائية لدينا.
There's that part where you use your hands like a ninja.
هناك ذلك الجزء الذي تستخدم فيه يديك مثل النينجا.
(She even made the signature move of "Famous.")
(حتى أنها قامت بالحركة المميزة لـ "Famous".)
We didn't teach Ho Dong.
نحن لم نعلم هو دونغ.
We've heard of young dancers,
لقد سمعنا عن الراقصين الشباب،
- but she's a young choreographer. - I know.
- لكنها مصممة رقصات شابة. - أنا أعرف.
- That's a first. - She has to create it.
- وهذا هو الأول. - وعليها أن تخلقه.
You can produce everything on your own.
يمكنك إنتاج كل شيء بنفسك.
- Yes. - Yes, since you make the songs...
- نعم. - نعم، بما أنك تصنع الأغاني...
You have a choreographer...
لديك مصمم رقصات...
You write your own rap lines. You can do everything.
أنت تكتب خطوط الراب الخاصة بك. يمكنك أن تفعل كل شيء.
They can do it all.
يمكنهم فعل كل شيء.
ANNIE, what is "B Camp?"
آني، ما هو "المعسكر ب"؟
B Camp is...
معسكر ب...
I'm trembling even as I speak about it.
أنا أرتجف حتى وأنا أتحدث عن ذلك.
What kind of camp? Is it more famous than "Divorce Camp?"
أي نوع من المخيم؟ هل هو أكثر شهرة من "معسكر الطلاق"؟
It's...
إنه...
What is "B Camp?"
ما هو "معسكر ب"؟
- We call "BAILEY Camp" "B Camp." - "BAILEY Camp?"
- نحن نسمي "معسكر بيلي" "معسكر ب". - "معسكر بيلي؟"
- Does she teach dance classes? - Even when we were trainees,
- هل تقوم بتدريس دروس الرقص؟ - حتى عندما كنا متدربين،
we would learn the dance from BAILEY,
كنا نتعلم الرقص من بيلي،
and whenever we practice under the leadership of BAILEY,
وكلما تدربنا تحت قيادة بيلي،
we would call it "B Camp."
نحن نسميه "معسكر ب".
(YOUNGSEO! You come over here.)
(يونغسيو! تعال إلى هنا.)
(In sync)
(متزامن)
(Leading with charisma)
(القيادة بالكاريزما)
At first, there were a lot of ups and downs,
في البداية كان هناك الكثير من الصعود والهبوط،
but these days... These days, as well? No...
لكن هذه الأيام... هذه الأيام أيضاً؟ لا...
No, we have too many ups and downs.
لا، لدينا الكثير من الصعود والهبوط.
- We still have ups and downs. - Because...
- لا يزال لدينا صعودا وهبوطا. - لأن...
BAILEY's...
بيلي...
- usual self, - Yes, we don't see that.
- النفس المعتادة، - نعم، لا نرى ذلك.
- and her choreographer mode... - She's scary.
- ووضع مصمم الرقصات الخاص بها... - إنها مخيفة.
- Teacher BAILEY. - during B Camp is so different.
- المعلم بيلي. - خلال المعسكر B، الأمر مختلف تمامًا.
Then it is a bit similar...
ثم إنه مشابه قليلاً ...
to "Divorce Camp."
إلى "معسكر الطلاق".
- He is so harsh. - Your role.
- فهو قاس جدا. - دورك.
- How do you scold them? - She doesn't scold.
- كيف توبخهم؟ - إنها لا توبخ.
- "Your fist has to be like this."
- إنها لا توبخ. - "يجب أن تكون قبضة يدك هكذا."
- "Like this." - That detailed?
- "مثله." - هذا مفصل؟
- Yes. - She's very detailed?
- نعم. - إنها مفصلة للغاية؟
BAILEY, excluding yourself,
بيلي، باستثناء نفسك،
give us the ranking for dancing skills.
تعطينا الترتيب لمهارات الرقص.
- Between the four. - They are all amazing.
- بين الأربعة. - كلهم ​​مذهلون.
- For us, Shin Dong is first place, - That's hard.
- بالنسبة لنا، شين دونغ هو المركز الأول - هذا صعب.
- and Eunhyuk was second. - That's it.
- وكان انهيوك في المركز الثاني. - هذا كل شيء.
- He is so good. - Yes, TARZZAN is good.
- انه جيد جدا. - نعم، طرزان جيد.
Im a bit of a slacker, though.
أنا قليلا من المتهرب، رغم ذلك.
- What? - Do you know what that means?
- ماذا؟ - هل تعرف ماذا يعني ذلك؟
- Of course, we do. - Sure.
- بالطبع نفعل. - بالتأكيد.
Im a bit of a slacker,
أنا قليلا من المتهرب،
- so I always get in trouble. - Do you not practice?
- لذلك أقع في المشاكل دائمًا. - هل لا تمارس؟
- In my own opinion, - It's because you're a genius.
- في رأيي الخاص - لأنك عبقري.
when I saw you dance, I thought YOUNGSEO was really good.
عندما رأيتك ترقص، اعتقدت أن يونغسيو كان جيدًا حقًا.
- Is that right? How is she? - YOUNGSEO is too fast.
- هل هذا صحيح؟ كيف حالها؟ - YOUNGSEO سريع جدًا.
She's fast?
انها سريعة؟
- She's fast to learn. - She's so fast to learn.
- إنها سريعة التعلم. - إنها سريعة جدًا في التعلم.
- Not her speed? - No.
- ليس سرعتها؟ - لا.
What a relief. I got her approval.
يا لها من راحة. لقد حصلت على موافقتها.
- BAILEY, can we see your dance? - We need to see it.
- بيلي، هل يمكننا رؤية رقصتك؟ - نحن بحاجة لرؤيته.
- Can you show us? - Yes.
- هل يمكنك أن تظهر لنا؟ - نعم.
- Really?
- نعم. - حقًا؟
- Let's go. - She even did PSY's dance.
- دعنا نذهب. - حتى أنها قامت برقصة PSY.
PSY?
ساي؟
That's such a long time ago.
هذا منذ وقت طويل.
(Choreography by BAILEY, "Psycho" by Red Velvet)
(تصميم الرقصات لبيلي، "Psycho" لريد فيلفيت)
"Psycho."
"مريض نفسي."
(BAILEY set up a wall.)
(أقام بيلي جدارًا.)
(The ultimate wall)
(الجدار النهائي)
There it is.
ها هو.
Hey.
يا.
- It does seem different. - Something about it.
- يبدو الأمر مختلفاً. - شيء عنه.
(Look at B, You can feel it)
(انظر إلى B، يمكنك أن تشعر به)
Yes.
نعم.
(You can feel it, It's a vibe)
(يمكنك أن تشعر به، إنه شعور)
She plays with it.
إنها تلعب بها.
- "Illusion."
- "وهم." - "وهم."
(Choreography by BAILEY, "Illusion" by aespa)
(تصميم الرقصات بواسطة بيلي، "الوهم" بواسطة إيسبا)
"Illusion."
"وهم."
Gosh, she's good.
يا إلهي، إنها جيدة.
Like this.
مثله.
(I would go to B Camp even if I'm scared.)
(سأذهب إلى المعسكر "ب" حتى لو كنت خائفًا).
Teacher BAI.
المعلم باي
She worked hard.
لقد عملت بجد.
B Camp.
معسكر ب.
That's amazing.
هذا مذهل.
I wouldn't be able to graduate if I went to B Camp.
لن أكون قادرًا على التخرج إذا ذهبت إلى المعسكر B.
She seems like a humanoid robot.
إنها تبدو وكأنها روبوت يشبه الإنسان.
- When she was dancing. - Like AI.
- عندما كانت ترقص. - مثل الذكاء الاصطناعي.
Next is the remarks.
التالي هو الملاحظات.
For ALLDAY PROJECT's remarks, it says, "mixed-gender group."
بالنسبة لتعليقات ALLDAY PROJECT، تقول "مجموعة مختلطة الجنس".
Did you all know that you would be in a mixed-gender group?
هل تعلمون جميعًا أنكم ستكونون في مجموعة مختلطة بين الجنسين؟
- Or... - I'm sure they didn't.
- أو... - أنا متأكد من أنهم لم يفعلوا ذلك.
did you get to know as you met each member?
هل تعرفت عندما التقيت بكل عضو؟
TARZZAN always says this,
طرزان يقول هذا دائمًا،
but it was like collecting Infinity Stones.
ولكن كان الأمر مثل جمع Infinity Stones.
- Each member was added along. - They joined in.
- تمت إضافة كل عضو على طول. - لقد انضموا.
But you're not supposed to collect all of them.
لكن ليس من المفترض أن تجمعهم جميعًا.
- That's when the game ends. - Is that why?
- وذلك عندما تنتهي اللعبة. - هل هذا هو السبب؟
But these two...
لكن هذين...
- were already a team, - Yes.
- كنا بالفعل فريقا، - نعم.
and BAILEY and I were a team, right?
وبيلي وأنا كنا فريقًا، أليس كذلك؟
- No. - BAILEY...
- لا. - بيلي...
BAILEY and I were already a team.
أنا وبيلي كنا بالفعل فريقًا.
- You guys need to talk it out. - And then...
- يا رفاق بحاجة إلى التحدث بها. - وثم...
- I will explain. - You guys need a team dinner.
- سأشرح. - يا رفاق بحاجة إلى عشاء الفريق.
THEBLACKLABEL has female trainees...
لدى THEBLACKLABEL متدربات من الإناث...
- and male trainees, - Yes.
- والمتدربين الذكور، - نعم.
but we don't know each other.
لكننا لا نعرف بعضنا البعض.
- Sure. That's how it is. - We never come across each other.
- بالتأكيد. هذا هو الحال. - نحن لا نلتقي أبدا.
But one day, I got to work on a song...
لكن في أحد الأيام، بدأت العمل على أغنية...
with TARZZAN at the studio.
مع طرزان في الاستوديو.
But after we recorded the song,
لكن بعد أن سجلنا الأغنية،
TEDDY said, "It would be nice if you two were a group."
قال تيدي، "سيكون من الجميل أن تكونا مجموعة."
So I asked, "Us two?"
لذلك سألت: "نحن الاثنان؟"
"As a duo?"
"كثنائي؟"
And he said we should recruit more members.
وقال أنه يجب علينا تجنيد المزيد من الأعضاء.
So we added them one by one.
لذلك أضفناهم واحدًا تلو الآخر.
Why did TEDDY like it when you two recorded the song?
لماذا أعجب تيدي عندما قمتما بتسجيل الأغنية؟
- Well, we are the same age, - Yes.
- حسنًا، نحن في نفس العمر - نعم.
and the energy was different.
وكانت الطاقة مختلفة.
When we were together, people somehow...
عندما كنا معًا، كان الناس بطريقة ما...
felt scared.
شعرت بالخوف.
Really? We're scary?
حقًا؟ نحن مخيفون؟
- You're scary. I was so scared. - I was also scared, actually.
- أنت مخيف. كنت خائفة جدا. - كنت خائفة أيضا، في الواقع.
I'm not scary.
أنا لست مخيفا.
When you just said that, I got a bit scared.
عندما قلت ذلك للتو، شعرت بالخوف قليلاً.
ANNIE doesn't know.
آني لا تعرف.
ANNIE, you're the only one who doesn't know.
آني، أنت الوحيد الذي لا يعرف.
- You're the only one. - You're a bit scary.
- أنت الوحيد. - أنت مخيف بعض الشيء.
- To be honest... - When you see TARZZAN,
- لأكون صادقًا... - عندما ترى طرزان،
he does have a scary vibe.
لديه أجواء مخيفة.
- What? No. - How am I scary?
- ماذا؟ رقم - كيف أنا مخيف؟
- "How am I scary?" - No.
- "كيف أنا مخيف؟" - لا.
- He's not scary at all. - He makes you relax.
- إنه ليس مخيفًا على الإطلاق. - يجعلك تسترخي.
But even back in the day with Roo'Ra,
لكن حتى في ذلك اليوم مع روورا،
- there were mixed-gender groups. - Yes.
- كانت هناك مجموعات مختلطة بين الجنسين. - نعم.
- But they could be misunderstood. - There are pros and cons.
- ولكن يمكن أن يساء فهمها. - هناك إيجابيات وسلبيات.
Were there scandals between you and Ji Hyeon?
هل كانت هناك فضائح بينك وبين جي هيون؟
There were so many, saying that we were dating.
كان هناك الكثير يقولون أننا نتواعد.
There were tons of news stories.
كان هناك طن من القصص الإخبارية.
But we were fine,
لكننا كنا بخير
because we really didn't get along.
لأننا حقا لم نتفق.
- Yes. - Is that so?
- نعم. - هل هذا صحيح؟
It didn't cause any damage because it wasn't true.
لم يسبب أي ضرر لأنه لم يكن صحيحا.
And I even called her because I was outraged.
حتى أنني اتصلت بها لأنني كنت غاضبًا.
But the advantage of mixed-gender groups is that...
لكن ميزة المجموعات المختلطة بين الجنسين هي أن...
it broadens the musical spectrum when creating music.
فهو يوسع الطيف الموسيقي عند تأليف الموسيقى.
You have male vocals and female vocals,
عندك غناء رجالي وغناء نسائي
and also the male and female lyrics.
وكذلك كلمات الذكور والإناث.
I'm not joking about this,
أنا لا أمزح بشأن هذا،
and you're here today,
وأنت هنا اليوم،
but way before that, when you first had your debut,
ولكن قبل ذلك بوقت طويل، عندما ظهرت لأول مرة،
he mentioned you guys several times.
لقد ذكركم يا رفاق عدة مرات.
- "Did you see ALLDAY PROJECT?" - "Their songs are so good."
- "هل رأيت مشروع ALLDAY؟" - "أغانيهم جيدة جدًا."
It's true.
هذا صحيح.
As soon as your music came out,
بمجرد أن خرجت موسيقاك،
I had chills at home for a month.
لقد أصبت بقشعريرة في المنزل لمدة شهر.
So at your company,
لذلك في شركتك،
who was the first one to join within this team?
من كان أول من انضم إلى هذا الفريق؟
- Who trained the longest? - Who was picked first?
- من تدرب الأطول؟ - من تم اختياره أولاً؟
Did you all start together?
هل بدأتم جميعًا معًا؟
- Who came in first? - The two members born in 2002.
- من جاء أولاً؟ - العضوين مواليد 2002 .
- "The two members born in 2002?" - Born in 2002?
- "العضوين مواليد 2002؟" - مواليد 2002؟
- Who was born in 2002? - Try and guess.
- من مواليد 2002؟ - حاول وتخمين.
- Who looks the oldest? - How young does it get?
- من يبدو الأقدم؟ - كم هو صغير السن؟
- Up to 2005.
- حتى 2005. - حتى 2005.
We had our debut in 2005.
كان لدينا أول ظهور لنا في عام 2005.
Born in 2002? TARZZAN and ANNIE.
مواليد 2002 ؟ طرزان وآني.
(Were TARZZAN and ANNIE born in 2002?)
(هل ولد طرزان وآني في عام 2002؟)
- Really? - We must look old.
- حقًا؟ - يجب علينا أن ننظر القديمة.
- You want us to be wrong. - Yeong Cheol,
- تريد منا أن نكون مخطئين. - يونج تشيول،
- do I look that old? - Yes, do we look that old?
- هل أبدو بهذا العمر؟ - نعم، هل نبدو بهذا العمر؟
Hey, I was born in 1974.
ياخي انا مواليد 1974.
What do you mean, "look old?"
ماذا تقصد بـ "تبدو قديمة"؟
I was startled. I thought I messed up.
لقد أذهلت. اعتقدت أنني افسدت.
How old are you? Born in 2002?
كم عمرك؟ مواليد 2002؟
Is that 23 or 22?
هل هذا 23 أم 22؟
That was the funniest thing that ever came out...
كان ذلك أطرف شيء خرج على الإطلاق..
- of Yeong Cheol in 2025. - Wait.
- ليونج تشيول في عام 2025. - انتظر.
- The funniest. - I thought I messed up.
- أطرف. - اعتقدت أنني افسدت.
- That was the funniest. - Why can't I say that?
- كان ذلك أطرف. - لماذا لا أستطيع أن أقول ذلك؟
- That was funny. - YOUNGSEO...
- كان ذلك مضحكا. - يونغسيو...
- and WOOCHAN were born in 2005. - That's right.
- و ووشان ولدا في عام 2005. - هذا صحيح.
- Right? - And BAILEY was born in 2004.
- يمين؟ - وبيلي من مواليد 2004.
- You're smart. - TARZZAN...
- أنت ذكي. - طرزان...
and ANNIE were born in 2002.
وآني ولدا في عام 2002.
How old is that? 23?
كم عمر ذلك؟ 23؟
Are you 22 years old?
هل عمرك 22 سنة؟
I'm 52 years old.
عمري 52 سنة.
(Sorry)
(آسف)
I'm so much older.
أنا أكبر سناً بكثير.
That's funny.
هذا مضحك.
For the next one, it says, "New challenge."
بالنسبة للسؤال التالي، مكتوب عليه "التحدي الجديد".
Is that a new song?
هل تلك أغنية جديدة؟
A new challenge?
تحدي جديد؟
Our new song will be released on November 17.
سيتم إصدار أغنيتنا الجديدة في 17 نوفمبر.
(Two days after the show airs)
(بعد يومين من بث العرض)
It's right after the show airs.
إنه مباشرة بعد بث العرض.
Two days after the show airs,
بعد يومين من بث البرنامج
- our new song will be released. - I can't wait.
- سيتم إصدار أغنيتنا الجديدة. - لا استطيع الانتظار.
The title is "ONE MORE TIME."
العنوان هو "مرة أخرى."
To introduce the song...
للتعريف بالأغنية...
You can do it.
يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك.
With a delicate melody...
مع لحن رقيق...
Hey, we've all done this before.
مهلا، لقد فعلنا كل هذا من قبل.
- Right. I remember. - Yes, keep going.
- يمين. أتذكر. - نعم، استمر.
And a beat at a speed as if you were driving a fast car.
وتغلب بسرعة كما لو كنت تقود سيارة سريعة.
Those are the key points in this song.
هذه هي النقاط الرئيسية في هذه الأغنية.
So, will you show us this new song today?
فهل ستعرض لنا هذه الأغنية الجديدة اليوم؟
- Do you want to see it? - Let's go!
- هل تريد رؤيته؟ - دعنا نذهب!
A new song.
أغنية جديدة.
A brand new song.
أغنية جديدة تمامًا.
- "ONE MORE TIME."
- "مرة أخرى." - "مرة أخرى."
- For the first time on TV.
- لأول مرة على شاشة التلفزيون. - "مرة أخرى."
(New song, "ONE MORE TIME" by ALLDAY PROJECT)
(أغنية جديدة، "ONE MORE TIME" من إنتاج ALLDAY PROJECT)
(The members love the new concept as well.)
(الأعضاء يحبون المفهوم الجديد أيضًا.)
"ONE MORE TIME!"
"مرة أخرى!"
All right. Lastly,
حسنًا. أخيرا،
it's time to ask the transfer students...
حان الوقت لسؤال الطلاب المنقولين...
what we were most curious about.
ما كنا أكثر فضولًا بشأنه.
Question Aptitude Test.
اختبار القدرات السؤال.
- "Ask Me!" - Me!
- "اسألني!" - أنا!
I'll go first.
سأذهب أولا.
Okay, ALLDAY PROJECT.
حسنًا، مشروع طوال اليوم.
How did you feel when you first heard your group name?
ما هو شعورك عندما سمعت اسم مجموعتك لأول مرة؟
You mean whether they really liked it?
تقصد ما إذا كانوا حقا أحب ذلك؟
"Does this mean we'll only last a day?"
"هل هذا يعني أننا سنستمر ليوم واحد فقط؟"
"What if the project gets shut down later?"
"ماذا لو تم إغلاق المشروع لاحقًا؟"
Just to let you know, when we first heard Super Junior,
فقط لأعلمك، عندما سمعنا سوبر جونيور لأول مرة،
we really didn't like it.
نحن حقا لم نحب ذلك.
The TVXQ members came back to the dorm crying.
عاد أعضاء TVXQ إلى المسكن وهم يبكون.
- Honest... - At first, Men on a Mission was...
- صادق... - في البداية، كان رجال في مهمة...
- Honestly, how did you feel? - like that too.
- بصراحة كيف كان شعورك؟ - هكذا أيضًا.
To be honest, it wasn't on the list of names that we had come up with.
لأكون صادقًا، لم يكن هذا الاسم مدرجًا في قائمة الأسماء التي توصلنا إليها.
We're THEBLACKLABEL,
نحن ذا بلاك ليبل،
and as I mentioned earlier, we were Infinity Stone.
وكما ذكرت سابقًا، كنا إنفينيتي ستون.
So, we wondered, "What is the blackest black in the world?"
لذا، تساءلنا: "ما هو اللون الأسود الأكثر سوادًا في العالم؟"
"So, a black stone, maybe an onyx?"
"إذن، حجر أسود، ربما جزع؟"
We had lots of ideas like this.
كان لدينا الكثير من الأفكار مثل هذا.
At first, there was no like or dislike.
في البداية، لم يكن هناك إعجاب أو كراهية.
It was like, "What? ALLDAY PROJECT?"
كان الأمر مثل "ماذا؟ مشروع طوال اليوم؟"
"Wait, then will this be my group's name from now on?"
"انتظر، هل سيكون هذا اسم مجموعتي من الآن فصاعدا؟"
- Right. - I think it was more like that.
- يمين. - أعتقد أن الأمر كان أشبه بذلك.
From now on, it's like a tattoo you can't erase.
من الآن فصاعدا، سيكون مثل الوشم الذي لا يمكنك محوه.
- You can't erase it. - That's right.
- لا يمكنك محوها. - هذا صحيح.
Even if we liked it, we would've been worried...
حتى لو أحببنا ذلك لكنا قلقين..
and the same thing if we didn't like it.
ونفس الشيء إذا لم يعجبنا.
Did you perhaps rebel about it? "The name isn't that great."
هل ربما تمردت على ذلك؟ "الاسم ليس بهذه الروعة."
- I know. - But this name was...
- أنا أعرف. - ولكن هذا الاسم كان...
given to us by will.i.am.
قدمها لنا will.i.am.
- For real? - Who is that?
- لريال مدريد؟ - من ذاك؟
- So, - Black Eyed Peas.
- إذن - بلاك آيد بيز.
- I just felt like it would be good. - Oh, really?
- لقد شعرت أنه سيكون جيدا. - أوه حقًا؟
I thought we'd be a success.
اعتقدت أننا سنكون ناجحين.
- There was that energy. - The energy.
- كانت هناك تلك الطاقة. - الطاقة.
Beautiful and Handsome would be good too.
جميل ووسيم سيكون جيدًا أيضًا.
- Why was ALLDAY... - "Beautiful and Handsome?"
- لماذا كان كل يوم... - "جميل ووسيم؟"
- ALLDAY... - Beautiful and Handsome.
- طوال اليوم... - جميل ووسيم.
"Hello! Here is "FAMOUS" by Beautiful and Handsome!"
"مرحبًا! إليكم أغنية "FAMOUS" للجميلة والوسيم!"
Beautiful and Handsome.
جميلة و وسيم.
- I love it! - Beautiful and Handsome's TARZZAN!
- أنا أحبه! - طرزان الجميلة والوسيم!
- Beautiful and Handsome. - I love it too.
- جميل ووسيم. - أنا أحب ذلك أيضا.
Hey, WOOCHAN. I thought you taught him...
مرحبًا ووشان. اعتقدت أنك علمته ...
how to rap and write lyrics. What is that?
كيفية موسيقى الراب وكتابة كلمات الأغاني. ما هذا؟
Come on, Soo Geun.
هيا، سو جيون.
But he did have that kind of charm too.
لكنه كان يتمتع بهذا النوع من السحر أيضًا.
Okay, Sang Min.
حسنًا، سونغ مين.
- Nice. - ALLDAY...
- لطيف - جيد. - كل يوم...
By the way, when I came up with this question...
بالمناسبة عندما طرحت هذا السؤال..
(Next, it's Sang Min's question.)
(بعد ذلك، إنه سؤال سانغ مين.)
Think about this one. Where do you think you'll be in 31 years?
فكر في هذا. أين تعتقد أنك ستكون بعد 31 عاما؟
- That's because... - That's so specific.
- وهذا لأن... - هذا محدد جدًا.
it's been 31 years since I debuted as a mixed group.
لقد مرت 31 عامًا منذ ظهوري لأول مرة كفرقة مختلطة.
I think that's a good question.
أعتقد أن هذا سؤال جيد.
We've never talked about this topic as a group.
لم نتحدث أبدًا عن هذا الموضوع كمجموعة.
In 31 years, you'll be exactly my age, TARZZAN.
خلال 31 عامًا، ستكون بمثل عمري تمامًا يا طرزان.
Things suddenly got so solemn. That's so sad.
أصبحت الأمور فجأة مهيبة جدًا. هذا حزين جدا.
- It's so... - It got so sad.
- الأمر كذلك... - لقد أصبح الأمر حزينًا جدًا.
Yeong Cheol will be 80 by then!
سيبلغ يونغ تشول 80 عامًا بحلول ذلك الوقت!
I've always wanted to become someone like my dad.
لقد أردت دائمًا أن أصبح شخصًا مثل والدي.
Hey, that's pretty cool.
مهلا، هذا رائع.
There's just so much my dad has done for me that I'm grateful for.
هناك الكثير مما فعله والدي من أجلي وأنا ممتن له.
So, whenever people ask me what my dream is...
لذا، عندما يسألني الناس ما هو حلمي...
It's great to be rich and famous,
من الرائع أن تكون غنيًا ومشهورًا،
but I always say that I want to be someone like my dad.
لكنني أقول دائمًا أنني أريد أن أكون شخصًا مثل والدي.
That's cool.
هذا بارد.
I want to become a good dad like my dad.
أريد أن أصبح أبًا جيدًا مثل والدي.
If your dad hears this, he will be so happy.
إذا سمع والدك هذا، سيكون سعيدًا جدًا.
- Exactly... - I honestly just want to be happy.
- بالضبط... - أنا بصراحة أريد أن أكون سعيداً.
- That's true. - And this moment never returns.
- هذا صحيح. - وهذه اللحظة لا تعود أبداً.
- Right. - You're all our seniors,
- يمين. - أنتم جميع كبارنا،
so you reminisce about the past.
لذلك تتذكر الماضي.
But seeing that from a third person's point of view,
لكن رؤية ذلك من وجهة نظر شخص ثالث،
we are in the middle of that page right now.
نحن في منتصف تلك الصفحة الآن.
So, I just want to enjoy this moment even more.
لذا، أريد فقط الاستمتاع بهذه اللحظة أكثر.
That's impressive.
هذا مثير للإعجاب.
You guys are so popular and busy,
أنتم يا رفاق مشهورون جدًا ومشغولون،
and you've been on many variety shows.
ولقد شاركت في العديد من البرامج المتنوعة.
What do you think about Men on a Mission?
ما رأيك في الرجال في مهمة؟
Are there any issues based on being here today?
هل هناك أي مشاكل تعتمد على وجودك هنا اليوم؟
Based on what you've seen so far...
بناءً على ما رأيته حتى الآن..
- No, just tell us. Because... - That question is trash.
- لا، فقط أخبرنا. لأن... - هذا السؤال هو القمامة.
- I think there are lots of issues. - I want to hear...
- أعتقد أن هناك الكثير من القضايا. - أريد أن أسمع...
the sensible opinions of young people these days.
الآراء المعقولة للشباب هذه الأيام.
I'm sure you were very surprised by what you saw here.
أنا متأكد من أنك فوجئت جدًا بما رأيته هنا.
It looked like we were fighting at certain points.
بدا الأمر وكأننا كنا نقاتل في نقاط معينة.
- So, their thoughts as Gen Z? - Well, if there's anything...
- إذًا، أفكارهم كجيل Z؟ -حسنا إذا كان هناك أي شيء...
- you think we should change... - Be honest.
- تعتقد أننا يجب أن نتغير... - كن صادقا.
They might not have watched Men on a Mission.
ربما لم يشاهدوا رجال في مهمة.
I watched it.
لقد شاهدته.
I hope you call us back on the show. There aren't any issues.
آمل أن تتصل بنا مرة أخرى في العرض. لا توجد أية مشاكل.
- Gosh, thank you. - You want to come back?
- يا إلهي، شكرا لك. - هل تريد العودة؟
I think that's the biggest lie celebrities tell.
أعتقد أن هذه هي أكبر كذبة يقولها المشاهير.
You say, "Please invite me again," so when Men on a Mission calls...
أنت تقول، "من فضلك ادعوني مرة أخرى،" لذلك عندما يتصل رجال في مهمة...
"Hi, ANNIE. This is Men on a Mission." Then, you go...
"مرحبًا آني. هؤلاء رجال في مهمة." ثم تذهب...
(Hang up!)
(يشنق!)
- No. - "Say that I'm abroad!"
- لا. - "قل أنني في الخارج!"
That's what they do.
هذا ما يفعلونه.
That breaks my heart so much.
هذا يكسر قلبي كثيرا.
But honestly, all of us...
لكن بصراحة كلنا..
being on a show together as a group of five...
أن نكون في عرض معًا كمجموعة من خمسة...
and doing something...
وفعل شيء...
- Is it your 1st time? - It's almost the 1st time.
- هل هذه هي المرة الأولى لك؟ - إنها المرة الأولى تقريبًا.
- You were all split up. - In a studio...
- لقد انفصلتم جميعًا. - في الاستوديو...
So, we were really worried.
لذلك، كنا قلقين حقًا.
But is it going better than you thought?
ولكن هل تسير الأمور بشكل أفضل مما كنت تعتقد؟
Or is it not going as well as you imagined?
أم أن الأمر لا يسير كما تصورت؟
It's so hard.
انه من الصعب جدا.
I don't think there's such a thing as doing well or not.
لا أعتقد أن هناك شيئًا اسمه القيام بعمل جيد أم لا.
This is just the way we are.
هذه هي الطريقة التي نحن عليها.
- TARZZAN. - TARZZAN is a great speaker.
- طرزان. - طرزان متحدث عظيم.
I'll keep this momentum going...
سأواصل هذا الزخم..
- and give you my question! - Let's go, Ho Dong!
- وأعطيك سؤالي! - دعنا نذهب، هو دونغ!
Like TARZZAN said, I just have to ask my question...
كما قال طرزان، علي فقط أن أطرح سؤالي...
- as who I am. - Let's go.
- كما أنا. - دعنا نذهب.
I just have to ask a sincere question from the heart.
أود فقط أن أطرح سؤالاً صادقًا من القلب.
- That's right. - Hurry up.
- هذا صحيح. - أسرع.
Don't try to play tricks.
لا تحاول أن تلعب الحيل.
- Hurry so we can let the kids go! - Goodness, seriously.
- اسرع حتى نتمكن من السماح للأطفال بالذهاب! - الخير بجدية.
Answer right away. Answer me honestly.
أجب على الفور. أجبني بصراحة.
- Got it, TARZZAN? - Got it.
- فهمت يا طرزان؟ - فهمتها.
Got it, YOUNGSEO? Got it, WOOCHAN?
فهمت، يونجسيو؟ فهمت، ووشان؟
- His card isn't even open. - You guys.
- بطاقته ليست مفتوحة حتى. - يا رفاق.
Have you been to ANNIE's house?
هل ذهبت إلى منزل آني؟
(Have you been to ANNIE's house?)
(هل زرت منزل آني؟)
- Good one. - That's trash!
- فكرة جيدة. - هذه القمامة!
It's totally trash.
إنها قمامة تمامًا.
Aren't you curious?
ألا تشعر بالفضول؟
- Hey! Aren't you curious about... - So trashy!
- يا! ألا تشعر بالفضول بشأن... - تافه جدًا!
- what she eats at home? - It's so trashy.
- ماذا تأكل في المنزل؟ - إنها تافهة جدًا.
- So trashy. - Hey.
- تافه جدا. - يا.
I agree.
أنا موافق.
- You're curious, aren't you? - Yes, it was so funny.
- أنت فضولي، أليس كذلك؟ - نعم، كان مضحكا جدا.
- I asked the same question. - We went there before the office.
- سألت نفس السؤال. - ذهبنا إلى هناك قبل المكتب.
I'm really curious.
أنا فضولي حقا.
- You're curious, aren't you? - Have you guys been there?
- أنت فضولي، أليس كذلك؟ - هل كنتم هناك يا رفاق؟
You've been there?
لقد كنت هناك؟
- We have. - And what...
- لدينا. - وماذا...
- They just come and go... - We all go...
- إنهم يأتون ويذهبون... - كلنا نذهب...
- as if it was their own place. - and make ramyeon.
- كما لو كان مكانهم. - وصنع الراميون.
- All of them? - They just come and go.
- كلهم؟ - إنهم يأتون ويذهبون فقط.
- Oh, really? - She said they had ramyeon.
- أوه حقًا؟ - قالت أن لديهم الراميون.
We all go, and TARZZAN made Chapagetti.
ذهبنا جميعًا، وقام طرزان بإعداد الشاباجيتي.
- Oh, really? - and he made Buldak ramyeon.
- أوه حقًا؟ - وصنع بولداك الراميون.
My parents tell me...
والدي يقول لي...
that it feels like our house has become the clubhouse.
أنه يبدو وكأن منزلنا أصبح النادي.
- Oh, dear. - Well, that's because...
- يا عزيزي. - حسنًا، هذا لأن...
First of all, it's the closest to the office.
أولا وقبل كل شيء، إنه الأقرب إلى المكتب.
I see.
أرى.
It's right on the route for us to stop by after work.
إنه على الطريق الصحيح بالنسبة لنا للتوقف بعد العمل.
But can anyone just go there...
ولكن هل يمكن لأي شخص أن يذهب إلى هناك؟
Well, they're not just anyone. They're your friends.
حسنًا، إنهم ليسوا مجرد أي شخص. إنهم أصدقاؤك.
- They're not just anyone. - Yes, well...
- إنهم ليسوا مجرد أي شخص. - نعم حسناً...
- Hey, what are you thinking? - No, I'm sorry.
- مهلا، في ماذا تفكر؟ - لا، أنا آسف.
- I'm sorry. Then... Gosh, sorry. - Jang Hoon.
- أنا آسف. ثم... يا إلهي، آسف. - جانج هون.
- It's because he wants to go.
- لأنه يريد الذهاب. - جانج هون.
- Then, we... - We're considered just anyone.
- ثم، نحن... - نحن نعتبر مجرد أي شخص.
- Can anyone like us go... - Why are you saying "us?"
- هل يمكن لأي شخص مثلنا أن يذهب... - لماذا تقول "نحن؟"
- and eat ramyeon there too? - Leave us out of it.
- وأكل الراميون هناك أيضا؟ - اتركونا منه.
- Jang Hoon... - They'll ask for your name...
-جانغ هون... -سوف يسألون عن اسمك...
- if you try to come in. - Right.
- إذا حاولت الدخول. - صحيح.
TARZZAN, what else was there besides ramyeon?
طرزان، ماذا كان هناك غير الراميون؟
When I went there, I just had a bowl of ramyeon,
عندما ذهبت إلى هناك، تناولت للتو وعاء من الراميون،
but I had to leave early for practice.
ولكن كان علي أن أغادر مبكراً للتدريب.
I just got to look around for a bit, and I said,
كان علي أن أنظر حولي قليلاً، وقلت،
"Gosh, this is awesome."
"يا إلهي، هذا رائع."
- "This is awesome." - Didn't they have any fruit...
- "هذا رائع." -أليس لديهم أي فاكهة...
that looked fascinating?
التي تبدو رائعة؟
- Hey. - Still,
- يا. - ما زال،
Jang Hoon could go to ANNIE's house.
يمكن لجانغ هون الذهاب إلى منزل آني.
He can't come to my house because the ceiling is too low.
لا يمكنه القدوم إلى منزلي لأن السقف منخفض جدًا.
You must have high ceilings, though.
يجب أن يكون لديك سقوف عالية، رغم ذلك.
It was high even for Jang Hoon.
لقد كانت عالية حتى بالنسبة لجانغ هون.
- My gosh. - All right.
- يا إلهي. - حسنًا.
You could go in even if Ha Seung Jin carries you on his shoulders.
يمكنك الدخول حتى لو حملك ها سونغ جين على كتفيه.
So, if you get the chance, please invite us.
لذا، إذا حصلت على الفرصة، يرجى دعوتنا.
We'll leave right after eating ramyeon too.
سنغادر مباشرة بعد تناول الراميون أيضًا.
- We won't do anything else. - We'll eat cup noodles.
- لن نفعل أي شيء آخر. - سوف نأكل كوب المعكرونة.
No need to cook anything. We can have cup noodles.
لا حاجة لطهي أي شيء. يمكننا تناول كوب من المعكرونة.
Don't do that. ANNIE.
لا تفعل ذلك. آني.
If you have to cook ramyeon, it's a chore to have to do dishes.
إذا كان عليك طهي الراميون، فمن العمل الرتيب أن تقوم بغسل الأطباق.
Just some cold water is fine.
فقط بعض الماء البارد جيد.
If you could take just three people from here,
إذا أمكنك أخذ ثلاثة أشخاص فقط من هنا،
- who would you invite? - Three people?
- من ستدعو؟ - ثلاثة أشخاص؟
- Just 3 people. - Yes, just 3.
- 3 أشخاص فقط. - نعم 3 فقط .
- "You guys can come." - Just three of us to your house.
- "يا رفاق يمكن أن تأتي." - ثلاثة فقط منا إلى منزلك.
(Nervous)
(متوتر)
(If I were to invite the brothers...)
(إذا كنت سأدعو الإخوة ...)
He can't come to my house because the ceiling is too low.
لا يمكنه القدوم إلى منزلي لأن السقف منخفض جدًا.
No need to cook anything. We can have cup noodles.
لا حاجة لطهي أي شيء. يمكننا تناول كوب من المعكرونة.
(Which 3 will get invitations to ANNIE's house?)
(أي ثلاثة سوف يحصلون على دعوات لمنزل آني؟)
As soon as your music came out,
بمجرد أن خرجت موسيقاك،
I had chills at home for a month.
لقد أصبت بقشعريرة في المنزل لمدة شهر.
Well...
حسنًا...
First, Ho Dong.
أولا، هو دونغ.
- Nice. - Oh, for side dishes.
- لطيف - جيد. - أوه، للأطباق الجانبية.
He'll get to try good side dishes.
سوف يجرب الأطباق الجانبية الجيدة.
- I'm all set. - And?
- أنا جاهز. - و؟
I told you.
أخبرتك.
And Jang Hoon.
وجانغ هون.
- The last one! - Let's go.
- الأخير! - دعنا نذهب.
- Let's go together. - One last person.
- دعونا نذهب معا. - شخص أخير.
- Let's go. - I knew it.
- دعنا نذهب. - كنت أعرف.
- Shin Dong. - Me?
- شين دونغ. - أنا؟
- Shin Dong? - What's going on?
- شين دونغ؟ - ماذا يحدث هنا؟
(Ho Dong, Jang Hoon, and Shin Dong are chosen as the elite 3.)
(تم اختيار هو دونغ وجانغ هون وشين دونغ ليكونوا النخبة 3.)
- All right. Let's go. - I think...
- حسنًا. دعنا نذهب. - أظن...
they'll be in charge of eating up all the leftovers.
سيكونون مسؤولين عن تناول كل بقايا الطعام.
(Here comes the leftover clean-up crew!)
(هنا يأتي طاقم التنظيف المتبقي!)
- They'll eat up all the leftovers. - We'll only eat ramyeon.
- سوف يأكلون كل بقايا الطعام. - سوف نأكل الراميون فقط.
(Today's leftover clean-up crew with bright faces)
(بقايا طاقم التنظيف اليوم بوجوه مشرقة)
- Hey, three boxes of ramyeon... - Aren't you happy?
- مهلا، ثلاثة صناديق من الراميون... - ألست سعيدا؟
All we need is some rameyon.
كل ما نحتاجه هو بعض الراميون.
- Excuse me. - Do you have...
- اعذرني. - هل لديك...
- So, - lots of ramyeon at home?
- إذًا - الكثير من الراميون في المنزل؟
- the security guards... - Yes.
- حراس الأمن... - نعم.
- We received permission. - Yes, we received permission.
- لقد حصلنا على إذن. - نعم، لقد حصلنا على إذن.
If we come by later,
إذا جئنا في وقت لاحق،
you can't tell us to leave, okay?
لا يمكنك أن تطلب منا المغادرة، حسنًا؟
We received permission.
لقد حصلنا على إذن.
- How come it's those three? - We're here to eat ramyeon.
- كيف يحدث هؤلاء الثلاثة؟ - نحن هنا لتناول الراميون.
These three can go.
هؤلاء الثلاثة يمكن أن يذهبوا.
- The three of us have permission. - Oh, nice.
- نحن الثلاثة لدينا إذن. - أوه، لطيف.
- The leftover clean-up crew. - But why is it Shin Dong?
- بقايا طاقم التنظيف. - ولكن لماذا هو شين دونغ؟
- I know. Why was I the last one? - Ever since I was little,
- أنا أعرف. لماذا كنت الأخير؟ - منذ أن كنت صغيراً،
- I was a huge fan. - Really?
- كنت من أشد المعجبين. - حقًا؟
I loved Super Junior so much.
لقد أحببت سوبر جونيور كثيرًا.
I used to only watch Shin Dong's videos.
كنت أشاهد فيديوهات شين دونغ فقط.
- Really? - Yes.
- حقًا؟ - نعم.
Thank you. I'll come over.
شكرًا لك. سوف آتي.
- Guys with bigger builds. - That's right.
- الرجال ذوي البنيات الأكبر. - هذا صحيح.
- Right. We have that in common. - The three of us.
- يمين. لدينا هذا المشترك. - نحن الثلاثة.
- That's right. - You know?
- هذا صحيح. - أنت تعرف؟
It's clear that ANNIE doesn't care about looks.
من الواضح أن آني لا تهتم بالمظهر.
- I do care about looks! - Her taste is like a foreigner's.
- أنا أهتم بالمظهر! - ذوقها مثل ذوق الأجنبي.
- No, you didn't care at all. - I totally care about looks.
- لا، لم تهتمي على الإطلاق. - أهتم بالمظهر تماماً.
Because we're the ones who seem relaxed.
لأننا نحن الذين نبدو مرتاحين.
- That's right. - Shin Dong, let's go...
- هذا صحيح. - شين دونغ، دعنا نذهب...
- and clean up all the leftovers. - Okay.
- وتنظيف جميع بقايا الطعام. - تمام.
- They'll take care of it. - Nice and clean.
- سوف يعتنون بالأمر. - جميلة ونظيفة.
We'll clean everything up.
سنقوم بتنظيف كل شيء.
- Don't leave anything. - I'll ask my question last.
- لا تترك شيئا. - سأطرح سؤالي أخيرا.
Have you guys perhaps received your first paychecks?
هل ربما استلمتم يا رفاق راتبكم الأول؟
- No, not yet. - Not yet.
- لا، ليس بعد. - ليس بعد.
Then, when you get your first paycheck,
وبعد ذلك، عندما تحصل على راتبك الأول،
is there something you want to splurge on?
هل هناك شيء تريد أن تتفاخر به؟
- A car? - Oh, really?
- سيارة؟ - أوه حقًا؟
- A car.
- سيارة؟ - سيارة.
- What kind of car?
- سيارة. - أي نوع من السيارة؟
- Which one? - I don't know.
- أيها؟ - لا أعرف.
- An SUV? - Just a car.
- سيارة دفع رباعي؟ - مجرد سيارة.
- A sports car? - A sports car.
- سيارة رياضية؟ - سيارة رياضية .
- What about you guys? - For my parents,
- ماذا عنكم يا رفاق؟ - لوالدي،
I want to buy them a house in Seoul.
أريد أن أشتري لهم منزلاً في سيول.
Then, we can live together.
وبعد ذلك، يمكننا أن نعيش معا.
- I'm sorry, but... - For your first paycheck...
- أنا آسف، ولكن... - من أجل راتبك الأول...
- Your 1st paycheck... - With your 1st paycheck?
- راتبك الأول... - مع راتبك الأول؟
Hey, these days...
هاه هذه الأيام...
- Can you buy a house in Seoul? - Houses are expensive in Seoul.
- هل يمكنك شراء منزل في سيول؟ - المنازل باهظة الثمن في سيول.
He can dream.
يمكنه أن يحلم.
- Maybe they earned that much. - I'll pay the monthly rent.
- ربما كسبوا هذا القدر. - سأدفع الإيجار الشهري.
- The monthly rent. - The first payment.
- الإيجار الشهري . - الدفعة الأولى.
- The key deposit. - I can pay the key deposit...
- إيداع المفتاح. - أستطيع أن أدفع وديعة المفتاح...
- and monthly rent. - You'll earn the key deposit.
- والإيجار الشهري. - سوف تكسب إيداع المفتاح.
Make the deposit with your first payment.
قم بالإيداع مع الدفعة الأولى.
- That'll do. - YOUNGSEO.
- هذا سوف يفعل. - يونجسيو.
To me, the definition of success...
بالنسبة لي تعريف النجاح...
is having the means to take care of a cat.
هو امتلاك الوسائل اللازمة لرعاية قطة.
- I want to have the means... - That's a good mindset.
- أريد أن أملك الوسائل... - هذه عقلية جيدة.
to take proper care of a cat...
للعناية الصحيحة بالقطط..
- at home. - You resemble a cat.
- في البيت. - أنت تشبه القطة.
I also want to repay my parents first.
أريد أيضًا أن أسدد دين والدي أولاً.
Ever since I was little,
منذ أن كنت صغيراً،
my mom has been my manager.
كانت أمي مديرتي.
- Your manager.
- مديرك. - مديرك.
She's like my friend.
إنها مثل صديقي.
- How nice. - We've spent so much time together.
- كم هو لطيف. - لقد أمضينا الكثير من الوقت معًا.
That's why I want to repay her.
لهذا السبب أريد أن أسدد لها.
After all, it's the first payment.
بعد كل شيء، إنها الدفعة الأولى.
- That's right. - So I want to do that.
- هذا صحيح. - لذلك أريد أن أفعل ذلك.
- You'll earn a lot. - Treat Soo Geun to a meal sometime.
- سوف تكسب الكثير. - كافئ Soo Geun بتناول وجبة في وقت ما.
(A meal to celebrate their making up)
(وجبة للاحتفال بمكياجهم)
ANNIE, why don't you use...
آني، لماذا لا تستخدمين...
your first payment...
الدفعة الأولى لك...
to buy your parents underclothes?
لشراء الملابس الداخلية لوالديك؟
- That's right. - That's too old-fashioned.
- هذا صحيح. - وهذا من الطراز القديم جدا.
- But traditionally... - I did mention it to them,
- ولكن تقليديا... - لقد ذكرت لهم ذلك،
- Did you? - but they didn't want underclothes.
- هل؟ - لكنهم لا يريدون الملابس الداخلية.
- What do they want? - Really?
- ماذا يريدون؟ - حقًا؟
- They want something else. - Gosh, your parents...
- يريدون شيئا آخر. - يا إلهي والديك..
I don't know. I had a similar idea.
لا أعرف. كان لدي فكرة مماثلة.
But what I want...
لكن ما أريد...
is similar to YOUNGSEO's answer.
يشبه إجابة YOUNGSEO.
- I see. - An animal?
- أرى. - حيوان؟
- I want more dogs. - Puppies.
- أريد المزيد من الكلاب. - الجراء.
- You want a dog.
- الجراء. - تريد كلباً.
I currently have two dogs,
حاليا عندي كلبين
- but I want more. - Do you want more?
- ولكن أريد المزيد. - هل تريد المزيد؟
Do you like big dogs? What kind of dogs do you like?
هل تحب الكلاب الكبيرة؟ أي نوع من الكلاب تحب؟
Big dogs are nice.
الكلاب الكبيرة لطيفة.
But if I'm raising a dog with my own money,
لكن إذا كنت أقوم بتربية كلب بأموالي الخاصة،
I want a dachshund.
أريد كلب ألماني.
I want a dachshund and a Great Dane.
أريد كلبًا ألمانيًا ودانماركيًا عظيمًا.
- I also want an Akita. - You really like dogs.
- أريد أيضا اكيتا. - أنت حقا تحب الكلاب.
You wanted the three of them instead of dogs, right?
لقد أردت الثلاثة بدلاً من الكلاب، أليس كذلك؟
- I get it now. - Yes.
- فهمت الآن. - نعم.
- Who is which breed? - I get it now.
- من هو الذي تولد؟ - فهمت الآن.
- I see.
- من هو الذي تولد؟ - أرى.
- It's her taste. - Let's go.
- إنها ذوقها. - دعنا نذهب.
Am I the dachshund?
هل أنا الكلب الألماني؟
(The trio was invited due to a clear reason.)
(تمت دعوة الثلاثي لسبب واضح.)
- I must be the Great Dane. - He's the Great Dane.
- يجب أن أكون الدانماركي العظيم. - إنه الدانماركي العظيم.
I'm the Great Dane.
أنا الدانماركي العظيم.
A round of applause.
جولة من التصفيق.
(Variety Show Game Club with ALLDAY PROJECT)
(نادي ألعاب Variety Show مع مشروع ALLDAY)
All right. Finally,
حسنًا. أخيراً،
Variety Show Game Club...
نادي الألعاب المتنوعة...
got new members.
حصلت على أعضاء جدد.
(New members joined.)
(انضم أعضاء جدد.)
Welcome.
مرحباً.
In this club, the variety show rookies...
في هذا النادي، مجموعة متنوعة تظهر الناشئين...
will learn the games they'll play when they appear on variety shows...
سيتعلمون الألعاب التي سيلعبونها عندما يظهرون في البرامج المتنوعة...
to improve their gaming skills...
لتحسين مهاراتهم في اللعب..
and learn some fun reactions.
وتعلم بعض ردود الفعل الممتعة.
It's a must-attend club for the variety show rookies.
إنه نادي يجب حضوره للمبتدئين في البرامج المتنوعة.
All right. This club...
حسنًا. هذا النادي...
is a lot of money for the operating expenses. Thus,
هو الكثير من المال لتغطية نفقات التشغيل. هكذا،
each game comes with tasty snacks.
تأتي كل لعبة مع وجبات خفيفة لذيذة.
So everyone should work hard.
لذا يجب على الجميع أن يعملوا بجد.
- This is great. - Let's go.
- هذا عظيم. - دعنا نذهب.
- It'll be a match... - The snacks will be tasty.
- ستكون مباراة... - الوجبات الخفيفة ستكون لذيذة.
between the old and new members.
بين الأعضاء القدامى والجدد.
- Do you want to join them? - Here comes the first game.
- هل تريد الانضمام إليهم؟ - هنا تأتي المباراة الأولى.
The first game is popular among Gen Zers these days.
تحظى اللعبة الأولى بشعبية كبيرة بين أجيال Zers هذه الأيام.
It's the Bbans Game.
إنها لعبة Bbans.
- Like underwear? - Bbans Game?
- مثل الملابس الداخلية؟ - لعبة ببانس؟
- Bbans Game. - Time out.
- لعبة ببانس. - نفذ الوقت.
- Bbans? - What?
- ببانس؟ - ماذا؟
- Bbans. - Time out.
- ببانس. - نفذ الوقت.
- Let me explain. - Please explain.
- اسمحوا لي أن أشرح. - يرجى التوضيح.
- Firstly, you need a nickname. - Okay.
- أولا، أنت بحاجة إلى لقب. - تمام.
You combine the first syllable of your name and "Bban."
يمكنك الجمع بين المقطع الأول من اسمك و"Bban".
For example, Ho Dong will be...
على سبيل المثال، سيكون هو دونغ...
- Ho Bban.
- هو ببان. - هو ببان.
- It's trendy. Ho Bban.
- إنها عصرية. هو ببان. - هو ببان.
- Then... - That's right.
- إذن... - هذا صحيح.
Is she AN Bban?
هي الببان؟
- That's right. AN Bban. - AN Bban.
- هذا صحيح. الببان. - الببان.
AN Bban, WOO Bban, YOUNG Bban, TAR Bban, and BAI Bban.
AN Bban، WOO Bban، YOUNG Bban، TAR Bban، وBAI Bban.
- Yes. BAI Bban. - It's similar to I Am Ground.
- نعم. باي ببان. - إنه مشابه لـ أنا أرضي.
But if you go, "Yeong Cheol, three."
ولكن إذا قلت، "يونغ تشول، ثلاثة".
Yeong Cheol, Yeong Cheol, Yeong Cheol, Yeong Cheol.
يونج تشيول، يونج تشيول، يونج تشيول، يونج تشيول.
You change the tone for the third one.
قمت بتغيير النغمة للثالثة.
- You must say it four times. - Yeong Cheol.
- يجب أن تقول ذلك أربع مرات. - يونج تشيول.
WOO Bban, four.
WOOO بان، الفراء.
WOO Bban, WOO Bban, WOO Bban, WOO Bban.
وو بان، ووو بان، ووو.
- There you go. - For goodness' sake.
- ها أنت ذا. - في سبيل الخير.
- Let's go. - Jang Bban, Jang Bban, Jang...
- دعنا نذهب. -جانغ بابان، جانج بابان، جانج...
- It's harder than you think. - Jang Bban, Jang Bban, Jang Bban.
- الأمر أصعب مما تعتقد. - جانغ بابان، جانج بابان، جانج بابان.
- You need to stay alert. - Let's go.
- عليك أن تبقى في حالة تأهب. - دعنا نذهب.
Five, six, seven, eight.
خمسة، ستة، سبعة، ثمانية.
- Bban, Bban, Bbans Game - Bban, Bban, Bbans Game
- Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans - Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans
Begin the self-introduction
ابدأ بالتعريف عن نفسك
I'm Chris Bban.
أنا كريس بان.
I'm BAI Bban.
أنا باي ببان.
I'm TAR Bban.
أنا تار ببان.
I'm YOUNG Bban.
أنا شاب ببان.
I'm WOO Bban.
أنا في WOO B.
- I'm AN Bban. - There you go.
- أنا أن ببان. - ها أنت ذا.
I'm Hee Bban.
أنا هي ببان.
I'm Soo Bban.
أنا سو ببان.
I'm Cheol Bban.
أنا تشيول ببان.
I'm Kyung Bban.
أنا كيونغ ببان.
I'm Sang Bban.
أنا سانغ ببان.
I'm Jang Bban.
أنا جانغ ببان.
I'm Ho Bban.
أنا هو ببان.
- Let's begin. - What?
- لنبدأ. - ماذا؟
Bban, Bban, Bbans Game
لعبة Bban، Bban، Bbans
- Bban, Bban, Bbans Game - Bban, Bban, Bbans Game
- Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans - Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans
- Let's begin - How do you do it?
- لنبدأ - كيف تفعل ذلك؟
- It'll be hard. - Sang Bban, two.
- سيكون من الصعب. - سانغ ببان، اثنان.
Sang Bban, Sang Bban, Sang Bban, Sang Bban.
سانغ ببان، سانغ ببان، سانغ ببان، سانغ ببان.
TAR Bban, three.
تار ببان، ثلاثة.
TAR Bban, TAR Bban, TAR Bban, TAR Bban.
احصل على BBAN، احصل على BBAN، احصل على BBAN، احصل على BBAN.
He's good.
انه جيد.
Jang Bban, two.
جانج ببان، اثنان.
Jang Bban, Jang Bban, Jang... What?
جانغ ببان، جانغ ببان، جانغ... ماذا؟
You're out.
أنت خارج.
- He's so bad at it. - Jang...
- انه سيء ​​للغاية في ذلك. - جانج...
- Focus.
- ركز. - جانج...
- Jang Bban, Jang Bban... - Jang Bban, Jang Bban.
- جانج بابان، جانج بابان... - جانج بابان، جانج بابان.
- Jang Bban is out.
- جانغ بيبان خارج. - جانغ بيبان خارج.
- Take a step back. - It's hard.
- خذ خطوة إلى الوراء. - إنه صعب.
- Let's do this.
- دعونا نفعل هذا. - دعونا نفعل هذا.
Let's go. Since TAR Bban succeeded in attacking,
دعنا نذهب. منذ أن نجح TAR Bban في الهجوم،
he'll begin.
سيبدأ.
- Bban, Bban, Bbans Game - Bban, Bban, Bbans Game
- Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans - Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans
Soo Bban, two.
سو ببان، اثنان.
- Soo Bban, Soo... - Incorrect.
- سوو ببان، سو... - غير صحيح.
(He missed a beat.)
(لقد غاب عن الفوز.)
Hey, why did you look that way?
مهلا، لماذا نظرت بهذه الطريقة؟
- Why did you do that? - It was a feint.
- لماذا فعلت ذلك؟ - لقد كانت خدعة.
- He looked that way. - It was a timed attack.
- بدا بهذه الطريقة. - لقد كان هجوما موقوتا.
It was a bluff.
لقد كانت خدعة.
He looked that way,
كان ينظر بهذه الطريقة،
- so I didn't think it was my turn. - Right.
- لذلك لم أعتقد أنه جاء دوري. - يمين.
That Bban is too strong.
أن Bban قوي جدا.
My goodness.
يا إلهي.
It's because I'm like Tarzan.
هذا لأنني مثل طرزان.
- I see. - I get it.
- أرى. - أحصل عليه.
TAR Bban is doing great.
TAR Bban يقوم بعمل رائع.
- Bban, Bban, Bbans Game - Bban, Bban, Bbans Game
- Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans - Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans
Hee Bban, three.
يا ببان، ثلاثة.
Hee Bban, Hee Bban, Hee Bban, Hee Bban.
هيي بيبان، هيي بيبان، هيي بيبان، هيي بيبان.
(Impressed)
(معجب)
AN Bban, four.
أن ببان، أربعة.
AN Bban, AN Bban, AN Bban, AN Bban.
الببان، الببان، الببان، الببان.
AN Bban, three.
أن ببان، ثلاثة.
(She defended well and attacked herself.)
(لقد دافعت جيدًا وهاجمت نفسها).
- She's good. - Is she my teammate?
- إنها جيدة. - هل هي زميلتي في الفريق؟
- You just needed to do it. - She's my teammate.
- كنت بحاجة فقط للقيام بذلك. - إنها زميلتي في الفريق.
- What was that? - ANNIE.
- ماذا كان هذا؟ - آني.
- It's too late. - You just needed to do it.
- لقد فات الأوان. - كنت بحاجة فقط للقيام بذلك.
You should've done it.
كان ينبغي عليك فعل ذلك.
You should've done it right away.
كان يجب أن تفعل ذلك على الفور.
Do you know what's funny?
هل تعرف ما هو المضحك؟
She looked around and said her own nickname.
نظرت حولها وقالت لقبها الخاص.
(She defended herself against Hee Chul's attack.)
(دافعت عن نفسها ضد هجوم هي تشول.)
(Whom should I attack?)
(من يجب أن أهاجم؟)
(She attacked herself.)
(هاجمت نفسها.)
- Isn't AN Bban a liar? - Why not?
- أليس أن ببان كاذبا؟ - ولم لا؟
She said she had a good short-term memory.
وقالت إن لديها ذاكرة جيدة على المدى القصير.
She heard everyone's nickname.
سمعت لقب الجميع.
(I have a very good short-term memory.)
(لدي ذاكرة جيدة جدًا على المدى القصير.)
(I see.)
(أرى.)
She heard everyone's nickname.
سمعت لقب الجميع.
Why did she say her own?
لماذا قالت بنفسها؟
- AN Bban. - Seriously.
- الببان. - بجد.
What about the Ivy League?
ماذا عن رابطة اللبلاب؟
- What about the Ivy League? - AN Bban.
- ماذا عن رابطة اللبلاب؟ - ان ببان.
- Please take a seat.
- من فضلك اجلس. - الببان.
- I'm so sad. - All right.
- أنا حزين جدا. - حسنًا.
- Bban, Bban, Bbans Game - Bban, Bban, Bbans Game
- Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans - Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans
BAI Bban, two.
باي ببان، اثنان.
BAI Bban, BAI Bban, BAI Bban, BAI Bban.
باي ببان، باي ببان، باي ببان، باي ببان.
Good.
جيد.
Ho Bban, two.
هو ببان، اثنان.
Ho Bban, Ho Bban, Ho Bban, Ho Bban.
هو ببان، هو ببان، هو ببان، هو ببان.
WOOCHAN, bang.
ووشان، فرقعة.
- What? - That's...
- ماذا؟ - هذا...
I can't go on. He said, "WOOCHAN, bang."
لا أستطيع الاستمرار. قال: "ووتشان، فرقعة."
What even was "WOOCHAN, bang?"
ما هو حتى "WOOCHAN، فرقعة؟"
- "WOOCHAN, bang." - Bang, bang!
- "ووتشان، أخي." - بانغ، بانغ!
Why did you shoot at WOOCHAN?
لماذا أطلقت النار على WOOCHAN؟
- What even was "WOOCHAN, bang?" - I can't go on.
- ما هو حتى "WOOCHAN، فرقعة؟" - لا أستطيع الاستمرار.
Is he a criminal?
هل هو مجرم؟
- Why did you shoot at WOOCHAN? - He got shot at.
- لماذا أطلقت النار على WOOCHAN؟ - تم إطلاق النار عليه.
- Did you say it as "Bread?" - I mean...
- هل قلت ذلك باسم "الخبز؟" - أعني...
WOOCHAN, bang.
ووشان، فرقعة.
- My goodness. - I'm sorry,
- يا إلهي. - أنا آسف،
but I thought he said, "Take off your top."
لكنني اعتقدت أنه قال: "اخلع قميصك".
I thought he said, "Take off your top."
اعتقدت أنه قال: "اخلع قميصك".
- "Take off your top."
- "اخلع قميصك." - "اخلع قميصك."
- Then you should've done this. - My eyes were on WOOCHAN.
- ثم كان ينبغي عليك أن تفعل هذا. - كانت عيني على ووشان.
How many times was he supposed to do that?
كم مرة كان من المفترض أن يفعل ذلك؟
- I'm sorry. - Hurry up.
- أنا آسف. - أسرع.
- Attacking is hard too. - My eyes were on WOOCHAN.
- الهجوم صعب أيضاً. - كانت عيني على ووشان.
- Step back. - Attacking is hard too.
- التراجع. - الهجوم صعب أيضاً.
All right. BAI Bban's attack was successful,
حسنًا. كان هجوم BAI Bban ناجحًا،
- so she'll go first. - BAI Bban is good.
- لذلك سوف تذهب أولا. - باي ببان جيد.
- Let's go. Three, four. - BAI Bban.
- دعنا نذهب. ثلاثة، أربعة. - باي ببان.
- Bban, Bban, Bbans Game - Bban, Bban, Bbans Game
- Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans - Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans
WOO Bban, four.
WOOO بان، الفراء.
- WOO Bban, WOO Bban. - Don't attack your teammate.
- وو ببان، وو ببان. - لا تهاجم زميلك في الفريق.
- Why did you do that? - Kyung Bban, two.
- لماذا فعلت ذلك؟ - كيونغ ببان، اثنان.
Kyung Bban, Kyung Bban, Kyung Bban, Kyung Bban.
كيونغ بابان، كيونغ بابان، كيونغ بابان، كيونغ بابان.
(He missed a beat.)
(لقد غاب عن الفوز.)
- You failed. - You missed a beat.
- لقد فشلت. - لقد فاتك فوز.
- You're a singer.
- لقد فاتك فوز. - أنت مغنية.
You shoot at your teammate.
أنت تطلق النار على زميلك في الفريق.
- Seriously. - Why did you attack your teammate?
- بجد. - لماذا هاجمت زميلك في الفريق؟
- Attack them. - We're a team.
- مهاجمتهم. - نحن فريق.
- It's okay. - It doesn't matter.
- لا بأس. - لا يهم.
- All right. - I was so startled.
- حسنًا. - لقد أذهلني ذلك.
- WOO Bban will start. - WOO Bban.
- سيبدأ WOO Bban. - وو في ب.
- Bban, Bban, Bbans Game - Bban, Bban, Bbans Game
- Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans - Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans
Kyung Bban, two.
كيونغ ببان، اثنان.
(He got eliminated a moment ago.)
(لقد تم القضاء عليه منذ لحظة.)
- Kyung Bban... - Kyung Bban, Kyung Bban...
- كيونغ ببان... - كيونغ ببان، كيونغ ببان...
(Kyung Bban participates even though he's out.)
(يشارك كيونغ بان بالرغم من خروجه.)
- Kyung Bban... Sorry. - Kyung Bban, Kyung Bban...
- كيونغ ببان... آسف. - كيونغ بابان، كيونغ بابان...
Why are you saying it?
لماذا تقول ذلك؟
(WOO Bban only attacks Kyung Bban.)
(WOO Bban يهاجم Kyung Bban فقط.)
- Keep going. - That was great.
- يستمر في التقدم. - ًكان كبيرا.
- I thought he was in the game.
- اعتقدت أنه كان في اللعبة. - ًكان كبيرا.
You guys are quite funny.
أنتم يا رفاق مضحكون للغاية.
You guys are good.
أنتم جيدون يا رفاق.
You guys are good at variety shows.
أنتم يا رفاق جيدون في العروض المتنوعة.
He summoned an eliminated member.
لقد استدعى عضوًا تمت إزالته.
- Bban, Bban, Bbans Game - Bban, Bban, Bbans Game
- Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans - Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans
Chris Bban, three.
كريس بان، ثلاثة.
Chris Bban, Chris Bban, Chris Bban, Chris Bban.
كريس بابان، كريس بابان، كريس بابان، كريس بابان.
- There you go. - Hee, three.
- ها أنت ذا. - هي، ثلاثة.
Hee, three.
هي، ثلاثة.
- You failed. - Hee.
- لقد فشلت. - هي.
- How cute. I like him. - That's funny.
- كم هو لطيف. أنا أحبه. - هذا مضحك.
- YOUNG Bban, one. - YOUNG Bban, YOUNG Bban...
- الشاب ببان، واحد. - شاب ببان، شاب ببان...
- You failed.
- لقد فشلت. - لقد فشلت.
- He's good.
- لقد فشلت. - انه جيد.
Hee Chul's ALL KILL PROJECT.
مشروع Hee Chul's ALL KILL.
You guys are ALLDAY PROJECT, right?
أنتم يا رفاق مشروع طوال اليوم، أليس كذلك؟
I'm ALL KILL PROJECT.
أنا كل مشروع القتل.
- That's right. - ALL KILL PROJECT.
- هذا صحيح. - كل مشروع القتل.
- Let's begin. - It's 3 to 2 now.
- لنبدأ. - إنها الساعة 3 إلى 2 الآن.
- The tables have been turned. - All right.
- لقد انقلبت الطاولة . - حسنًا.
- Hee Chul will start. - Set...
- سيبدأ هيي تشول. - تعيين...
- Once they're out, it'll end. - Let's take out BAI Bban.
- بمجرد خروجهم، سوف ينتهي الأمر. - دعونا نخرج باي ببان.
Both teams had four members get eliminated,
كان لدى كلا الفريقين أربعة أعضاء تم القضاء عليهم،
so why does that team have four members remaining?
فلماذا بقي لهذا الفريق أربعة أعضاء؟
- Three members remain.
- يبقى ثلاثة أعضاء. - يبقى ثلاثة أعضاء.
Ho Dong isn't sitting at the front.
هو دونغ لا يجلس في المقدمة.
Ho Dong is in the back.
هو دونغ في الخلف.
You made a grave mistake.
لقد ارتكبت خطأ فادحا.
AN Bban.
الببان.
- How could you say that? - I'm sorry.
- كيف يمكنك أن تقول ذلك؟ - أنا آسف.
- Are you making fun of me?
- هل تسخر مني؟ - أنا آسف.
- I'm so sorry. - From here,
- أنا آسف جدا. - من هنا،
it really looks like he's at the front.
يبدو حقًا أنه في المقدمة.
- I'm so sorry. - I thought four members remained.
- أنا آسف جدا. - اعتقدت بقي أربعة أعضاء.
I thought four members remained.
اعتقدت أن أربعة أعضاء بقيوا.
- I'm sorry. - Go back further.
- أنا آسف. - العودة أبعد من ذلك.
- Let's begin. - I took two steps back.
- لنبدأ. - لقد اتخذت خطوتين إلى الوراء.
- Go back further. - Let's begin.
- العودة أبعد من ذلك. - لنبدأ.
- Bban, Bban, Bbans Game - Bban, Bban, Bbans Game
- Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans - Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans
TAR Bban, one.
تار ببان، واحد.
TAR Bban, TAR Bban, TAR Bban, TAR Bban.
احصل على BBAN، احصل على BBAN، احصل على BBAN، احصل على BBAN.
(He didn't add an accent.)
(لم يضف لهجة.)
You failed.
لقد فشلت.
Hey!
يا!
We're bad at this.
نحن سيئون في هذا.
BAI Bban!
باي ببان!
- Only BAILEY remains. - Let's turn the tables.
- يبقى بيلي فقط. - دعونا نقلب الطاولة.
One member remains.
بقي عضو واحد.
It's BAI Bban versus Sang Bban, Cheol Bban, and Hee Bban.
إنه BAI Bban مقابل Sang Bban و Cheol Bban و Hee Bban.
- Bban, Bban, Bbans Game - Bban, Bban, Bbans Game
- Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans - Bban، Bban، لعبة Bbans
- BAI Bban, two. - BAI Bban, BAI Bban.
- باي ببان، اثنان. - باي ببان، باي ببان.
- There you go. - Sang Bban, two.
- ها أنت ذا. - سانغ ببان، اثنان.
Sang Bban, Sang Bban, Sang Bban, Sang Bban.
سانغ ببان، سانغ ببان، سانغ ببان، سانغ ببان.
- There you go. - BAI Bban, three.
- ها أنت ذا. - باي ببان، ثلاثة.
BAI Bban, BAI Bban. BAI Bban, BAI Bban.
باي ببان، باي ببان. باي ببان، باي ببان.
Cheol Bban, three.
موسيقى ببان، ثلاثة.
Cheol Bban, Cheol Bban, Cheol Bban, Cheol Bban.
موسيقى ببان، موسيقى ببان، موسيقى ببان، موسيقى ببان.
Cheol Bban, four.
موسيقى ببان، أربعة.
I...
أنا...
(BAI Bban is out.)
(باي ببان خارج.)
Bang, bang, bang!
بانغ، بانغ، بانغ!
Team Men on a Mission won...
فاز فريق رجال في مهمة...
a snack that's popular among Gen Zers.
وجبة خفيفة تحظى بشعبية كبيرة بين جنرال زيرز.
A snack you can enjoy gnawing on,
وجبة خفيفة يمكنك الاستمتاع بقضمها،
- corn rib will be given. - Yes!
- سيتم إعطاء ضلع الذرة. - نعم!
You won't get it now.
لن تحصل عليه الآن.
The snacks you've won...
الوجبات الخفيفة التي ربحتها...
will be given to you at once after the games end.
سيتم إعطاؤها لك مرة واحدة بعد انتهاء الألعاب.
- Let's go. - Now comes the second game...
- دعنا نذهب. - والآن تأتي المباراة الثانية...
that was popular in the 2010s.
التي كانت شائعة في 2010s.
It's the Hoppang Jjinppang Daeppang Game.
إنها لعبة Hoppang Jjinppang Daeppang.
It's the upgraded version of 007 Bang.
إنها النسخة المطورة من 007 بانج.
If someone directs "Ho" at you,
إذا قام شخص ما بتوجيه كلمة "Ho" إليك،
you raise both hands and say, "Bang!"
ترفع كلتا يديك وتقول: "بانغ!"
For "Ho," you do it yourself.
بالنسبة لـ "هو"، أنت تفعل ذلك بنفسك.
For "Jjin,"
بالنسبة لـ "جين"
the ones on your sides say, "Bang!"
الذين على جانبك يقولون "بانغ!"
You shouldn't do it.
لا يجب أن تفعل ذلك.
For "Dae," everyone except you...
بالنسبة لـ "داي"، الجميع ما عداك...
- should say, "Bang!" - "Bang!"
- ينبغي أن يقول، "الانفجار!" - "انفجار!"
- WOOCHAN will start. - Okay.
- سيبدأ ووشان. - تمام.
- No! - Five, six, seven, eight.
- لا! - خمسة، ستة، سبعة، ثمانية.
- Hoppang, Jjinppang, Daeppang!
- القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang! - القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang!
- Let's go and eat bread!
- دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز! - دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز!
- Ho! - Bang!
- هو! - انفجار!
- You're out. - No, "Ho" was directed at you.
- أنت خارج. - لا، "هو" كانت موجهة إليك.
- So I did it. - You confused it with "Jjin."
- لذلك فعلت ذلك. - لقد خلطت بينه وبين "جين".
- You're out. Please stand up. - That startled me.
- أنت خارج. من فضلك قف. - لقد أذهلني ذلك.
Wait in your car.
انتظر في سيارتك.
- Then... - I'll go to my car for real.
- إذن... - سأذهب إلى سيارتي حقًا.
- Come on. - No.
- تعال. - لا.
- Don't pull the chair out. - Show us.
- لا تسحب الكرسي. - تبين لنا.
- That's right.
- لا تسحب الكرسي. - هذا صحيح.
- Go to the chair. - Leave the circle.
- اذهب إلى الكرسي. - اترك الدائرة.
- Go ahead. - All right.
- تفضل. - حسنًا.
- Kyung Hoon got attacked, - Okay.
- كيونج هون تعرض للهجوم - حسنًا.
so he'll begin.
لذلك سوف يبدأ.
- Hoppang, Jjinppang, Daeppang!
- القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang! - القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang!
- Let's go and eat bread!
- دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز! - دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز!
- Ho! - Bang!
- هو! - انفجار!
Dae!
داي!
(Everyone raises their hands.)
(الجميع يرفعون أيديهم).
- Ho! - Bang!
- هو! - انفجار!
Jjin!
ججين!
Ho!
هو!
- Jjin!
- ججين! - انفجار!
- Ho! - Bang!
- هو! - انفجار!
- Hold on. - BAILEY didn't raise her hands.
- يتمسك. - بيلي لم ترفع يديها.
- BAILEY.
- بيلي لم ترفع يديها. - بيلي.
- This is hard. - BAILEY is out.
- هذا صعب. - بيلي خارج.
This game will make my voice go hoarse.
هذه اللعبة سوف تجعل صوتي أجش.
Everyone is good.
الجميع جيد.
- Guys, please pick up the speed. - That's right.
- يا شباب، يرجى رفع السرعة. - هذا صحيح.
- You guys are like... - It's hard.
- يا رفاق مثل... - إنه أمر صعب.
- Don't do this. - I think people are nervous.
- لا تفعل هذا. - أعتقد أن الناس متوترون.
People are like sloths.
الناس مثل الكسلان.
- I'll go first. - Ho Dong will begin.
- سأذهب أولا. - سيبدأ هو دونغ.
- All right. - Let's go.
- حسنًا. - دعنا نذهب.
- Hoppang, Jjinppang, Daeppang!
- القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang! - القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang!
- Let's go and eat bread!
- دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز! - دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز!
- Ho! - Bang!
- هو! - انفجار!
Jjin!
ججين!
- Ho! - Bang! Dae!
-. هو!! -- لقد ضربت! داي!
- Bang! - Bang! That startled me.
- انفجار! - انفجار! لقد أذهلني ذلك.
- Ho! - Bang!
- هو! - انفجار!
- Gosh, I'm sorry. - Jjin! Bang!
- يا إلهي، أنا آسف. - ججين! انفجار!
- Dae? - Bang!
- هناك هناك؟ -- لقد ضربت!
(Kyung Hoon gets eliminated for missing the timing.)
(يتم إقصاء كيونغ هون بسبب إضاعته للتوقيت.)
He's out.
لقد خرج.
I was so surprised. He attacked me.
لقد فوجئت جدا. لقد هاجمني.
(He suddenly tried to take out his teammate.)
(فجأة حاول إخراج زميله في الفريق).
(I'm sorry.)
(أنا آسف.)
(Flailing)
(يخفق)
(He belatedly pointed to himself.)
(وأشار متأخرا إلى نفسه.)
- Soo Geun will attack.
- سو جيون سوف يهاجم. - سو جيون سوف يهاجم.
- Soo Geun.
- سو جيون سوف يهاجم. - سو جيون.
- Hoppang, Jjinppang, Daeppang!
- القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang! - القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang!
- Let's go and eat bread!
- دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز! - دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز!
- Ho! - Bang! Jjin!
- هو! - انفجار! ججين!
- Bang!
- انفجار! - انفجار!
- Jjin!
- ججين! - انفجار!
- Dae! - Bang!
- هناك! -- لقد ضربت!
(It's so confusing.)
(إنه أمر محير للغاية.)
- Why did you say, "Dae?" - It was great.
- لماذا قلت، "داي؟" - كان رائعا.
You could've gone with "Jjin" or "Ho."
كان بإمكانك اختيار "Jjin" أو "Ho".
Why "Dae" instead of "Jjin" or "Ho?"
لماذا "داي" بدلاً من "جين" أو "هو"؟
- She's good. - That startled me.
- إنها جيدة. - لقد أذهلني ذلك.
(Soo Geun is out.)
(سو جيون خارج.)
- "Dae..." - Listen, guys.
- "داي..." - اسمعوا يا رفاق.
- You'll win... - Will you tell them to understand?
- ستفوز... - هل ستقول لهم ليفهموا؟
if you understand the game.
إذا فهمت اللعبة.
You're nervous...
أنت عصبي...
because you don't understand it.
لأنك لا تفهم ذلك.
All right. Let's begin.
حسنًا. لنبدأ.
- Hoppang, Jjinppang, Daeppang!
- القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang! - القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang!
- Let's go and eat bread!
- دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز! - دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز!
- Jjin! - Bang!
- ججين! - انفجار!
- Ho! - Bang! Dae!
-. هو!! -- لقد ضربت! داي!
- Bang!
- انفجار! - انفجار!
- Dae!
- هناك! -- لقد ضربت!
(Ho Dong is out.)
(هو دونغ خارج.)
"Dae" threw you off, right?
"داي" طردك، أليس كذلك؟
(The man with 10 years of experience tried to school the newbies.)
(الرجل الذي يتمتع بخبرة 10 سنوات حاول تعليم المبتدئين).
- (- Dae! - (Bang!)
- (-أ (أنا - - - مخلفاتها!
("Dae" made him crumble.)
("داي" جعله ينهار.)
- "Dae" threw you off, right? - My goodness.
- "داي" طردك، أليس كذلك؟ - يا إلهي.
- "Dae" throws you off. - You know...
- "داي" يرميك. - أنت تعرف...
Why did I do that?
لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
- Well done. - "Dae" throws you off.
- أحسنت. - "داي" يرميك.
- Seriously. - "Dae" is hard.
- بجد. - "داي" صعب.
Gosh, I said "Bang" so loudly.
يا إلهي، لقد قلت "بانغ" بصوت عالٍ جداً.
We're good at games.
نحن جيدون في الألعاب.
They're much better.
إنهم أفضل بكثير.
It's 5 to 3 right now.
إنها من 5 إلى 3 الآن.
- Let's go. - It's so awkward.
- دعنا نذهب. - إنه أمر محرج للغاية.
- Jjin! - Bang!
- ججين! - انفجار!
- Ho! - What?
- هو! - ماذا؟
- You said "Bang" after "Jjin." - What was that?
- لقد قلت "بانغ" بعد "جين". - ماذا كان هذا؟
- Ho! - Bang!
- هو! - انفجار!
Jjin!
ججين!
(Flinching)
(الجفل)
- You didn't do it. - Christian is out.
- أنت لم تفعل ذلك. - كريستيان خارج.
- You have a chance. - Let's do well.
- لديك فرصة. - دعونا نفعل جيدا.
- Let's go. - You have a chance.
- دعنا نذهب. - لديك فرصة.
- It's confusing. - TARZZAN will attack.
- إنه أمر محير. - طرزان سوف يهاجم.
- Hoppang, Jjinppang, Daeppang!
- القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang! - القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang!
- Let's go and eat bread!
- دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز! - دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز!
Ho!
هو!
Bang! Dae!
دبليو كاتر! داي!
- Bang!
- انفجار! - انفجار!
- Dae!
- هناك! -- لقد ضربت!
- I didn't raise my hands. - There you go.
- لم أرفع يدي. - ها أنت ذا.
- I didn't do it. - He didn't do it.
- لم أفعل ذلك. - لم يفعل ذلك.
- That counts.
- هذا مهم. - لم يفعل ذلك.
- No.
- لم يفعل ذلك. - لا.
My hands were on my thighs.
كانت يدي على فخذي.
(His hands were on his thighs.)
(كانت يديه على فخذيه).
I didn't take them off.
أنا لم خلعهم.
- I didn't take them off. - Well done.
- أنا لم خلعهم. - أحسنت.
- That counts. - Had I taken them off,
- هذا مهم. - لو خلعتهم،
I would've accepted defeat.
كنت سأقبل الهزيمة.
- Well done. - I didn't take them off.
- أحسنت. - أنا لم خلعهم.
- That counts.
- هذا مهم. - هذا مهم.
- Well done.
- هذا مهم. - أحسنت.
- Jang Hoon will begin. - He makes the rules.
- سيبدأ جانغ هون. - هو الذي يضع القواعد.
Five, six, seven, eight.
خمسة، ستة، سبعة، ثمانية.
- Hoppang, Jjinppang, Daeppang!
- القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang! - القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang!
- Let's go and eat bread!
- دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز! - دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز!
- Ho! - Bang!
- هو! - انفجار!
- Jjin!
- ججين! - انفجار!
- Ho. - What?
- هو. - ماذا؟
- Why did you raise your hands? - You startled me.
- لماذا رفعت يديك؟ - لقد أذهلتني.
Jang Hoon, why did you raise them?
جانغ هون، لماذا قمت بتربيتهم؟
He suddenly said, "Bang!"
قال فجأة: "بانغ!"
- Come on out. - Jang Hoon was startled.
- هيا خارجا. - كان جانغ هون مذهولا.
I lasted pretty long, right?
لقد صمدت طويلاً، أليس كذلك؟
- This is bad. - It's a 1-on-4 match.
- هذا سيء. - إنها مباراة 1 ضد 4.
- Get ready. - Let's go.
- استعد. - دعنا نذهب.
- Hee Chul, take them out. - They're really good.
- هي تشول، أخرجهم. - إنهم جيدون حقًا.
- Let's go.
- دعنا نذهب. - دعنا نذهب.
- Hee Chul will attack. - Okay.
- هي تشول سوف يهاجم. - تمام.
- Hoppang, Jjinppang, Daeppang!
- القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang! - القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang!
- Let's go and eat bread!
- دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز! - دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز!
Ho!
هو!
- I'm out. - She's out.
- أنا خارج. - لقد خرجت.
YOUNGSEO.
يونجسيو.
- Okay. - My goodness.
- تمام. - يا إلهي.
- An ace member is out. - Let's go.
- عضو الآس خارج. - دعنا نذهب.
- Okay. - Let's begin.
- تمام. - لنبدأ.
- Hee Chul will attack. - Concentrate.
- هي تشول سوف يهاجم. - يركز.
Five, six, seven, eight.
خمسة، ستة، سبعة، ثمانية.
- Hoppang, Jjinppang, Daeppang!
- القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang! - القفز، Jjinppang، Daeppang!
- Let's go and eat bread!
- دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز! - دعنا نذهب ونأكل الخبز!
- Ho! - Bang!
- هو! - انفجار!
- Jjin!
- ججين! - انفجار!
- Dae!
- هناك! -- لقد ضربت!
(ADP wins Round 2.)
(ADP يفوز بالجولة الثانية.)
(Screaming)
(صراخ)
Team ADP won.
فاز فريق ADP.
- Did we lose? - Team ADP...
- هل خسرنا؟ - فريق ADP...
will receive the snacks everybody loves.
سوف تتلقى الوجبات الخفيفة التي يحبها الجميع.
They'll receive the best snacks, fried chilis and tteokbokki.
سيحصلون على أفضل الوجبات الخفيفة والفلفل الحار المقلي والتيتوكبوكي.
(Fried chilis and tteokbokki)
(الفلفل الحار المقلي و تتوكبوكي)
The last game, the third game remains.
المباراة الأخيرة، وتبقى المباراة الثالثة.
The last game...
المباراة الاخيرة...
keeps both the Gen Zers and the oldies on their toes.
يبقي كلا من الجيل Zers والقدامى على أصابع قدميهم.
- It's the Triple Meter Game. - Yes.
- إنها لعبة المتر الثلاثي. - نعم.
It's I Am Ground...
إنها أنا الأرض...
in triple meter.
في متر ثلاثي.
Let me explain.
اسمحوا لي أن أشرح.
Not quadruple meter?
لا رباعية متر؟
(Singing a tune)
(يغني لحناً)
- One, two, three - One, two, three
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة
In this manner... Ho Dong, two.
بهذه الطريقة... هو دونغ، اثنان.
- Ho Dong, Ho Dong. - There you go.
- هو دونغ، هو دونغ. - ها أنت ذا.
Shin Dong, one.
شين دونغ، واحد.
Shin Dong. That's how you do it.
شين دونغ. هذه هي الطريقة التي تفعل بها ذلك.
It's hard since it's in triple meter.
إنه أمر صعب لأنه في المتر الثلاثي.
It's like a waltz.
انها مثل الفالس.
- Ho Dong, four. - It's hard.
- هو دونغ، أربعة. - إنه صعب.
- But it's triple meter. - If it's Ho Dong, one...
- لكنه ثلاثة أمتار. - إذا كان هو دونغ، واحد...
What are we supposed to call him?
ماذا يفترض بنا أن نسميه؟
- Christian.
- مسيحي. - مسيحي.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
All right.
حسنًا.
- Don't make me do it. - Let's begin.
- لا تجعلني أفعل ذلك. - لنبدأ.
- Christian will begin. - Christian.
- سيبدأ المسيحي. - مسيحي.
Let's begin slowly.
لنبدأ ببطء.
Bam, barabam
بام، بارابام
- Barabam, barabam - Barabam, barabam
- برابام، برابام - برابام، برابام
- One, two, three - One, two, three
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة
- One, two, three - Let's begin. Set, go.
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - لنبدأ. اضبط، اذهب.
Jang Hoon, two.
جانغ هون، اثنان.
Jang Hoon, Jang Hoon.
جانغ هون، جانغ هون.
- Christian... - You failed.
- كريستيان... - لقد فشلت.
- I think I'll win. - It's unexpected,
- أعتقد أنني سأفوز. - الأمر غير متوقع،
- but he's pretty bad at games. - I told you...
- لكنه سيء ​​جدًا في الألعاب. - أخبرتك...
that his name was confusing.
أن اسمه كان محيرًا.
Why did you attack Christian then?
لماذا هاجمت كريستيان إذن؟
He caught my eye!
لقد لفت انتباهي!
For goodness' sake!
من أجل الخير!
- Christian will begin. - It's hard to call his name.
- سيبدأ المسيحي. - من الصعب أن ننادي باسمه.
- It's hard. - Set, go.
- إنه صعب. - اضبط، انطلق.
- One, two, three - Who?
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - من؟
- Christian will begin. Set, go. - Slowly.
- سيبدأ المسيحي. اضبط، اذهب. - ببطء.
Kyung Hoon, two.
كيونغ هون، اثنان.
Kyung Hoon, Kyung Hoon.
كيونغ هون، كيونغ هون.
Christian, four.
كريستيان، أربعة.
Four? Four doesn't...
أربعة؟ أربعة لا...
Four doesn't work.
أربعة لا يعمل.
- Christian, three. - Get out.
- كريستيان، ثلاثة. - اخرج.
- We mess up while attacking.
- كريستيان، ثلاثة. - نحن نخطئ أثناء الهجوم.
- Christian will begin. - Okay.
- سيبدأ المسيحي. - تمام.
- One, two, three - One, two, three
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة
Set, go.
اضبط، اذهب.
Soo Geun, three.
سو جيون، ثلاثة أعوام.
Soo Geun, Soo Geun, Soo Geun.
سو جيون، سو جيون، سو جيون.
TARZZAN, two.
طرزان، اثنان.
TARZZAN, TARZZAN.
طرزان، طرزان.
Yeong Cheol, one.
يونغ تشيول، واحد.
Yeong Cheol. TARZZAN, two.
يونج تشيول. طرزان، اثنان.
- You failed. - Was it off-beat?
- لقد فشلت. - هل كان خارج الإيقاع؟
- Attacking is hard. - Yes.
- الهجوم صعب. - نعم.
We're losing spectacularly.
نحن نخسر بشكل مذهل.
I know. What are you guys going to do?
أنا أعرف. ماذا ستفعلون يا رفاق؟
- Attacking is hard. - TARZZAN will begin.
- الهجوم صعب. - طرزان ستبدأ.
- One, two, three - One, two, three
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة
Ho Dong, one.
هو دونغ، واحد.
Ho Dong. WOOCHAN, two.
هو دونغ. ووشان، اثنان.
WOOCHAN, WOOCHAN. Ho Dong, two.
ووشان، ووشان. هو دونغ، اثنان.
Ho Dong, Ho Dong. WOOCHAN, one.
هو دونغ، هو دونغ. ووشان، واحد.
WOOCHAN. Ho Dong, two.
ووشان. هو دونغ، اثنان.
Ho Dong, Ho Dong. WOOCHAN, three.
هو دونغ، هو دونغ. ووشان، ثلاثة.
WOOCHAN, WOOCHAN, WOOCHAN.
ووشان، ووشان، ووشان.
- Ho Dong, three. - Ho Dong, Ho Dong, Ho Dong.
- هو دونغ، ثلاثة. - هو دونغ، هو دونغ، هو دونغ.
WOOCHAN, two.
ووشان، اثنان.
WOOCHAN, WOOCHAN.
ووشان، ووشان.
Yeong Cheol, two... Never mind.
يونغ تشيول، اثنان... لا يهم.
- Yeong Cheol isn't here. - Yes! Come on!
- يونج تشيول ليس هنا. - نعم! تعال!
- Well done. - He got confused.
- أحسنت. - حصل على الخلط.
WOOCHAN.
ووشان.
- Yes! Come on! - He got confused.
- نعم! تعال! - حصل على الخلط.
- He wanted to look cool. - Yeong Cheol.
- أراد أن يبدو رائعا. - يونج تشيول.
- Ho Dong. - Well done.
- هو دونغ. - أحسنت.
- Ho Dong is good. - I thought you guys were dating.
- هو دونغ جيد. - اعتقدت يا رفاق كنتم تتواعدون.
- We met eyes so many times. - I didn't see anyone else.
- التقينا العيون مرات عديدة. - لم أرى أي شخص آخر.
My eyes were fixed on him.
كانت عيناي مثبتتين عليه.
I didn't see anyone else.
لم أرى أي شخص آخر.
- All right. - Ho Dong.
- حسنًا. - هو دونغ.
- One, two, three - One, two, three
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة
- One, two, three - Set, go.
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - استعد، انطلق.
YOUNGSEO, two.
يونغسيو، اثنان.
YOUNGSEO, YOUNGSEO.
يونجسيو، يونجسيو.
- Hee Chul, one. - Incorrect.
- هي تشول، واحد. - غير صحيح.
The beat was off.
كان الإيقاع معطلاً.
- Bye. - Calling the name is hard.
- الوداع. - مناداة الاسم صعب.
- I don't know. - The beat is hard.
- لا أعرف. - الإيقاع صعب .
- The beat is so fast. - YOUNGSEO.
- الإيقاع سريع جدًا. - يونجسيو.
- That's right.
- الإيقاع سريع جدًا. - هذا صحيح.
YOUNGSEO and WOOCHAN, at the second beat...
يونغسيو و ووشان، في الضربة الثانية...
after clapping, you say, "Hee Chul, two."
بعد التصفيق، تقول، "هي تشول، اثنان."
Many apologies.
اعتذارات كثيرة.
Wasn't she being sarcastic?
لم تكن الساخرة؟
Gosh, many apologies.
يا إلهي، اعتذارات كثيرة.
- All right. - All right. Many apologies.
- حسنًا. - حسنًا. اعتذارات كثيرة.
(Did I hear that right?)
(هل سمعت ذلك بشكل صحيح؟)
- YOUNGSEO. - All right.
- يونجسيو. - حسنًا.
- Ta-da. - YOUNGSEO.
- تا دا. - يونجسيو.
- All right. Many apologies. - I think YOUNGSEO is upset.
- حسنًا. اعتذارات كثيرة. - أعتقد أن يونغسيو مستاء.
- YOUNGSEO.
- يونجسيو. - يونجسيو.
- Her red hair is telling. - YOUNGSEO,
- شعرها الأحمر يقول. - يونجسيو،
I sincerely apologize.
أنا أعتذر بصدق.
She keeps using her both hands.
إنها تستمر في استخدام كلتا يديها.
- Let's go. - Ho Dong will begin.
- دعنا نذهب. - سيبدأ هو دونغ.
- Yeong Cheol, one. - Five, six, seven, eight.
- يونغ تشيول، واحد. - خمسة، ستة، سبعة، ثمانية.
(The game begins with Ho Dong!)
(تبدأ اللعبة مع هو دونغ!)
- Set, go. - One, two, three
- اضبط، انطلق. - واحد اثنين ثلاثة
ANNIE, three.
آني، ثلاثة.
ANNIE...
آني...
(Ho Dong looks elsewhere.)
(هو دونغ يبحث في مكان آخر.)
(The queen of short-term memory is out.)
(ملكة الذاكرة قصيرة المدى خرجت.)
- I'm sorry. - I thought you were good at it.
- أنا آسف. - اعتقدت أنك كنت جيدة في ذلك.
- ANNIE, when you do this... - You know,
- آني، عندما تفعلين هذا... - كما تعلمين،
you should look the person in the eye.
يجب أن تنظر إلى عيني الشخص.
- You have so many excuses. - It's only polite.
- لديك الكثير من الأعذار. - إنه مؤدب فقط.
Call the lawyer.
اتصل بالمحامي.
You should've looked me in the eye.
كان عليك أن تنظر لي في العين.
- I used a feint earlier. - He made a timed attack.
- لقد استخدمت خدعة في وقت سابق. - لقد قام بهجوم موقوت.
- TARZZAN did it 1st.
- طرزان فعلها أولاً. - طرزان فعلها أولاً.
- TARZZAN. - Don't put us in the same bracket.
- طرزان. - لا تضعونا في نفس الفئة.
- Eye contact. - I don't use a feint.
- التواصل بالعين . - أنا لا أستخدم الخدعة.
- He won't eat ramyeon at her place. - I'm sorry,
- لن يأكل الراميون في مكانها. - أنا آسف،
but when will you move back?
ولكن متى ستعود؟
We shouldn't take Ho Dong to ANNIE's place.
لا ينبغي لنا أن نأخذ هو دونغ إلى منزل آني.
- Ho Dong should be excluded. - No, he should still come.
- ينبغي استبعاد هو دونغ. - لا، لا يزال يتعين عليه أن يأتي.
- I see. - This game doesn't do me any good.
- أرى. - هذه اللعبة لا تفيدني.
I'll wait in the alley.
سأنتظر في الزقاق.
- Let's begin. Set, go. - Let's begin.
- لنبدأ. اضبط، اذهب. - لنبدأ.
(Ho Dong will begin!)
(سيبدأ هو دونغ!)
- One, two, three - One, two, three
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة
- Five, six, seven, eight. - One, two, three
- خمسة، ستة، سبعة، ثمانية. - واحد اثنين ثلاثة
TARZZAN, three.
طرزان، ثلاثة.
TARZZAN, TARZZAN, TARZZAN.
طرزان، طرزان، طرزان.
Sang Min, two.
سانغ مين، اثنان.
Sang Min, Sang Min.
في مين، من مين.
TARZZAN, three.
طرزان، ثلاثة.
TARZZAN, TARZZAN, TARZZAN.
طرزان، طرزان، طرزان.
Soo Geun, one.
سو جيون، واحد.
Soo Geun. Baby, three.
سو جيون. طفل، ثلاثة.
(Baby?)
(طفل؟)
Baby, baby, baby, one more time!
حبيبتي، حبيبتي، حبيبتي، مرة أخرى!
- "Baby, three." - Baby.
- "طفلي، ثلاثة." - طفل.
You're still a baby.
أنت لا تزال طفلا.
You aren't mature yet, baby.
أنت لم تنضج بعد يا عزيزي.
You're a baby!
أنت طفل!
(BAILEY gets scolded for no reason.)
(يتم توبيخ بيلي بدون سبب.)
For goodness' sake.
في سبيل الخير.
Why did I say "Baby?"
لماذا قلت "حبيبي"؟
- You know... - I said "Baby..."
- كما تعلم... - قلت "حبيبي..."
- instead of "BAILEY." - It's hard to get the name right.
- بدلاً من "بيلي". - من الصعب الحصول على الاسم الصحيح.
- Baby. - They're really good.
- طفل. - إنهم جيدون حقًا.
- It's no joke. - It's a 3-on-3 match.
- إنها ليست مزحة. - إنها مباراة 3 ضد 3.
- You know... - Let's do this.
- كما تعلم... - دعونا نفعل هذا.
One, two, three
واحد اثنين ثلاثة
Set, go.
اضبط، اذهب.
BAILEY, two.
بيلي، اثنان.
BAILEY, BAILEY.
بيلي، بيلي.
- Ho... - You failed.
- هو... - لقد فشلت.
(She was doing well.)
(كانت في صحة جيدة.)
- All right. - It's okay.
- حسنًا. - لا بأس.
Christian, Christian, Christian.
مسيحي، مسيحي، مسيحي.
Ho Dong, one.
هو دونغ، واحد.
Ho Dong.
هو دونغ.
You failed.
لقد فشلت.
Do well.
أحسنت.
What was that? You were doing so well.
ماذا كان هذا؟ كنت تفعل ذلك بشكل جيد.
- I don't know. - You suddenly got eliminated.
- لا أعرف. - لقد تم القضاء عليك فجأة.
To cheer you guys up at this point,
لكي أشجعكم يا رفاق في هذه المرحلة،
- I'll introduce the last snack. - What?
- سأقدم الوجبة الخفيفة الأخيرة. - ماذا؟
It's the best snack in history that's loved by everyone.
إنها أفضل وجبة خفيفة في التاريخ ومحبوبة من قبل الجميع.
- It's fried chicken. - Fried chicken.
- إنه الدجاج المقلي. - دجاج مقلي.
(Fried chicken)
(دجاج مقلي)
- It's fried chicken. - Okay.
- إنه الدجاج المقلي. - تمام.
- I really want to eat it.
- تمام. - أنا حقا أريد أن أكله.
- Hee Chul. - I was born in the year of rooster,
- هي تشول. - لقد ولدت في عام الديك،
- so I have to eat it. - Same here.
- لذلك لا بد لي من أكله. - نفس الشيء هنا.
- Really?
- حقًا؟ - نفس الشيء هنا.
- Let's begin. - I said hello.
- لنبدأ. - قلت مرحبا.
Christian will attack first.
سوف يهاجم كريستيان أولاً.
Five, six, seven, eight.
خمسة، ستة، سبعة، ثمانية.
- One, two, three - One, two, three
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة
- Hee Chul, three. - Hee Chul, Hee Chul, Hee Chul.
- هي تشول، ثلاثة. - هيي تشول، هيي تشول، هيي تشول.
TARZZAN, one.
طرزان، واحد.
TARZZAN. Sang Min, three.
طرزان. سانغ مين، ثلاثة.
- You failed.
- لقد فشلت. - لقد فشلت.
(To everyone's disappointment, the ace, TARZZAN, gets eliminated.)
(لخيبة أمل الجميع، تم القضاء على الآس طرزان.)
- We'll win.
- لقد فشلت. - سنفوز.
- All right.
- حسنًا. - سنفوز.
- Christian. - You know...
- مسيحي. - أنت تعرف...
- You can do it. - It isn't easy.
- يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك. - ليس من السهل.
Hee Chul will attack.
سوف يهاجم هي تشول.
Five, six, seven, eight.
خمسة، ستة، سبعة، ثمانية.
- One, two, three - One, two, three
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة
(We believe in Christian.)
(نحن نؤمن بالمسيحية.)
- One, two, three - Set, go.
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - استعد، انطلق.
- Christian, three. - Christian, Christian, Christian.
- كريستيان، ثلاثة. - مسيحي، مسيحي، مسيحي.
Hee Chul, two.
هي تشول، اثنان.
Hee Chul, Hee Chul. Christian, one.
هي تشول، هي تشول. كريستيان، واحد.
Christian. Sang Min, three.
مسيحي. سانغ مين، ثلاثة.
Sang Min, Sang Min, Sang Min. Christian, three.
سانغ مين، سانغ مين، سانغ مين. كريستيان، ثلاثة.
You failed.
لقد فشلت.
- His name is so hard. - Okay. Let's go.
- اسمه صعب جدا. - تمام. دعنا نذهب.
(Christian came this far thanks to his name.)
(لقد وصل كريستيان إلى هذا الحد بفضل اسمه.)
- It's too long. - I told you that it was hard.
- إنه طويل أكثر من اللازم. - قلت لك أن الأمر صعب.
I love Mexico!
أنا أحب المكسيك!
- All right. - It's the final match.
- حسنًا. - إنها المباراة النهائية.
(Finally, the last match)
(وأخيرا المباراة الأخيرة)
(My friends believe in me.)
(أصدقائي يؤمنون بي.)
Hee Chul, one.
هي تشول، واحد.
Hee Chul. Christian, three.
هي تشول. كريستيان، ثلاثة.
Christian, Christian, Christian.
مسيحي، مسيحي، مسيحي.
- Hee Chul, two. - Hee Chul, Hee Chul.
- هي تشول، اثنان. - هي تشول، هي تشول.
- Christian, three. - Christian, Christian, Christian.
- كريستيان، ثلاثة. - مسيحي، مسيحي، مسيحي.
Hee Chul, one.
هي تشول، واحد.
Hee Chul. Christian, one.
هي تشول. كريستيان، واحد.
Christian. Hee Chul, three.
مسيحي. هي تشول، ثلاثة.
What was that?
ماذا كان هذا؟
Can't I be happy? Why?
لا أستطيع أن أكون سعيدا؟ لماذا؟
Hey, can't I be happy about moving to the rhythm?
مهلا، ألا يمكنني أن أكون سعيدا بالانتقال إلى الإيقاع؟
- Hey, we were doing well. - We're playing a game.
- مهلا، كنا في حالة جيدة. - نحن نلعب لعبة.
Just now...
الآن...
(It's a mess.)
(إنها فوضى.)
Tequila!
تكيلا!
I thought I was talking to my uncle.
اعتقدت أنني كنت أتحدث مع عمي.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Are you from Mexico?
هل أنت من المكسيك؟
- Suddenly, - The club turned international.
- فجأة - تحول النادي إلى المستوى الدولي.
you spoke in tongue.
لقد تكلمت باللسان.
(The final match resumes.)
(تستأنف المباراة النهائية.)
- One, two, three - One, two, three
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة
- One, two, three - Let's go.
- واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة - هيا بنا.
Set, go.
اضبط، اذهب.
- Hee Chul, three. - Hee Chul, Hee Chul, Hee Chul.
- هي تشول، ثلاثة. - هيي تشول، هيي تشول، هيي تشول.
- Christian, three. - Christian, Christian, Christian.
- كريستيان، ثلاثة. - مسيحي، مسيحي، مسيحي.
Hee Chul, one.
هي تشول، واحد.
Hee Chul. Christian, two.
هي تشول. كريستيان، اثنان.
Christian, Christian.
مسيحي، مسيحي.
- Hee Chul, three. - Hee Chul, Hee Chul, Hee Chul.
- هي تشول، ثلاثة. - هيي تشول، هيي تشول، هيي تشول.
- Christian, three. - Christian, Christian, Christian.
- كريستيان، ثلاثة. - مسيحي، مسيحي، مسيحي.
(They pick up the speed.)
(إنهم يلتقطون السرعة.)
(Everyone becomes absorbed in the league of their own.)
(يصبح الجميع منغمسين في الدوري الخاص بهم.)
Hee Chul, one.
هي تشول، واحد.
Hee Chul. Christian, one.
هي تشول. كريستيان، واحد.
Christian. Hee Chul, three.
مسيحي. هي تشول، ثلاثة.
Hee Chul, Hee Chul, Hee Chul.
هيي تشول، هيي تشول، هيي تشول.
- Christian, three. - Christi, Christian...
- كريستيان، ثلاثة. - كريستي، كريستيان...
Christi, Christian...
كريستي، كريستيان...
(Hee Chul doesn't disappoint.)
(هي تشول لا يخيب أملك).
- You don't disappoint. - I did it!
- أنت لا تخيب. - أنا فعلت هذا!
- Hee Chul. - Well done.
- هي تشول. - أحسنت.
(We admit defeat.)
(نحن نعترف بالهزيمة).
- Thus, fried chicken... - It was so much fun.
- هكذا، الدجاج المقلي... - لقد كان ممتعاً جداً.
- will go to Team Men on a Mission. - I'm sorry.
- سوف يذهب إلى فريق الرجال في مهمة. - أنا آسف.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
- All games are over.
- أنا آسف. - انتهت جميع الألعاب.
Team Men on a Mission...
رجال الفريق في مهمة...
won the 1st and 3rd games and took the corresponding snacks.
فاز في المباراتين الأولى والثالثة وحصل على الوجبات الخفيفة المقابلة.
Team ALLDAY PROJECT won the second game...
فاز فريق ALLDAY PROJECT بالمباراة الثانية...
and took the corresponding snacks.
وأخذ الوجبات الخفيفة المقابلة.
You know, food tastes better...
كما تعلمون، الطعام مذاق أفضل...
when it's shared.
عندما يتم مشاركتها.
What? My thighs turned red!
ماذا؟ تحولت فخذي إلى اللون الأحمر!
Team Men on a Mission...
رجال الفريق في مهمة...
won the 1st and 3rd games and took the corresponding snacks.
فاز في المباراتين الأولى والثالثة وحصل على الوجبات الخفيفة المقابلة.
Team ALLDAY PROJECT won the second game...
فاز فريق ALLDAY PROJECT بالمباراة الثانية...
and took the corresponding snacks.
وأخذ الوجبات الخفيفة المقابلة.
You know, food tastes better...
كما تعلمون، الطعام مذاق أفضل...
when it's shared.
عندما يتم مشاركتها.
What? My thighs turned red!
ماذا؟ تحولت فخذي إلى اللون الأحمر!
New members joined the club on this good day.
انضم أعضاء جدد إلى النادي في هذا اليوم الجيد.
Why don't we enjoy the snacks together?
لماذا لا نستمتع بالوجبات الخفيفة معًا؟
Let's eat together.
دعونا نأكل معا.
- The snacks are on Senior Dong! - Okay.
- الوجبات الخفيفة موجودة على سينيور دونغ! - تمام.
- Let's go. - Will we actually get snacks?
- دعنا نذهب. - هل سنحصل فعلا على وجبات خفيفة؟
Bring in the food.
أحضر الطعام.
- Bring in the food. - Seriously, it was great.
- أحضر الطعام . - على محمل الجد، كان عظيما.
- Show me the chicken. - Seriously, today...
- أرني الدجاج. - بجدية اليوم..
This is great.
هذا عظيم.
Oh, my gosh.
يا إلهي.
(It's a hearty snack set.)
(إنها مجموعة وجبات خفيفة دسمة.)
- Welcome. - We won.
- مرحباً. - فزنا.
- Fried chicken. - What's this?
- دجاج مقلي. - ما هذا؟
I love this brand.
أنا أحب هذه العلامة التجارية.
- Thank you for the food.
- شكرا لك على الطعام. - شكرا لك على الطعام.
- It looks tasty. - Enjoy the food.
- يبدو لذيذا. - استمتع بالطعام.
It's cheese.
انها الجبن.
- Christian. - Thank you.
- مسيحي. - شكرًا لك.
- Fried chicken. - Oh, my gosh. Cheese.
- دجاج مقلي. - يا إلهي. جبن.
What's this? It's a fried chili.
ما هذا؟ إنه فلفل حار مقلي.
The moment I bite into it,
في اللحظة التي أعض فيها،
the aroma of cheese hits me.
رائحة الجبن تضربني.
It isn't regular chicken.
إنه ليس دجاج عادي
- It isn't regular chicken. - It's the Gen Z food.
- إنه ليس دجاجًا عاديًا. - إنه طعام الجيل Z.
It's the new menu. I haven't tried it yet.
إنها القائمة الجديدة. لم أحاول ذلك بعد.
- How is it so tasty? - It's the trendiest these days.
- كيف هو لذيذ جدا؟ - إنها الأكثر عصرية هذه الأيام.
Now that I've tried it, I see why that's the case.
الآن بعد أن حاولت ذلك، أرى لماذا هذا هو الحال.
- Corn. - I see the reason why.
- حبوب ذرة. - أرى السبب.
This isn't a regular sauce.
هذه ليست صلصة عادية.
- I think it's a pineapple sauce. - Yes.
- أعتقد أنها صلصة الأناناس. - نعم.
Dip it in the sauce. Let's see how it is.
اغمسها في الصلصة. دعونا نرى كيف هو.
We got this sauce for the chicken.
لقد حصلنا على هذه الصلصة للدجاج.
It's good. Hee Chul, here.
انها جيدة. هي تشول، هنا.
Try it.
جربه.
- It's tasty. - Yes.
- إنه لذيذ. - نعم.
(He puts sauce on the chicken and takes a big bite.)
(يضع الصلصة على الدجاج ويتناول قضمة كبيرة.)
If you dip it in the sauce, you'll be able to eat endlessly.
إذا غمستها في الصلصة، ستتمكن من تناول الطعام إلى ما لا نهاية.
This isn't a regular sauce.
هذه ليست صلصة عادية.
- I think it's a pineapple sauce. - Yes.
- أعتقد أنها صلصة الأناناس. - نعم.
Dip it in the sauce. Let's see how it is.
اغمسها في الصلصة. دعونا نرى كيف هو.
We got this sauce for the chicken.
لقد حصلنا على هذه الصلصة للدجاج.
It's good. Hee Chul, here.
انها جيدة. هي تشول، هنا.
- Try it. - It's tasty.
- جربه. - إنه لذيذ.
- Yes.
- نعم. - إنه لذيذ.
(He puts sauce on the chicken and takes a big bite.)
(يضع الصلصة على الدجاج ويتناول قضمة كبيرة.)
If you dip it in the sauce, you'll be able to eat endlessly.
إذا غمستها في الصلصة، ستتمكن من تناول الطعام إلى ما لا نهاية.
Pineapple and mayonnaise sauce.
صوص أناناس و مايونيز
- It's really tasty. - Corn rib.
- إنه لذيذ حقًا. - ضلع الذرة .
Look at the powder.
انظر إلى المسحوق.
When I eat it with the pineapple sauce,
عندما أتناوله مع صلصة الأناناس،
the mix of sweetness and saltiness is nice.
مزيج الحلاوة والملوحة جميل.
- Sweetness and saltiness. - The way he talks...
- الحلاوة والملوحة. - طريقة كلامه...
- Nice. - That was realistic.
- لطيف - جيد. - كان ذلك واقعيا.
- It's good, right? - Nice.
- انها جيدة، أليس كذلك؟ - لطيف - جيد.
- It's insane. - It's good.
- إنه مجنون. - إنه جيد.
It's sweet and salty.
انها حلوة ومالحة.
How was it to join the show today?
كيف كان الانضمام إلى العرض اليوم؟
I still can't believe...
مازلت لا أصدق...
that I'm in this classroom.
أنني في هذا الفصل الدراسي.
It'll be a cherished memory for the rest of my life.
ستكون ذكرى عزيزة لبقية حياتي.
We loved having you here.
لقد أحببنا وجودك هنا.
I feel like ALLDAY PROJECT...
أشعر وكأنني مشروع طوال اليوم ...
lost to you guys in terms of energy.
خسرت لكم يا رفاق من حيث الطاقة.
We want to come back here and teach you guys a lesson.
نريد أن نعود إلى هنا ونعلمكم درسًا.
- Thank you. - That's a good idea.
- شكرًا لك. - هذه فكرة جيدة.
- Teach us a lesson. - I had that thought.
- يعلمنا درسا. - كان لدي هذا الفكر.
So you guys should be on your toes.
لذا يا رفاق يجب أن تكونوا على أصابع قدميك.
- He's good. - Just you wait.
- انه جيد. - فقط عليك الانتظار.
Being on this show makes me think,
التواجد في هذا العرض يجعلني أفكر،
"ADP became pretty successful."
"أصبح ADP ناجحًا جدًا."
I feel like I've become a celebrity.
أشعر وكأنني أصبحت من المشاهير.
We had so much fun.
كان لدينا الكثير من المرح.
- Thank you.
- شكرًا لك. - شكرًا لك.
Thank you for coming.
شكرا لحضوركم.
- Okay. - ADP forever!
- تمام. - ADP إلى الأبد!
Forever!
للأبد!
(The preview of next week's episode will be revealed soon.)
(سيتم الكشف عن معاينة حلقة الأسبوع المقبل قريبًا.)
(Across the court of passion,)
(عبر محكمة العاطفة)
(the special transfer students appear.)
(يظهر طلاب النقل الخاص.)
("Rising Eagles" Special)
("النسور الصاعدة" خاص)
(Chon Tae Poong, Park Eun Seok, Son Tae Jin, and Jeong Jin Woon)
(شون تاي بونج، بارك إيون سوك، سون تاي جين، وجيونج جين وون)
(Coach Jang Hoon is leading the Rising Eagles.)
(المدرب جانغ هون يقود فريق النسور الصاعدة).
(Will Jang Hoon buy the Brother School?)
(هل سيشتري جانغ هون مدرسة الأخ؟)
(Coach Tae Poong's thoughts on Coach Seo)
(أفكار المدرب تاي بونج حول المدرب سيو)
(He's too much of a boomer.)
(إنه كثير من الطفرة.)
(There's a controversy of Coach Seo being a boomer.)
(هناك جدل حول كون المدرب سيو من جيل الطفرة.)
(I thought I was a player too.)
(اعتقدت أنني لاعب أيضًا.)
(Tae Jin, the vocalist who went to Seoul National University)
(تاي جين، المنشد الذي ذهب إلى جامعة سيول الوطنية)
(Jang Hoon said,)
(وقال جانج هون،)
("He went to the second-best school in Korea.")
("ذهب إلى ثاني أفضل مدرسة في كوريا.")
(I want to ask him which school is the best.)
(أريد أن أسأله ما هي المدرسة الأفضل.)
(Coach Seo said to Jin Woon, the cheering fairy,)
(قال المدرب سيو لجين وون، الجنية المبتهجة،)
("No cheering.")
("ممنوع الهتاف").
(They expose Jang Hoon endlessly.)
(إنهم يفضحون جانغ هون إلى ما لا نهاية.)
(I should've scolded Jin Woon some more.)
(كان يجب أن أوبخ جين وون أكثر.)
(Eun Seok and Ho Dong met through a table tennis show.)
(التقي إيون سوك وهو دونغ من خلال عرض لتنس الطاولة.)
(Table tennis versus basketball?)
(تنس الطاولة مقابل كرة السلة؟)
(Basketball, of course.)
(كرة السلة بالطبع).
(He'll be a starting player in the next season by 100 percent.)
(سيكون لاعبًا أساسيًا في الموسم المقبل بنسبة 100 بالمائة).
(Team Jang Hoon versus Team Tae Poong)
(فريق جانج هون ضد فريق تاي بونج)
(The passionate basketball match)
(مباراة كرة السلة الحماسية)
(Seo Jang Hoon!)
(سيو جانج هون!)
(Come on out.)
(تعال خارج.)
(The best shooting skills!)
(أفضل مهارات الرماية!)
(Fancy talent!)
(موهبة خيالية!)
(Shooting)
(إطلاق نار)
(Scoring a goal without fail)
(تسجيل هدف بدون فشل)
(The Men on a Mission members struggle.)
(يكافح أعضاء "الرجال في مهمة").
(It's a ruckus.)
(إنها ضجة.)
(Even Coach Jang Hoon struggles.)
(حتى المدرب جانغ هون يعاني).
(Let's dive into the legendary match of the transfer students!)
(دعونا نتعمق في المباراة الأسطورية للطلاب المنقولين!)
(Don't miss Men on a Mission on Saturday at 9pm.)
(لا تفوت الرجال في مهمة يوم السبت الساعة 9 مساءً.)